<publications><publication><id>han_1</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/26f2093c813fdb5b3b3dac458004e732c/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Investigating H$\alpha$, UV, and IR star-formation rate diagnostics for
  a large sample of z ~ 2 galaxies</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Irene</first><last>Shivaei</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Naveen A.</first><last>Reddy</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Charles C.</first><last>Steidel</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Alice E.</first><last>Shapley</last></author></authors><keys><key>galaxy</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>calibration</key><key>dust</key><key>high-z</key><key>sfr</key></keys><date>2015-03-16 09:29:02</date><changeDate>2015-03-16 09:29:02</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2015</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1503.03929</url><note>cite arxiv:1503.03929Comment: Accepted for publication in ApJ, 11 pages, 6 figures, 2 tables</note><abstract>We use a sample of 262 spectroscopically confirmed star-forming galaxies at
redshifts $2.08z2.51$ to compare H$\alpha$, UV, and IR
star-formation-rate diagnostics and to investigate the dust properties of the
galaxies. At these redshifts, the H$\alpha$ line shifts to the $K_s$-band. By
comparing $K_s$-band photometry to underlying stellar population model fits
to other UV, optical, and near-infrared data, we infer the H$\alpha$ flux for
each galaxy. We obtain the best agreement between H$\alpha$- and UV-based SFRs
if we assume that the ionized gas and stellar continuum are reddened by the
same value and that the Calzetti attenuation curve is applied to both. Aided
with MIPS 24$\mu$m data, we find that an attenuation curve steeper than the
Calzetti curve is needed to reproduce the observed IR/UV ratios of galaxies
younger than 100 Myr. Furthermore, using the bolometric star-formation rate
inferred from the UV and mid-IR data (SFR$_IR$+SFR$_UV$), we calculated the
conversion between the H$\alpha$ luminosity and SFR to be $(7.5\pm1.3) \times
10^-42$ for a Salpeter IMF, which is consistent with the Kennicutt (1998)
conversion. The derived conversion factor is independent of any assumption of
the dust correction and is robust to stellar population model uncertainties.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_2</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2ace72ec838bf9cc8751648df650e5c1c/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Towards universal hybrid star formation rate estimators</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>M.</first><last>Boquien</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>R.</first><last>Kennicutt</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>D.</first><last>Calzetti</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>D.</first><last>Dale</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>M.</first><last>Galametz</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>M.</first><last>Sauvage</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>K.</first><last>Croxall</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>B.</first><last>Draine</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>A.</first><last>Kirkpatrick</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>N.</first><last>Kumari</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>L.</first><last>Hunt</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>I.</first><last>De Looze</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>E.</first><last>Pellegrini</last></author><author><nr>14</nr><first>M.</first><last>Relano</last></author><author><nr>15</nr><first>J. D.</first><last>Smith</last></author><author><nr>16</nr><first>F.</first><last>Tabatabaei</last></author></authors><keys><key>uv</key><key>ir</key><key>estimator</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>sfr</key></keys><date>2016-04-01 09:44:28</date><changeDate>2016-04-01 09:44:28</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2016</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1603.09340</url><note>cite arxiv:1603.09340Comment: 25 pages, 12 figures, 8 tables. Accepted for publication in A&amp;A</note><abstract>To compute the SFR of galaxies from the rest-frame UV it is essential to take
into account the obscuration by dust. To do so, one of the most popular methods
consists in combining the UV with the emission from the dust itself in the IR.
Yet, different studies have derived different estimators, showing that no such
hybrid estimator is truly universal. In this paper we aim at understanding and
quantifying what physical processes drive the variations between different
hybrid estimators. Doing so, we aim at deriving new universal UV+IR hybrid
estimators to correct the UV for dust attenuation, taking into account the
intrinsic physical properties of galaxies. We use the CIGALE code to model the
spatially-resolved FUV to FIR SED of eight nearby star-forming galaxies drawn
from the KINGFISH sample. This allows us to determine their local physical
properties, and in particular their UV attenuation, average SFR, average
specific SFR (sSFR), and their stellar mass. We then examine how hybrid
estimators depend on said properties. We find that hybrid UV+IR estimators
strongly depend on the stellar mass surface density (in particular at 70 and
100 micron) and on the sSFR (in particular at 24 micron and the TIR).
Consequently, the IR scaling coefficients for UV obscuration can vary by almost
an order of magnitude. This result contrasts with other groups who found
relatively constant coefficients with small deviations. We exploit these
variations to construct a new class of hybrid estimators based on observed UV
to near-IR colours and near-IR luminosity densities per unit area. We find that
they can reliably be extended to entire galaxies. The new estimators provide
better estimates of attenuation-corrected UV emission than classical hybrid
estimators. Naturally taking into account the variable impact of dust heated by
old stellar populations, they constitute a step towards universal estimators.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_3</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2c26c16e0a8036000b788fada656f59dd/mgrani</bibsomy_id><title>Application of Spreading Activation Techniques in Information Retrieval</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>F.</first><last>Crestani</last></author></authors><keys><key>semantic</key><key>merged:hotho</key><key>msn</key><key>ir</key><key>spreading</key><key>***</key><key>network</key><key>retrieval</key><key>merged:mgrani</key><key>survey</key><key>search</key><key>information</key><key>activation</key></keys><date>2008-05-27 08:15:25</date><changeDate>2008-05-27 08:15:52</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1997</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1023/A:1006569829653</url><abstract>This paper surveys the use of Spreading Activation techniques onSemantic Networks in Associative Information Retrieval. The majorSpreading Activation models are presented and their applications toIR is surveyed. A number of works in this area are criticallyanalyzed in order to study the relevance of Spreading Activation forassociative IR.
ER  -</abstract><journal>Artificial Intelligence Review</journal><volume>11</volume><number>6</number><pages>453--482</pages></publication><publication><id>han_4</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/26a1f84786266b91ef694f2f3c0510578/pprett</bibsomy_id><title>Applying connectionist models to information retrieval</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>S.</first><last>Cunningham</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>G.</first><last>Holmes</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>J.</first><last>Littin</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>R.</first><last>Beale</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>I.</first><last>Witten</last></author></authors><keys><key>connectionist,</key><key>merged:pprett</key><key>ir</key></keys><date>2008-06-17 16:01:02</date><changeDate>2008-06-17 16:01:04</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>1997</year><url>http://citeseer.ist.psu.edu/357098.html</url><abstract>: Adaptive information retrieval (IR) systems based on connectionist

architectures have captured the attention of researchers over the past decade. This

paper provides a review of connectionist IR research, including the major models

for connectionist document and query representation, techniques to enhance query

re-formulation, dynamic document routing (information filtering), and

connectionist techniques for document clustering.

1. Introduction

Information retrieval (IR) systems...</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_5</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/20599158ce6abbe681519d8d45c436472/ijtsrd</bibsomy_id><title>Four IR Sensor Based Automatic Control of Railway Gate using Microcontroller</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Hay Man Oo | Ni Ni San Hlaing | Thin Thin</first><last>Oo</last></author></authors><keys><key>motor</key><key>merged:ijtsrd</key><key>&amp;</key><key>IR</key><key>Electronics</key><key>LED</key><key>Engineering</key><key>Arduino</key><key>UNO</key><key>Buzzer</key><key>Servo</key><key>sensor</key><key>Communication</key></keys><date>2019-09-12 08:25:47</date><changeDate>2019-09-12 08:25:47</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2019</year><url>https://www.ijtsrd.com/engineering/electronics-and-communication-engineering/26634/four-ir-sensor-based-automatic-control-of-railway-gate-using-microcontroller/hay-man-oo</url><abstract>This paper investigates based on four IR sensor automatic control of railway gate using a microcontroller system. There are so many railway accidents happening due to the carelessness in manual operations or lack of worker. So  this paper describes four IR sensor based automatic control of railway gate system for saving precious human lives and preventing major disasters in railway track. Railway gate may be saved for the road users to prevent accidents in terms of train speed at a level crossing. Automatic railway gate control system is an innovative circuit which automatically controls the operation of railway gates detecting the arrival and departure of train at the gate. This automatic system can be replaced by the gates operated by the gatekeeper. The operation using Arduino UNO that integrated with other circuits involved such as power supply  IR sensors  light indicators  buzzer  and gate motors. The servo motor is used to control the open and close status of the railway crossing gate. The four IR sensors are placed on the railway tracks. The gate is closed when the first one senses the train and is opened when the second one senses the train. This operation is performed when the train is coming from the left side of the gate. When the train is coming from the right side  the third and fourth sensors is performed in the same operation. The red LED is HIGH when the gate is closed and the green LED is HIGH when the gate is opened. This system is based on software programming to operate the hardware structure. Program for four IR sensor based automatic control of railway gate system is based on Arduino UNO with C language. The main function of the design is Arduino UNO. Hay Man Oo | Ni Ni San Hlaing | Thin Thin Oo "Four IR Sensor Based Automatic Control of Railway Gate using Microcontroller" Published in International Journal of Trend in Scientific Research and Development (ijtsrd)  ISSN: 2456-6470  Volume-3 | Issue-5   August 2019  URL: https://www.ijtsrd.com/papers/ijtsrd26634.pdfPaper URL: https://www.ijtsrd.com/engineering/electronics-and-communication-engineering/26634/four-ir-sensor-based-automatic-control-of-railway-gate-using-microcontroller/hay-man-oo</abstract><journal>International Journal of Trend in Scientific Research and Development</journal><volume>3</volume><number>5</number><pages>1109-1113</pages><language>English</language><issn>2456-6470</issn><doi>https://doi.org/10.31142/ijtsrd26634</doi></publication><publication><id>han_6</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2ac6a6ce1f96751efa8e82a1e58f9bd7b/jrennstich</bibsomy_id><title>State and Society in International Relations: A Second Agenda</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Fred</first><last>Halliday</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:jrennstich</key><key>ir</key><key>state</key><key>neomarxism</key><key>theory</key></keys><date>2010-03-02 17:25:53</date><changeDate>2010-03-02 17:28:00</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1987</year><url /><abstract>Discusses conceptual and definitional issues surrounding the role of the state in IR.</abstract><journal>Millennium</journal><volume>16</volume><number>2</number><pages>215--229</pages></publication><publication><id>han_7</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/28a50c41811c394bdfd69716bee54a746/beate</bibsomy_id><title>Comparative analysis of clicks and judgments for IR evaluation</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Jaap</first><last>Kamps</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Marijn</first><last>Koolen</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Andrew</first><last>Trotman</last></author></authors><keys><key>comparison</key><key>study</key><key>implicit-feedback</key><key>social-search</key><key>evaluation</key><key>clickdata</key><key>clicks</key><key>learning-to-rank</key><key>merged:dblp</key><key>clickthrough</key><key>merged:beate</key><key>dblp</key></keys><date>2011-07-21 17:11:07</date><changeDate>2011-07-21 17:11:07</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2009</year><url>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/1507509.1507522</url><abstract>Queries and click-through data taken from search engine transaction logs is an attractive alternative to traditional test collections, due to its volume and the direct relation to end-user querying. The overall aim of this paper is to answer the question: How does click-through data differ from explicit human relevance judgments in information retrieval evaluation? We compare a traditional test collection with manual judgments to transaction log based test collections---by using queries as topics and subsequent clicks as pseudo-relevance judgments for the clicked results.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Specifically, we investigate the following two research questions: Firstly, are there significant differences between clicks and relevance judgments. Earlier research suggests that although clicks and explicit judgments show reasonable agreement, clicks are different from static absolute relevance judgments. Secondly, are there significant differences between system ranking based on clicks and based on relevance judgments? This is an open question, but earlier research suggests that comparative evaluation in terms of system ranking is remarkably robust.</abstract><pages>80--87</pages><doi>10.1145/1507509.1507522</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the 2009 workshop on Web Search Click Data</booktitle><series>WSCD '09</series><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>978-1-60558-434-8</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_8</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2434b2d6121ed998e203065945481096b/griesbau</bibsomy_id><title>Discounted Cumulated Gain Based Evaluation of Multiple-Query IR Sessions</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kalervo</first><last>Järvelin</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Susan</first><last>Price</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Lois</first><last>Delcambre</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Marianne</first><last>Nielsen</last></author></authors><keys><key>study</key><key>engine</key><key>evaluation</key><key>engines</key><key>interactive</key><key>merged:griesbau</key><key>user</key><key>search</key></keys><date>2010-03-23 11:42:36</date><changeDate>2010-03-23 11:42:36</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2008</year><url>http://www.info.uta.fi/tutkimus/fire/archive/2008/SessionDCG-ECIR-08.pdf</url><abstract>IR research has a strong tradition of laboratory evaluation of systems. Such research is based on test collections, pre-defined
test topics, and standard evaluation metrics. While recent research has emphasized the user viewpoint by proposing user-basedmetrics and non-binary relevance assessments, the methods are insufficient for truly user-based evaluation. The common assumptionof a single query per topic and session poorly represents real life. On the other hand, one well-known metric for multiplequeries per session, instance recall, does not capture early (within session) retrieval of (highly) relevant documents. Wepropose an extension to the Discounted Cumulated Gain (DCG) metric, the Session-based DCG (sDCG) metric for evaluation scenariosinvolving multiple query sessions, graded relevance assessments, and open-ended user effort including decisions to stop searching.The sDCG metric discounts relevant results from later queries within a session. We exemplify the sDCG metric with data froman interactive experiment, we discuss how the metric might be applied, and we present research questions for which the metricis helpful.</abstract><journal>Advances in Information Retrieval</journal><pages>4--15</pages></publication><publication><id>han_9</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2f66dfd0d4ef404f40b3c6d5200328c7c/conchuir</bibsomy_id><title>Semplore: An IR Approach to Scalable Hybrid Query of Semantic Web Data</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Lei</first><last>Zhang</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Qiaoling</first><last>Liu</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Jie</first><last>Zhang</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Haofen</first><last>Wang</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Yue</first><last>Pan</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Yong</first><last>Yu</last></author></authors><keys><key>aswc07,</key><key>iswc07</key><key>merged:conchuir</key></keys><date>2009-02-13 13:22:04</date><changeDate>2009-02-13 13:22:05</changeDate><pub-type>incollection</pub-type><year>2008</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1007/978-3-540-76298-0\_47</url><abstract>As an extension to the current Web, Semantic Web will not only contain structured data with machine understandable semantics but also textual information. While structured queries can be used to find information more precisely on the Semantic Web, keyword searches are still needed to help exploit textual information. It thus becomes very important that we can combine precise structured queries with imprecise keyword searches to have a hybrid query capability. In addition, due to the huge volume of information on the Semantic Web, the hybrid query must be processed in a very scalable way. In this paper, we define such a hybrid query capability that combines unary tree-shaped structured queries with keyword searches. We show how existing information retrieval (IR) index structures and functions can be reused to index semantic web data and its textual information, and how the hybrid query is evaluated on the index structure using IR engines in an efficient and scalable manner. We implemented this IR approach in an engine called Semplore. Comprehensive experiments on its performance show that it is a promising approach. It leads us to believe that it may be possible to evolve current web search engines to query and search the Semantic Web. Finally, we breifly describe how Semplore is used for searching Wikipedia and an IBM customer’s product information.</abstract><journal>The Semantic Web</journal><pages>652--665</pages><doi>http://dx.doi.org/10.1007/978-3-540-76298-0\_47</doi></publication><publication><id>han_10</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2d0c2d8adee5d7269a6c9e1f0d2da31c0/riche.ma</bibsomy_id><title>Constitution and hardnesses of the Al-Ir system</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>P. J.</first><last>Hill</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>L. A.</first><last>Cornish</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>M. J.</first><last>Witcomb</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:riche.ma</key><key>Al_Ir_phase_diagram</key></keys><date>2011-01-27 11:10:48</date><changeDate>2011-01-27 11:10:48</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1998</year><url>http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/B6TWY-3V8S31X-2K/2/cd905af2b224bda13e30c376c4d79f84</url><abstract>The Al-Ir phase diagram was investigated using optical and scanning electron microscopy, and X-ray diffraction. The results were found to agree with published literature, with the exception of the congruent melting of Al2.7Ir and a previously unreported eutectic reaction to form Al2.7Ir and AlIr. The AlIr and Al2.7Ir phases had the widest composition ranges: 47-53 and 23-30 at.% Ir respectively.
Mechanical tests, in the form of Vickers hardness tests were used to deduce the fracture toughness of the alloys. It was found that the high Al-content intermetallic compounds were very brittle, and the alloys containing AlIr were tougher. This compound was tougher on the Ir-rich side, especially when there was a small amount of the AlIr+(Ir) eutectic between the AlIr dendrites.</abstract><journal>Journal of Alloys and Compounds</journal><volume>280</volume><number>1-2</number><pages>240 - 250</pages><issn>0925-8388</issn><doi>10.1016/S0925-8388(98)00748-8</doi></publication><publication><id>han_11</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2e7e4b1601267f459faa9b292174f0a90/bibgreen</bibsomy_id><title>An agenda for green information retrieval research</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Gobinda</first><last>Chowdhury</last></author></authors><keys><key>greenbib</key><key>merged:bibgreen</key></keys><date>2020-02-18 19:48:11</date><changeDate>2020-03-04 09:03:06</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2012</year><url /><note>Green IR; Green IR research agenda.; Green IT and cloud computing; Information retrieval for sustainable development; Sustainable development</note><abstract>Nowadays we use information retrieval systems and services as part of our many day-to-day activities ranging from a web and database search to searching for various digital libraries, audio and video collections/services, and so on. However, IR systems and services make extensive use of ICT (information and communication technologies) and increasing use of ICT can significantly increase greenhouse gas (GHG, a term used to denote emission of harmful gases in the atmosphere) emissions. Sustainable development, and more importantly environmental sustainability, has become a major area of concern of various national and international bodies and as a result various initiatives and measures are being proposed for reducing the environmental impact of industries, businesses, governments and institutions. Research also shows that appropriate use of ICT can reduce the overall GHG emissions of a business, product or service. Green IT and cloud computing can play a key role in reducing the environmental impact of ICT. This paper proposes the concept of Green IR systems and services that can play a key role in reducing the overall environmental impact of various ICT-based services in education and research, business, government, etc., that are increasingly being reliant on access and use of digital information. However, to date there has not been any systematic research towards building Green IR systems and services. This paper points out the major challenges in building Green IR systems and services, and two different methods are proposed for estimating the energy consumption, and the corresponding GHG emissions, of an IR system or service. This paper also proposes the four key enablers of a Green IR viz. Standardize, Share, Reuse and Green behavior. Further research required to achieve these for building Green IR systems and services are also mentioned.</abstract><journal>Information Processing &amp; Management</journal><volume>48</volume><number>6</number><pages>1067-1077</pages><language>en</language><issn>03064573</issn><doi>10.1016/j.ipm.2012.02.003</doi></publication><publication><id>han_12</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2abb49bfc87d0ef0e5c9023161384ea15/ewomant</bibsomy_id><title>Modeling task-genre relationships for IR in the workplace</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Luanne</first><last>Freund</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Elaine G.</first><last>Toms</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Charles L.A.</first><last>Clarke</last></author></authors><keys><key>vertical_search</key><key>merged:ewomant</key></keys><date>2008-07-01 12:50:23</date><changeDate>2008-07-01 12:50:23</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2005</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=1076034.1076110</url><abstract>Context influences the search process, but to date research has not definitively identified which aspects of context are the most influential for information retrieval, and thus are worthy of integration in today's retrieval systems. In this research, we isolated for examination two aspects of context: task and document genre and examined the relationship between them within a software engineering work domain. In this domain, the nature of the task has an impact on decisions of relevance and usefulness, and the document collection contains a distinctive set of genre. Our data set was a document repository created and used by our target population. The document surrogates were meta-tagged by purpose and document type. Correspondence analysis of this categorical data identified some specific relationships between genres and tasks, as well as four broad dimensions of variability underlying these relationships. These results have the potential to inform the design of a contextual retrieval system by refining search results for this domain.</abstract><pages>441--448</pages><doi>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/1076034.1076110</doi><booktitle>SIGIR '05: Proceedings of the 28th annual international ACM SIGIR conference on Research and development in information retrieval</booktitle><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>1-59593-034-5</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_13</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/255cf6af78570f152e39f3df715e5f9db/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Driving gas shells with radiation pressure on dust in
  radiation-hydrodynamic simulations</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Tiago</first><last>Costa</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Joakim</first><last>Rosdahl</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Debora</first><last>Sijacki</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Martin</first><last>Haehnelt</last></author></authors><keys><key>radiation</key><key>AGN</key><key>IR</key><key>pressure</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>dust</key></keys><date>2017-03-20 11:33:41</date><changeDate>2017-03-20 11:33:51</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1703.05766</url><note>cite arxiv:1703.05766Comment: 23 pages, 11 figures, 3 tables, submitted to MNRAS</note><abstract>We present radiation-hydrodynamic simulations of radiatively-driven gas
shells launched by bright active galactic nuclei (AGN) in isolated dark matter
haloes. Our goals are (1) to investigate the ability of AGN radiation pressure
on dust to launch galactic outflows and (2) to constrain the efficiency of
infrared (IR) multi-scattering in boosting outflow acceleration. Our
simulations are performed with the radiation-hydrodynamic code RAMSES-RT and
include both single- and multi-scattered radiation pressure from an AGN,
radiative cooling and self-gravity. Since outflowing shells always eventually
become transparent to the incident radiation field, outflows that sweep up all
intervening gas are likely to remain gravitationally bound to their halo even
at high AGN luminosities. The expansion of outflowing shells is well described
by simple analytic models as long as the shells are mildly optically thick to
IR radiation. In this case, an enhancement in the acceleration of shells
through IR multi-scattering occurs as predicted, i.e. a force dP/dt = tau_IR
L/c is exerted on the gas. For high optical depths tau_IR &gt; 50, however,
momentum transfer between outflowing optically thick gas and IR radiation is
rapidly suppressed, even if the radiation is efficiently confined. At high
tau_IR, the characteristic flow time becomes shorter than the required trapping
time of IR radiation such that the momentum flux dP/dt &lt;&lt; tau_IR L/c. We argue
that while unlikely to unbind massive galactic gaseous haloes, AGN radiation
pressure on dust could play an important role in regulating star formation and
black hole accretion in the nuclei of massive compact galaxies at high
redshift.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_14</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/22e042b83a39dafbc518001bcc5cac3cf/riche.ma</bibsomy_id><title>A combined first-principles/CALPHAD modeling of the Al-Ir system</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Chao</first><last>Jiang</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Brian</first><last>Gleeson</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:riche.ma</key><key>Al_Ir_phase_diagram</key></keys><date>2011-01-26 10:44:05</date><changeDate>2011-01-26 10:44:05</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2006</year><url>http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/B6TW8-4KF1HY5-6/2/1e99926b4c874938705f95ec9744a34b</url><abstract>A combined first-principles/CALPHAD approach was employed to model the thermodynamics of the Al-Ir system. Among the six intermetallic compounds in this system, the formation enthalpies of Al9Ir2, Al3Ir and AlIr were obtained from T = 0 K first-principles total energy calculations. The formation enthalpies of Al45Ir13, Al13Ir4 and Al2.7Ir, whose structures are either unknown or too complicated for first-principles calculations, were estimated using a greedy algorithm developed in this study. The mixing enthalpies of Al1-xIrx face-centered cubic (fcc) alloys were calculated at x = 0.25, 0.5 and 0.75 using the special quasirandom structure approach. The vibrational formation entropy of AlIr was also calculated using the supercell method within the harmonic and quasi-harmonic approximation, respectively. We demonstrated that, with the incorporation of first-principles energetics, a physically meaningful thermodynamic description of the Al-Ir system can be obtained even with very scarce experimental data. The predicted B2 and fcc two-phase equilibrium in the Al-Ir-Ni ternary system was also in reasonable agreement with experiments.</abstract><journal>Acta Materialia</journal><volume>54</volume><number>15</number><pages>4101 - 4110</pages><issn>1359-6454</issn><doi>10.1016/j.actamat.2006.03.058</doi></publication><publication><id>han_15</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/28b0db6e8cb4c50eb1e7ba59b90635011/gesis_dump</bibsomy_id><title>Profiling European physicians' usage of eHealth services</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Jose Manuel</first><last>Ortega Egea</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Maria Victoria</first><last>Román González</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Manuel</first><last>Recio Menéndez</last></author></authors><keys><key>review_proved</key><key>merged:gesis_dump</key><key>input2016</key><key>english</key><key>2011</key><key>indexproved</key><key>Eurobarometer</key><key>EB_input2016</key><key>article</key><key>SCOPUSindexed</key><key>fdz_jb</key><key>checked</key><key>reviewed</key><key>FDZ_IUP</key></keys><date>2019-03-20 18:49:19</date><changeDate>2019-10-01 13:00:44</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2011</year><url>http://InformationR.net/ir/16-1/paper467.html</url><note>http://InformationR.net/ir/16-1/paper467.html. (Eurobarometer)</note><abstract>Introduction. Deeper knowledge of physicians' eHealth-related behaviour is needed in different countries. This paper clarifies the usage patterns of eHealth services among European general practitioners.
Method. The survey database Flash-Eurobarometer No. 126 'General Practitioners and the Internet' is analysed. Additional socio-demographic variables are also included, such as country, age, sex, location, and size of the medical practice. Telephone interviews were conducted for data collection purposes.
Analysis. Latent class cluster analysis was applied to identify homogeneous segments of eHealth adopters among European physicians. Country, age, sex, location, and size of the medical practice were included as covariates in the analyses, in order to obtain a descriptive profiling of the identified segments.
Results. The analysis yielded three segments of European physicians using eHealth services. After adding the group of physicians not using the Internet, the following four final segments were identified: Information Searchers, Advanced Users, Laggards and Non-Internet Users. The analysis of covariates in the latent class cluster model showed that country, sex and age were significantly related to physicians' usage patterns of eHealth services. Chi squared analyses were performed to account for the group of Non-Internet Users, further confirming the existence of strong country differences and moderate age influences, but very weak effects of sex on physicians' eHealth-related behaviour.
Conclusion. The identification of European physicians' eHealth usage patterns contributes to the development of suitable and adapted promotion strategies, aimed at ensuring efficient adoption processes of Internet technologies among providers of patient care services in the analysed countries.</abstract><journal>Information Research</journal><volume>16(1)</volume><number>467</number></publication><publication><id>han_16</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/27d2714c8697952b7f35794bf775bc5c3/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Quasar Probabilities and Redshifts from WISE mid-IR through GALEX UV
  Photometry</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>M. A.</first><last>DiPompeo</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>J.</first><last>Bovy</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>A. D.</first><last>Myers</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>D.</first><last>Lang</last></author></authors><keys><key>selection</key><key>wise</key><key>quasar</key><key>redshifts</key><key>probabilities</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2015-07-13 10:04:00</date><changeDate>2015-07-13 10:04:00</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2015</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1507.02884</url><note>cite arxiv:1507.02884Comment: 11 pages, 18 figures, accepted for publication in MNRAS. Quasar  catalog available here:  http://www.mpia.de/homes/joe/xdqsozcat_galex_ukidss_wise_p20.fits.gz and code  is available here: https://github.com/xdqso/xdqso</note><abstract>Extreme deconvolution (XD) of broad-band photometric data can both separate
stars from quasars and generate probability density functions for quasar
redshifts, while incorporating flux uncertainties and missing data.
Mid-infrared photometric colors are now widely used to identify hot dust
intrinsic to quasars, and the release of all-sky WISE data has led to a
dramatic increase in the number of IR-selected quasars. Using forced-photometry
on public WISE data at the locations of SDSS point sources, we incorporate this
all-sky data into the training of the XDQSOz models originally developed to
select quasars from optical photometry. The combination of WISE and SDSS
information is far more powerful than SDSS alone, particularly at $z&gt;2$. The
use of SDSS$+$WISE photometry is comparable to the use of
SDSS$+$ultraviolet$+$near-IR data. We release a new public catalogue of
5,537,436 (total; 3,874,639 weighted by probability) potential quasars with
probability $P_QSO &gt; 0.2$. The catalogue includes redshift
probabilities for all objects. We also release an updated version of the
publicly available set of codes to calculate quasar and redshift probabilities
for various combinations of data. Finally, we demonstrate that this method of
selecting quasars using WISE data is both more complete and efficient than
simple WISE color-cuts, especially at high redshift. Our fits verify that above
$z 3$ WISE colors become bluer than the standard cuts applied to select
quasars. Currently, the analysis is limited to quasars with optical
counterparts, and thus cannot be used to find highly obscured quasars that WISE
color-cuts identify in significant numbers.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_17</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2342afb1b446f051676563696adb288cd/hlwoodcock</bibsomy_id><title>Density functional theory study on molecular structure and vibrational IR spectra of isocytosine</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>J. S.</first><last>Kwiatkowski</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>J.</first><last>Leszczynski</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:hlwoodcock</key><key>bibtex-import</key></keys><date>2006-06-16 05:03:46</date><changeDate>2006-06-16 05:03:46</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1997</year><url /><abstract>Density functional theory with the combined Becke3-LYP exchange-correlation energy functional DET(B3-LYP) method using the 6-31G(d, p) basis set is applied to predict molecular parameters (geometries, rotational constants, dipole moments) and vibrational IR spectra (harmonic wavenumbers, absolute intensities) of six tautomers of the isocytosine molecule. The results are compared with the corresponding data calculated at the conventional ab initio Hartree-Fock (HF) level using the same basis set and with available experimental data. Calculations show that (a) three amino tautomers are slightly nonplanar species with, evidently, a distorted amino group, (b) the DFT (B3-LYP)/G-31G(d, p) method predicts better molecular parameters, than do the HF calculations, and (c) the DFT(B3-LYP)-calculated vibrational IR spectra of isocytosine agree well with the available recorded IR spectra, and they show marked improvement over the IR spectra predicted at the HF/6-31G(d, p) level. Tautomeric stabilities of isocytosine are discussed on the basis of computed electronic energies by the DFT(B3-LYP) and ab initio approaches including the MP2 and MP4(SDQ) calculations of electronic energies and predicted zero-point vibrational energies by DFT(B3-LYP) and HF methods. This relative energies at 0 K of the tautomeric forms of isocytosine predicted by both conventional ab initio and DET(B3-LYP) methods correlate well with the experimental data, showing the predominance of the aminohydroxy tautomer of isocytosine for an isolated molecule. (C) 1997 John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc.</abstract><journal>INTERNATIONAL JOURNAL OF QUANTUM CHEMISTRY</journal><volume>61</volume><number>3</number><pages>453--465</pages></publication><publication><id>han_18</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/223db3db82768d2509c819089ea959924/lepsky</bibsomy_id><title>The twist measure for IR evaluation : taking user's effort into account</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Nicola</first><last>Ferro</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Gianmaria</first><last>Silvello</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Heikki</first><last>Keskustalo</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Ari</first><last>Pirkola</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Kalervo</first><last>Järvelin</last></author></authors><keys><key>retrievaltests</key><key>merged:lepsky</key></keys><date>2018-11-04 17:00:37</date><changeDate>2018-11-04 17:00:37</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2016</year><url /><abstract>We present a novel measure for ranking evaluation, called Twist (τ). It is a measure for informational intents, which handles both binary and graded relevance. τ stems from the observation that searching is currently a that searching is currently taken for granted and it is natural for users to assume that search engines are available and work well. As a consequence, users may assume the utility they have in finding relevant documents, which is the focus of traditional measures, as granted. On the contrary, they may feel uneasy when the system returns nonrelevant documents because they are then forced to do additional work to get the desired information, and this causes avoidable effort. The latter is the focus of τ, which evaluates the effectiveness of a system from the point of view of the effort required to the users to retrieve the desired information. We provide a formal definition of τ, a demonstration of its properties, and introduce the notion of effort/gain plots, which complement traditional utility-based measures. By means of an extensive experimental evaluation, τ is shown to grasp different aspects of system performances, to not require extensive and costly assessments, and to be a robust tool for detecting differences between systems.</abstract><journal>Journal of the Association for Information Science &amp; Technology</journal><volume>67</volume><number>3</number><pages>620--648</pages><issn>23301635</issn><doi>10.1002/asi.23416</doi><shorttitle>The twist measure for IR evaluation</shorttitle></publication><publication><id>han_19</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/268d7f8ce41a0d921c7f63240e72a3fa6/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Quenching star formation with quasar outflows launched by trapped IR
  radiation</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Tiago</first><last>Costa</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Joakim</first><last>Rosdahl</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Debora</first><last>Sijacki</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Martin G.</first><last>Haehnelt</last></author></authors><keys><key>quasar</key><key>radiation</key><key>outflow</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2017-09-27 10:11:37</date><changeDate>2017-09-27 10:11:37</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1709.08638</url><note>cite arxiv:1709.08638Comment: 33 pages (26 main paper + 7 pages of references and appendices).  Submitted to MNRAS</note><abstract>We present cosmological radiation-hydrodynamic simulations, performed with
the code Ramses-RT, of radiatively-driven outflows in a massive quasar host
halo at z = 6. Our simulations include both single- and multi-scattered
radiation pressure on dust from a quasar and are compared against simulations
performed with thermal feedback. For radiation pressure-driving, we show that
there is a critical quasar luminosity above which a galactic outflow is
launched, set by the equilibrium of gravitational and radiation forces. While
this critical luminosity is unrealistically high in the single-scattering limit
for plausible black hole masses, it is in line with a 3 x 10^9 M_SUN black hole
accreting at its Eddington limit, if infrared (IR) multi-scattering radiation
pressure is included. The outflows are fast (v &gt; 1000 km/s) and strongly
mass-loaded with peak mass outflow rates 10^3 - 10^4 M_SUN/yr, but short-lived
(&lt; 10 Myr). Outflowing material is multi-phase, though predominantly composed
of cool gas, forming via a thermal instability in the shocked swept-up
component. Radiation pressure- and thermally-driven outflows both affect their
host galaxies profoundly, but in different, complementary ways.
Thermally-driven outflows couple more efficiently to diffuse halo gas,
generating more powerful, hotter and more volume-filling outflows. IR
radiation, through its ability to penetrate dense gas via diffusion, is more
efficient at ejecting gas from the bulge. The combination of gas ejection
through outflows with internal pressurisation by trapped IR radiation leads to
a complete shut down of star formation in the bulge. We hence argue that
radiation pressure-driven feedback may be a crucial ingredient in regulating
star formation in compact starbursts, especially during the quasar's
öbscured"' phase.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_20</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/26bcd2c25b85fe73c3eac116884a06928/jrennstich</bibsomy_id><title>You Just Don'T Understand: Troubled Engagements between Feminists and IR Theorists</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Ann J.</first><last>Tickner</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:jrennstich</key><key>feminism</key><key>ir</key><key>text</key><key>teaching</key><key>theory</key></keys><date>2010-03-02 17:25:53</date><changeDate>2010-03-02 17:26:53</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2002</year><url /><abstract>This article reconstructs some conversational encounters between feminists and IR theorists and offers some hypotheses as to why misunderstandings so frequently result from these encounters. It claims that contemporary feminist perspectives on international relations are based on ontologies and epistemologies that are quite different from those that inform the conventional discipline. Therefore, they do not fit comfortably within conventional state-centric and structural approaches to IR theorizing, nor with the methodologies usually employed by IR scholars. As an illustration of how these differences can cause misunderstandings, the article offers some feminist perspectives on security, a concept central to the discipline. It also suggests how feminist approaches can offer some new ways to understand contemporary security problems. In conclusion, it suggests how feminist/IR engagements might be pursued more constructively.</abstract><journal>International Studies Quarterly</journal><volume>41</volume><number>4</number><pages>611--632</pages></publication><publication><id>han_21</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2de349fb151da9f8f67ca52aebea84192/griesbau</bibsomy_id><title>The concept of relevance in IR</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Pia</first><last>Borlund</last></author></authors><keys><key>retrievaltests</key><key>merged:lepsky</key><key>concept</key><key>IR</key><key>merged:dblp</key><key>merged:griesbau</key><key>relevance</key><key>dblp</key><key>information-retrieval</key><key>merged:brusilovsky</key><key>informationretrieval</key><key>merged:aho</key><key>merged:zalan.kramer</key><key>SS</key></keys><date>2011-12-20 20:04:47</date><changeDate>2011-12-20 20:04:47</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2003</year><url>http://comminfo.rutgers.edu/~muresan/IR/Docs/Articles/jasistBorlund2003.pdf</url><abstract>This article introduces the concept of relevance as viewed and applied in the context of IR evaluation, by presenting an overview of the multidimensional and dynamic nature of the concept. The literature on relevance reveals how the relevance concept, especially in regard to the 
multidimensionality of relevance, is many faceted, and does not just refer to the various relevance criteria users may apply in the process of judging relevance of retrieved information objects. From our point of view, the multidimensionality of relevance explains why some will argue that no 
consensus has been reached on the relevance concept. Thus, the objective of this article is to present an overview of the many different views and ways by which the concept of relevance is used—leading to a consistent and compatible understanding of the concept. In addition, special attention 
is paid to the type of situational relevance. Many researchers perceive situational relevance as the most realistic type of user relevance, and therefore situational relevance is discussed with reference to its potential dynamic nature, and as a requirement for interactive information retrieval 
(IIR) evaluation.</abstract><journal>Journal of the American Society for Information Science and Technology</journal><volume>54</volume><number>10</number><pages>913--925</pages><issn>1532-2890</issn><doi>10.1002/asi.10286</doi><publisher>Wiley Subscription Services, Inc., A Wiley Company</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_22</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/256ab2f4e11d927fd8ec6ad5719b79d3f/thesaiorg</bibsomy_id><title>Sensitivity Analysis for Water Vapor Profile Estimation with Infrared: IR Sounder Data Based on Inversion</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kohei</first><last>Arai</last></author></authors><keys><key>error</key><key>merged:thesaiorg</key><key>humidity.</key><key>IR</key><key>analysis;</key><key>air</key><key>relative</key><key>MODTRAN;</key><key>temperature;</key><key>budget</key><key>sounde;</key></keys><date>2014-02-21 08:00:08</date><changeDate>2014-02-21 08:00:08</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2012</year><url>http://ijacsa.thesai.org/</url><abstract>Sensitivity analysis for water vapor profile estimation with Infrared: IR sounder data based on inversion is carried out. Through simulation study, it is found that influence due to ground surface relative humidity estimation error is greater than that of sea surface temperature estimation error on the water vapor vertical profile retrievals.</abstract><journal>International Journal of Advanced Computer Science and Applications(IJACSA)</journal><volume>3</volume><number>11</number></publication><publication><id>han_23</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2cd75861afe9e2f29ebc40165473d8b38/brazovayeye</bibsomy_id><title>Implementing GP on Optimizing both Boolean and
                 Extended Boolean Queries in IR and Fuzzy IR systems
                 with Respect to the Users Profiles</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Suhail</first><last>Owais</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Pavel</first><last>Kromer</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Vaclav</first><last>Snasel</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Dusan</first><last>Husek</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Roman</first><last>Neruda</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:brazovayeye</key><key>genetic</key><key>algorithms,</key><key>programming,</key><key>poster</key></keys><date>2008-06-19 17:35:00</date><changeDate>2008-06-19 17:49:10</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2006</year><url /><abstract>Rapidly growing amount of the data available on World
                 Wide Web (WWW) as the ultimate collection of public
                 accessible text documents complicates the task of
                 acquiring usable and relevant information from raw
                 data. Several methods of improvement and optimisation
                 of Information Retrieval (IR) systems providing user
                 interaction with WWW documents have been introduced and
                 discussed. In this paper, theory and application of
                 Genetic Programming (GP) as an optimization method of
                 modern user oriented IR and fuzzy IR (FIR) systems
                 optimisation of search queries is presented.</abstract><pages>5648--5654</pages><booktitle>Proceedings of the 2006 IEEE Congress on Evolutionary
                 Computation</booktitle><publisher>IEEE Press</publisher><isbn>0-7803-9487-9</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_24</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/238e6bf4c763f1a6d5f84f442f7bd9c06/sasha-markov</bibsomy_id><title>Adaptive vibrational configuration interaction (A-VCI): A posteriori error estimation to efficiently compute anharmonic IR spectra</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Romain</first><last>Garnier</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Marc</first><last>Odunlami</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Vincent</first><last>Le Bris</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Didier</first><last>Bégué</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Isabelle</first><last>Baraille</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Olivier</first><last>Coulaud</last></author></authors><keys><key>spectroscopy</key><key>configuration-interaction</key><key>merged:sasha-markov</key></keys><date>2016-06-06 11:10:46</date><changeDate>2016-06-06 11:10:46</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2016</year><url>http://scitation.aip.org/content/aip/journal/jcp/144/20/10.1063/1.4952414</url><abstract>A new variational algorithm called adaptive vibrational configuration interaction (A-VCI) intended for the resolution of the vibrational Schrödinger equation was developed. The main advantage of this approach is to efficiently reduce the dimension of the active space generated into the configuration interaction (CI) process. Here, we assume that the Hamiltonian writes as a sum of products of operators. This adaptive algorithm was developed with the use of three correlated conditions, i.e., a suitable starting space, a criterion for convergence, and a procedure to expand the approximate space. The velocity of the algorithm was increased with the use of a posteriori error estimator (residue) to select the most relevant direction to increase the space. Two examples have been selected for benchmark. In the case of H2CO, we mainly study the performance of A-VCI algorithm: comparison with the variation-perturbation method, choice of the initial space, and residual contributions. For CH3CN, we compare the A-VCI results with a computed reference spectrum using the same potential energy surface and for an active space reduced by about 90%.</abstract><journal>The Journal of Chemical Physics</journal><volume>144</volume><number>20</number><doi>http://dx.doi.org/10.1063/1.4952414</doi></publication><publication><id>han_25</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/26566f0a3d392c8755c40b013905a20cb/lepsky</bibsomy_id><title>Cognitive perspectives of information retrieval interaction : elements of a cognitive IR theory</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>P</first><last>Ingwersen</last></author></authors><keys><key>kognition</key><key>merged:lepsky</key><key>information_retrieval</key></keys><date>2018-11-04 17:00:37</date><changeDate>2018-11-04 17:00:37</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1996</year><url /><abstract>The objective of the paper is to amalgamate theories of text retrieval from various research traditions into a cognitive theory for information retrieval interaction. Set in a cognitive framework, the paper outlines the concept of polyrepresentation applied to both the user's cognitive space and the information space of IR systems. The concept seeks to represent the current user's information need, problem state, and domain work task or interest in a structure of causality. Further, it implies that we should apply different methods of representation and a variety of IR techniques of different cognitive and functional origin simultaneously to each semantic full-text entity in the information space. The cognitive differences imply that by applying cognitive overlaps of information objects, originating from different interpretations of such objects through time and by type, the degree of uncertainty inherent in IR is decreased. Polyrepresentation and the use of cognitive overlaps are associated with, but not identical to, data fusion in IR. By explicitly incorporating all the cognitive structures participating in the interactive communication processes during IR, the cognitive theory provides a comprehensive view of these processes. It encompasses the ad hoc theories of text retrieval and IR techniques hitherto developed in mainstream retrieval research. It has elements in common with van Rijsbergen and Lalmas' logical uncertainty theory and may be regarded as compatible with that conception of IR. Epistemologically speaking, the theory views IR interaction as processes of cognition, potentially occurring in all the information processing components of IR, that may be applied, in particular, to the user in a situational context. The theory draws upon basic empirical results from information seeking investigations in the operational online environment, and from mainstream IR research on partial matching techniques and relevance feedback. By viewing users, source systems, intermediary mechanisms and information in a global context, the cognitive perspective attempts a comprehensive understanding of essential IR phenomena and concepts, such as the nature of information needs, cognitive inconsistency and retrieval overlaps, logical uncertainty, the concept of `document', relevance measures and experimental settings. An inescapable consequence of this approach is to rely more on sociological and psychological investigative methods when evaluating systems and to view relevance in IR as situational, relative, partial, differentiated and non-linear. The lack of consistency among authors, indexers, evaluators or users is of an identical cognitive nature. It is unavoidable, and indeed favourable to IR. In particular, for full-text retrieval, alternative semantic entities, including Salton et al.'s `passage retrieval', are proposed to replace the traditional document record as the basic retrieval entity. These empirically observed phenomena of inconsistency and of semantic entities and values associated with data interpretation support strongly a cognitive approach to IR and the logical use of polyrepresentation, cognitive overlaps, and both data fusion and data diffusion.</abstract><journal>Journal of documentation</journal><volume>52</volume><number>1</number><pages>3--50</pages></publication><publication><id>han_26</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2ac69ea1c760f913cae73285664c94292/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Dust Properties of CII Detected z $\sim$ 5.5 Galaxies: New HST/WFC3
  Near-IR Observations</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Ivana</first><last>Barišić</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Andreas L.</first><last>Faisst</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Peter L.</first><last>Capak</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Riccardo</first><last>Pavesi</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Dominik A.</first><last>Riechers</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Nick Z.</first><last>Scoville</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Kevin C.</first><last>Cooke</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Jeyhan S.</first><last>Kartaltepe</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Caitlin M.</first><last>Casey</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Vernesa</first><last>Smolčić</last></author></authors><keys><key>galaxies</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>dust</key><key>high-z</key></keys><date>2017-07-12 09:59:17</date><changeDate>2017-07-12 09:59:17</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1707.02980</url><note>cite arxiv:1707.02980Comment: 9 pages, 3 figures, 1 table. Accepted for publication in The  Astrophysical Journal</note><abstract>We examine the rest-frame ultra-violet (UV) properties of 10
CII$łambda158\,m$$-$detected galaxies at $z\sim5.5$ in COSMOS
using new HST/WFC3 near-infrared imaging. Together with pre-existing $158\,\rm
m-$continuum and CII line measurements by ALMA, we study their dust
attenuation properties on the IRX-$\beta$ diagram, which connects the total
dust emission ($\propto$ IRX=log($L_FIR/L_1600$)) to the line-of-sight dust
column ($\propto\beta$). We find systematically bluer UV continuum spectral
slopes ($\beta$) compared to previous low-resolution ground-based measurements,
which relieves some of the tension between models of dust attenuation and
observations at high redshifts. While most of the galaxies are consistent with
local starburst or Small Magellanic cloud like dust properties, we find
galaxies with low IRX values and a large range in $\beta$ that cannot be
explained by models of a uniform dust distribution well mixed with stars. A
stacking analysis of Keck/DEIMOS optical spectra indicates that these galaxies
are metal-poor with young stellar populations which could significantly alter
their spatial dust distribution.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_27</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2d2d44de266d188d8a12b6adecbdd4e9e/klawei</bibsomy_id><title>Neural Models for Information Retrieval</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Bhaskar</first><last>Mitra</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Nick</first><last>Craswell</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:klawei</key><key>IR</key><key>deep_learning</key></keys><date>2017-05-23 08:24:25</date><changeDate>2017-05-23 08:24:25</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1705.01509</url><note>cite arxiv:1705.01509</note><abstract>Neural ranking models for information retrieval (IR) use shallow or deep
neural networks to rank search results in response to a query. Traditional
learning to rank models employ machine learning techniques over hand-crafted IR
features. By contrast, neural models learn representations of language from raw
text that can bridge the gap between query and document vocabulary. Unlike
classical IR models, these new machine learning based approaches are
data-hungry, requiring large scale training data before they can be deployed.
This tutorial introduces basic concepts and intuitions behind neural IR models,
and places them in the context of traditional retrieval models. We begin by
introducing fundamental concepts of IR and different neural and non-neural
approaches to learning vector representations of text. We then review shallow
neural IR methods that employ pre-trained neural term embeddings without
learning the IR task end-to-end. We introduce deep neural networks next,
discussing popular deep architectures. Finally, we review the current DNN
models for information retrieval. We conclude with a discussion on potential
future directions for neural IR.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_28</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/24cc8362fff6e6ddd1e24f74d66ab3964/lillejul</bibsomy_id><title>Comparing Effectiveness in TDT and IR</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>James</first><last>Allan</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Victor</first><last>Lavrenko</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Hubert</first><last>Jin</last></author></authors><keys><key>event_detection</key><key>merged:lillejul</key><key>erc</key><key>DETECTION,INFORMATION</key><key>RETRIEVAL,ROUTING,TRACKING</key></keys><date>2012-09-17 17:48:52</date><changeDate>2012-09-17 17:48:55</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2000</year><url>http://oai.dtic.mil/oai/oai?verb=getRecord\&amp;amp;metadataPrefix=html\&amp;amp;identifier=ADA478126</url><abstract>Many of the research tasks in Topic Detection and Tracking have counterparts in Information Retrieval research. However, the two research communities evaluate their tasks differently, which makes it very difficult to determine the extent to which they can help each other. In this study, we compare the performance of TDT tracking task to the IR filtering task, and show that they have nearly identical effectiveness. We also show a method for using tracking to predict error rates for the TDT First Story Detection (FSD) task. We then show that FSD performance is what tracking predicts. More importantly, we show that with current approaches, FSD performance has probably reached the limits of effectiveness.</abstract><journal>Technical Report</journal></publication><publication><id>han_29</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2600d4de8f9f3359d9f1b130a0f177577/jaeschke</bibsomy_id><title>Temporal Information Retrieval</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Nattiya</first><last>Kanhabua</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Roi</first><last>Blanco</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Kjetil</first><last>Nørvåg</last></author></authors><keys><key>retrieval</key><key>merged:jaeschke</key><key>web</key><key>ir</key><key>information</key><key>temporal</key></keys><date>2015-07-15 15:09:06</date><changeDate>2015-07-15 15:09:06</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2015</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1561/1500000043</url><abstract>Temporal dynamics and how they impact upon various components of information retrieval (IR) systems have received a large share of attention in the last decade. In particular, the study of relevance in information retrieval can now be framed within the so-called temporal IR approaches, which explain how user behavior, document content and scale vary with time, and how we can use them in our favor in order to improve retrieval effectiveness. This survey provides a comprehensive overview of temporal IR approaches, centered on the following questions: what are temporal dynamics, why do they occur, and when and how to leverage temporal information throughout the search cycle and architecture. We first explain the general and wide aspects associated to temporal dynamics by focusing on the web domain, from content and structural changes to variations of user behavior and interactions. Next, we pinpoint several research issues and the impact of such temporal characteristics on search, essentially regarding processing dynamic content, temporal query analysis and time-aware ranking. We also address particular aspects of temporal information extraction (for instance, how to timestamp documents and generate temporal profiles of text). To this end, we present existing temporal search engines and applications in related research areas, e.g., exploration, summarization, and clustering of search results, as well as future event retrieval and prediction, where the time dimension also plays an important role.</abstract><journal>Foundations and Trends in Information Retrieval</journal><volume>9</volume><number>2</number><pages>91--208</pages><issn>1554-0669</issn><doi>10.1561/1500000043</doi></publication><publication><id>han_30</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2548e214c60f97c831fee5df4836226f9/aho</bibsomy_id><title>The IIR evaluation model: a framework for evaluation of interactive information retrieval systems</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Pia</first><last>Borlund</last></author></authors><keys><key>evaluation</key><key>merged:aho</key><key>information-exploration</key></keys><date>2018-03-19 12:24:51</date><changeDate>2018-03-19 12:24:51</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2003</year><url>http://informationr.net/ir/8-3/paper152.html</url><abstract>An alternative approach to evaluation of interactive information retrieval (IIR) systems, referred to as the IIR evaluation model, is proposed. The model provides a framework for the collection and analysis of IR interaction data. The aim of the model is two-fold: 1) to facilitate the evaluation of IIR systems as realistically as possible with reference to actual information searching and retrieval processes, though still in a relatively controlled evaluation environment; and 2) to calculate the IIR system performance taking into account the non-binary nature of the assigned relevance assessments. The IIR evaluation model is presented as an alternative to the system-driven Cranfield model (Cleverdon, Mills &amp; Keen, 1966; Cleverdon &amp; Keen, 1966) which still is the dominant approach to the evaluation of IR and IIR systems. Key elements of the IIR evaluation model are the use of realistic scenarios, known as simulated work task situations, and the (call for) alternative performance measures. A simulated work task situation, which is a short 'cover story', serves two main functions: 1) it triggers and develops a simulated information need by allowing for user interpretations of the situation, leading to cognitively individual information need interpretations as in real life; and 2) it is the platform against which situational relevance is judged. Further, by being the same for all test persons experimental control is provided. Hence, the concept of a simulated work task situation ensures the experiment both realism and control. Guidelines and recommendations for the application of simulated work task situations are provided. Examples of alternative performance measures are: relative relevance (RR), ranked half-life (RHL) (Borlund &amp; Ingwersen, 1998), cumulated gain (CG) and cumulated gain with discount (DCG) (Järvelin &amp; Kekäläinen, 2000).  These measures can incorporate non-binary relevance assessments, necessary due to the result of realistic interaction and relevance assessment behaviour of users in the process of searching and assessing relevance of retrieved information objects.</abstract><journal>Information Research</journal><volume>8</volume><number>3</number></publication><publication><id>han_31</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2f25b85851869f2614fd734f8da300108/miki</bibsomy_id><title>The total infrared luminosity may significantly overestimate the star
  formation rate of recently quenched galaxies</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Christopher C.</first><last>Hayward</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Lauranne</first><last>Lanz</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Matthew L. N.</first><last>Ashby</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Giovanni</first><last>Fazio</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Lars</first><last>Hernquist</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Juan Rafael</first><last>Martínez-Galarza</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Kai</first><last>Noeske</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Howard A.</first><last>Smith</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Stijn</first><last>Wuyts</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Andreas</first><last>Zezas</last></author></authors><keys><key>indicator</key><key>ir</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>sfr</key></keys><date>2014-02-04 08:32:50</date><changeDate>2014-02-04 08:32:50</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2014</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1402.0006</url><note>cite arxiv:1402.0006Comment: 6 pages, 3 figures. Submitted to MNRAS Letters. Comments encouraged</note><abstract>The total infrared (IR) luminosity is very useful for estimating the star
formation rate (SFR) of galaxies, but converting the IR luminosity into an SFR
relies on assumptions that do not hold for all galaxies. We test the
effectiveness of the IR luminosity as an SFR indicator by applying it to
synthetic spectral energy distributions generated from three-dimensional
hydrodynamical simulations of isolated disc galaxies and galaxy mergers. In
general, the SFR inferred from the IR luminosity agrees well with the true
instantaneous SFR of the simulated galaxies. However, for the major mergers in
which a strong starburst is induced, the SFR inferred from the IR luminosity
can overestimate the instantaneous SFR during the post-starburst phase by
greater than two orders of magnitude. Even though the instantaneous SFR
decreases rapidly after the starburst, the stars that were formed in the
starburst remain dust-obscured and thus produce significant IR luminosity.
Consequently, use of the IR luminosity as an SFR indicator may cause one to
conclude that post-starburst galaxies are still star-forming, whereas in
reality, star formation was recently quenched.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_32</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/273b4efaa112ce9e8ea85b4f055948b7d/ericblackman</bibsomy_id><title>Multi-scale Radio-IR Correlations in M31 and M33: The Role of Magnetic Fields and Star Formation</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>F. S.</first><last>Tabatabaei</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>E. M.</first><last>Berkhuijsen</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>P.</first><last>Frick</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>R.</first><last>Beck</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>E.</first><last>Schinnerer</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:ericblackman</key></keys><date>2019-03-25 08:20:55</date><changeDate>2019-03-25 08:20:55</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2013</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.6253</url><abstract>Interstellar magnetic fields and the propagation of cosmic ray electrons have
an important impact on the radio-infrared (IR) correlation in galaxies. This
becomes evident when studying different spatial scales within galaxies. We
investigate the correlation between the infrared (IR) and free-free/synchrotron
radio continuum emission at 20 cm from the two local group galaxies M31 and M33
on spatial scales between 0.4 and 10 kpc. The multi-scale radio-IR correlations
have been carried out using a wavelet analysis. The free-free and IR emission
are correlated on all scales, but on some scales the synchrotron emission is
only marginally correlated with the IR emission. The synchrotron-IR correlation
is stronger in M33 than in M31 on small scales (&amp;lt;1 kpc), but it is weaker than
in M31 on larger scales. Taking the smallest scale on which the synchrotron-IR
correlation exists as the propagation length of cosmic ray electrons, we show
that the difference on small scales can be explained by the smaller propagation
length in M33 than in M31. On large scales, the difference is due to the thick
disk/halo in M33, which is absent in M31. A comparison of our data with data on
NGC6946, the LMC and M51 suggests that the propagation length is determined by
the ratio of ordered-to-turbulent magnetic field strength, which is consistent
with diffusion of CR electrons in the ISM. As the diffusion length of CR
electrons influences the radio-IR correlation, this dependence is a direct
observational evidence of the importance of magnetic fields for the radio-IR
correlation within galaxies. The star formation rate per surface area only
indirectly influences the diffusion length as it increases the strength of the
turbulent magnetic field.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_33</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/22bceae8079a58b55af05b84be26b33a4/juver</bibsomy_id><title>Information Retrieval</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>C.J.</first><last>van Rijsbergen</last></author></authors><keys><key>multimedia</key><key>technique</key><key>IR</key><key>multi-lingual</key><key>Information_Retrieval</key><key>wismasys0809</key><key>research</key><key>merged:juver</key></keys><date>2008-11-05 17:57:15</date><changeDate>2011-09-22 16:39:16</changeDate><pub-type>book</pub-type><year>1979</year><url>http://books.google.de/books?id=MrzB9AAmcRoC&amp;dq=C.J.+van+Rijsbergen:+Information+Retrieval&amp;pg=PP1&amp;ots=Eksrlfg72h&amp;source=bn&amp;sig=LJUUXH1lU1W1lav5OAKhMy6RAX4&amp;hl=de&amp;sa=X&amp;oi=book_result&amp;resnum=4&amp;ct=result#PPR5,M1</url><abstract>This is a general introduction to Information Retrieval concentrating on some specific topics. I will begin by setting the scene for IR research and introduce its extensive experimental evaluation methodology. I will highlight some of the related areas of research which are currently in fashion emphasising the role of IR in each. For each introductory topic I will illustrate its relevance to IR in the context of a multimedia and multi-lingual environment where appropriate. I will also try and relate these topics to the other papers contained in this volume. My main purpose will be to introduce some underlying concepts and ideas essential for the understanding of IR research and techniques.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_34</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/29a48b1263d1202a236aaab4772a187a0/jfischer</bibsomy_id><title>IR spectroscopy of a Pd-carbonyl surface compound</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>K.</first><last>Wolter</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>O.</first><last>Seiferth</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>J.</first><last>Libuda</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>H.</first><last>Kuhlenbeck</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>M.</first><last>B�umer</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>H. J.</first><last>Freund</last></author></authors><keys><key>science</key><key>surface</key><key>merged:jfischer</key></keys><date>2009-10-30 10:04:05</date><changeDate>2009-10-30 10:04:21</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1997</year><url>http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/B6TFN-3SFVBFC-2C/2/738daf8f3538c55e213402a508c87e69</url><abstract>Pd is deposited onto a model alumina surface in the presence of a
	CO atmosphere of 3 × 10-6 mbar at liquid nitrogen temperatures.
	According to the IR spectra the palladium carbonyl compound formed
	contains weakly bound terminal and more strongly bound bridging CO
	molecules, the spectra being similar to the IR spectra of colloidal
	metal particles in solution and the IR spectra of CO adsorbed
	on small deposited Pd particles. In line with thermal desorption
	studies of the stability of the compound, the IR spectra reveal
	the transition from the compound to a situation where CO is adsorbed
	on larger compact metal aggregates upon heating to room temperature.</abstract><journal>Chem. Phys. Lett.</journal><volume>277</volume><number>5-6</number><pages>513--520</pages><issn>0009-2614</issn><doi>10.1016/S0009-2614(97)00956-1</doi></publication><publication><id>han_35</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2f70729ce23a73e2fbf6f30bdfbb0d0bb/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Herschel-PACS Observations of Far-IR CO Line Emission in NGC 1068:
  Highly Excited Molecular Gas in the Circumnuclear Disk</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>S.</first><last>Hailey-Dunsheath</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>E.</first><last>Sturm</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>J.</first><last>Fischer</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>A.</first><last>Sternberg</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>J.</first><last>Graci&amp;#xe1;-Carpio</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>R.</first><last>Davies</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>E.</first><last>Gonz&amp;#xe1;lez-Alfonso</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>D.</first><last>Mark</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>A.</first><last>Poglitsch</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>A.</first><last>Contursi</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>R.</first><last>Genzel</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>D.</first><last>Lutz</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>L.</first><last>Tacconi</last></author><author><nr>14</nr><first>S.</first><last>Veilleux</last></author><author><nr>15</nr><first>A.</first><last>Verma</last></author><author><nr>16</nr><first>J. A.</first><last>de Jong</last></author></authors><keys><key>warm</key><key>molecular</key><key>agn</key><key>gas</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2012-02-28 05:11:51</date><changeDate>2012-02-28 05:11:51</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2012</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1202.5746</url><note>cite arxiv:1202.5746Comment: 18 pages, 10 figures. Submitted to ApJ</note><abstract>We report the detection of far-IR CO rotational emission from the
prototypical Seyfert 2 galaxy NGC 1068. Using Herschel-PACS, we have detected
10 transitions in the J_upper=14-24 (E_upper/k_B = 580-1656 K) range, all of
which are consistent with arising from within the central 10&amp;quot; (700 pc). The
detected transitions are modeled as arising from 2 different components: a
moderate excitation (ME) component close to the galaxy systemic velocity, and a
high excitation (HE) component that is blueshifted by ~70 km s^-1. We employ
a large velocity gradient (LVG) model and derive n_H2~10^5.7 cm^-3,
T_kin~150 K, and M_H2~10^6.9 M_sun for the ME component, and n_H2~10^6.3
cm^-3, T_kin~440 K, and M_H2~10^5.8 M_sun for the HE component, although
for both components the uncertainties in the density and mass are ~plus/minus 1
dex. Both components arise from denser and possibly warmer gas than traced by
low-J CO transitions, and the ME component likely makes a significant
contribution to the mass budget in the nuclear region. We compare the CO line
profiles with those of other molecular tracers observed at higher spatial and
spectral resolution, and find that the ME transitions are consistent with these
lines arising in the ~200 pc diameter ring of material traced by H_2 1-0 S(1)
observations. The blueshift of the HE lines may also be consistent with the
bluest regions of this H_2 ring, but a better kinematic match is found with a
clump of infalling gas ~40 pc north of the AGN. We consider potential heating
mechanisms, and conclude that X-ray or shock heating of both components is
viable, while far-UV heating is unlikely. We also report sensitive upper limits
extending up to J_upper=50, which place constraints on the emission from the
X-ray obscuring medium.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_36</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2775c7ee7077a42257e053fc90f9629a6/dret</bibsomy_id><title>Neighborhood Restrictions in Geographic IR</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Steven</first><last>Schockaert</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Martine</first><last>De Cock</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:dret</key></keys><date>2009-01-14 00:43:43</date><changeDate>2011-09-22 16:39:42</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2007</year><url /><abstract>Geographic information retrieval (GIR) systems allow users to specify a geographic context, in addition to a more traditional query, enabling the system to pinpoint interesting search results whose relevancy is location-dependent. In particular local search services have become a widely used mechanism to find businesses, such as hotels, restaurants, and shops, which satisfy a geographical restriction. Unfortunately, many useful types of geographic restrictions are currently not supported in these systems, including restrictions that specify the neighborhood in which the business should be located. As the boundaries of city neighborhoods are not readily available, automated techniques to construct representations of the spatial extent of neighborhoods are required to support this kind of restrictions. In this paper, we propose such a technique, using fuzzy footprints to cope with the inherent vagueness of most neighborhood boundaries, and we provide experimental results that demonstrate the potential of our technique in a local search setting.</abstract><pages>167-174</pages><doi>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/1277741.1277772</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the 30th Annual International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research and Development in Information Retrieval</booktitle><publisher>ACM Press</publisher><isbn>978-1-59593-597-7</isbn><uri>http://www.cwi.ugent.be/martine/papers/volledig/sschockaert2007b.pdf</uri></publication><publication><id>han_37</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/260dee28820870efa3af4463f451ac4a8/wnpxrz</bibsomy_id><title>Exploring Independent Trends in a Topic-Based Search Engine</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Jukka</first><last>Perkio</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Wray</first><last>Buntine</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Sami</first><last>Perttu</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:wnpxrz</key><key>engine</key><key>ir</key><key>topic</key><key>search</key></keys><date>2007-08-15 11:45:58</date><changeDate>2007-08-15 11:45:58</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2004</year><url>http://cms.dt.uh.edu/Faculty/ChenP/IR/perkio04exploring.pdf</url><abstract>Topic-based search engines are an alternative to simple keyword search engines that are common in today’s intranets. The temporal behaviour of the topics in a topic model based search engine can be used for trend analysis, which is an important research goal on its own. We apply topic modelling to an online financial newspaper data and show that some of the trends in the topics are consistent with common understanding.</abstract><pages>664--668</pages><booktitle>WI'04: IEEE/WIC/ACM International Conference on Web Intelligence</booktitle></publication><publication><id>han_38</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2f1f52bb37fae37c595c349955d3034b8/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Composite Reflective/Absorptive IR-Blocking Filters Embedded in
  Metamaterial Antireflection Coated Silicon</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>C. D.</first><last>Munson</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>S. K.</first><last>Choi</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>K. P.</first><last>Coughlin</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>J. J.</first><last>McMahon</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>K. H.</first><last>Miller</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>L. A.</first><last>Page</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>E. J.</first><last>Wollack</last></author></authors><keys><key>filters</key><key>metamaterial</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2017-03-02 07:20:52</date><changeDate>2017-03-02 07:20:52</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1702.08454</url><note>cite arxiv:1702.08454</note><abstract>Infrared (IR) blocking filters are crucial for controlling the radiative
loading on cryogenic systems and for optimizing the sensitivity of bolometric
detectors in the far-IR. We present a new IR filter approach based on a
combination of patterned frequency selective structures on silicon and a thin
(50 $m$ thick) absorptive composite based on powdered reststrahlen
absorbing materials. For a 300 K blackbody, this combination reflects
$\sim$50\% of the incoming light and blocks 99.8\% of the total
power with negligible thermal gradients and excellent low frequency
transmission. This allows for a reduction in the IR thermal loading to
negligible levels in a single cold filter. These composite filters are
fabricated on silicon substrates which provide excellent thermal transport
laterally through the filter and ensure that the entire area of the absorptive
filter stays near the bath temperature. A metamaterial antireflection coating
cut into these substrates reduces in-band reflections to below 1\%, and the
in-band absorption of the powder mix is below 1\% for signal bands below 750
GHz. This type of filter can be directly incorporated into silicon refractive
optical elements.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_39</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/212592d5f805db5bd127ee5abae1a4325/jaeschke</bibsomy_id><title>IR evaluation methods for retrieving highly relevant documents</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kalervo</first><last>Järvelin</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Jaana</first><last>Kekäläinen</last></author></authors><keys><key>retrieval</key><key>merged:jaeschke</key><key>evaluation</key><key>ir</key><key>merged:dblp</key><key>information</key><key>dblp</key></keys><date>2009-11-03 13:28:34</date><changeDate>2014-07-28 15:57:11</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2000</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=345545</url><abstract>This paper proposes evaluation methods based on the use of non-dichotomous relevance judgements in IR experiments. It is argued that evaluation methods should credit IR methods for their ability to retrieve highly relevant documents. This is desirable from the user point of view in modern large IR environments. The proposed methods are (1) a novel application of P-R curves and average precision computations based on separate recall bases for documents of different degrees of relevance, and (2) two novel measures computing the cumulative gain the user obtains by examining the retrieval result up to a given ranked position. We then demonstrate the use of these evaluation methods in a case study on the effectiveness of query types, based on combinations of query structures and expansion, in retrieving documents of various degrees of relevance. The test was run with a best match retrieval system (In-Query1) in a text database consisting of newspaper articles. The results indicate that the tested strong query structures are most effective in retrieving highly relevant documents. The differences between the query types are practically essential and statistically significant. More generally, the novel evaluation methods and the case demonstrate that non-dichotomous relevance assessments are applicable in IR experiments, may reveal interesting phenomena, and allow harder testing of IR methods.</abstract><pages>41--48</pages><doi>10.1145/345508.345545</doi><booktitle>SIGIR '00: Proceedings of the 23rd Annual International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research and Development in Information Retrieval</booktitle><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>1-58113-226-3</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_40</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2c54ce7c0abcbba97fa9bb5262fb3a689/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Automatic stellar spectra parameterisation in the IR CaII triplet region</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>G.</first><last>Kordopatis</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>A.</first><last>Recio-Blanco</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>P.</first><last>de Laverny</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>A.</first><last>Bijaoui</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>V.</first><last>Hill</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>G.</first><last>Gilmore</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>R. F. G.</first><last>Wyse</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>C.</first><last>Ordenovic</last></author></authors><keys><key>triplet</key><key>Ca</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2011-09-29 19:21:02</date><changeDate>2011-09-29 19:21:02</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2011</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1109.6237</url><note>cite arxiv:1109.6237
Comment: 17 pages, 11 figures, accepted for publication in A&amp;amp;A</note><abstract>(Abridged) Galactic archaeology aims to determine the evolution of the Galaxy
from the chemical and kinematical properties of its stars. The analysis of
current large spectroscopic surveys (thousands of stars) and future ones
(millions of stars) require automated analysis techniques to obtain robust
estimates of the stellar parameters. Several on-going and planned spectroscopic
surveys have selected their wavelength region to contain the IR CaII triplet
and this paper focuses on the automatic analysis of such spectra.
  We investigated two algorithms, MATISSE and DEGAS, both of which compare the
observed spectrum to a grid of synthetic spectra, but each uses a different
mathematical approach for finding the optimum match and hence the best stellar
parameters.
  We identified degeneracies in different regions of the HR diagram: hot dwarfs
and giants share the same spectral signatures. Furthermore, the surface gravity
of cooler dwarfs is difficult to determine accurately. These effects are
intensified when the information decreases (e.g. metal-poor stars or low SNR
spectra). Our results show that the local projection method MATISSE is
preferred for high SNR spectra, whereas the decision-tree method DEGAS is
preferred for noisier spectra. We therefore propose a hybrid approach of both
methods and show that sufficiently accurate results for the purposes of
galactic archaeology are retrieved down to SNR~20 for typical thin or thick
disc stars, and down to SNR~50 for the more metal-poor halo giants.
  If unappreciated, degeneracies in stellar parameters can introduce biases in
derived quantities for target stars such as distances and full space motions.
These biases can be minimised using the knowledge gained by thorough testing of
the proposed algorithm, which in turn lead to robust automated methods for the
coming extensive stellar spectroscopic surveys in the Local Group.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_41</id><bibsomy_id>http://ir-library.ku.ac.ke/handle/123456789/8985</bibsomy_id><title>Efficiency of Macropropagation in Relation to Other Banana Seedling Production Methods in Different Agro-ecologies in Central and Eastern Kenya</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Martha Rhoda</first><last>Kasyoka</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:liloubio</key><key>kenya</key><key>Macropropagation</key></keys><date>2014-03-06 15:32:04</date><changeDate>2014-03-06 15:32:04</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2014</year><url>http://ir-library.ku.ac.ke/handle/123456789/8985</url><abstract>Department of Agricultural Sciences and Technology, 72p. 2013</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_42</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2da4c2281e31e9d9ef984d16ace1553c7/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Herschel Far-IR counterparts of SDSS galaxies: Analysis of commonly used
  Star Formation Rate estimates</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>H. Domínguez</first><last>Sánchez</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>A.</first><last>Bongiovanni</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>M. A.</first><last>Lara-López</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>I.</first><last>Oteo</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>J.</first><last>Cepa</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>A. M. Pérez</first><last>García</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>M.</first><last>Sánchez-Portal</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>A.</first><last>Ederoclite</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>D.</first><last>Lutz</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>G.</first><last>Cresci</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>I.</first><last>Delvecchio</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>S.</first><last>Berta</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>B.</first><last>Magnelli</last></author><author><nr>14</nr><first>P.</first><last>Popesso</last></author><author><nr>15</nr><first>F.</first><last>Pozzi</last></author><author><nr>16</nr><first>L.</first><last>Riguccini</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:miki</key><key>calibration</key><key>sfr</key></keys><date>2014-03-17 10:59:18</date><changeDate>2014-03-17 10:59:18</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2014</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.3615</url><note>cite arxiv:1403.3615Comment: 24 pages, 23 figures, accepted for publication in MNRAS</note><abstract>We study a hundred of galaxies from the spectroscopic Sloan Digital Sky
Survey with individual detections in the Far-Infrared Herschel PACS bands (100
or 160 $\mu$m) and in the GALEX Far-UltraViolet band up to z$\sim$0.4 in the
COSMOS and Lockman Hole fields. The galaxies are divided into 4 spectral and 4
morphological types. For the star forming and unclassifiable galaxies we
calculate dust extinctions from the UV slope, the H$\alpha$/H$\beta$ ratio and
the $L_IR/L_UV$ ratio. There is a tight correlation between the
dust extinction and both $L_IR$ and metallicity. We calculate
SFR$_total$ and compare it with other SFR estimates (H$\alpha$, UV, SDSS)
finding a very good agreement between them with smaller dispersions than
typical SFR uncertainties. We study the effect of mass and metallicity, finding
that it is only significant at high masses for SFR$_H\alpha$. For the AGN and
composite galaxies we find a tight correlation between SFR and L$_IR$
($\sigma\sim$0.29), while the dispersion in the SFR - L$_UV$ relation is
larger ($\sigma\sim$0.57). The galaxies follow the prescriptions of the
Fundamental Plane in the M-Z-SFR space.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_43</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2df4307114199e3b68483937e13b56990/jrennstich</bibsomy_id><title>Between Science and Art: Questionable International Relations Theories</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Yiwei</first><last>Wang</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:jrennstich</key><key>ir</key></keys><date>2010-03-02 17:25:53</date><changeDate>2010-03-02 17:27:13</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2007</year><url /><abstract>International relations (IR) is both a science and an art, i.e. the unity of object and subject. Traditional international relations theories (IRT) have probed the laws of IR, in an attempt to become the universal science. IRT have developed into a class doctrine that defends the legitimacy of the western international system as a result of proceeding from the reality of IR, while neglecting its evolving process, and overlooking the meaning of art and the presence of multi-international systems. In other words, IRT have turned into what Karl Marx might have deemed as the vulgar international relations theories (VIRT). For this reason, we declare the end of international relations theories. This phenomenon can only be negated by the so-called Chinese School, which will set the sustainable and harmonious relations among nations, between state and non-state actors, and within states and non-state actors (in one word `global-society') in five life-forces of economy, politics, military, culture, and religion. Consequently, this will bring about a real regression of nationality and compatible development of various international systems.</abstract><journal>Japanese Journal of Political Science</journal><volume>8</volume><number>2</number><pages>191--208</pages><affiliation>Center for American Studies, Fudan University email: yiweiwang@fudan.edu.cn</affiliation></publication><publication><id>han_44</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2ff7a440d25d6644d639b399434cbae2f/gsmith</bibsomy_id><title>Comparison between mass spectra of individual organic particles generated by UV laser ablation and in the IR/UV two-step mode</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Alla</first><last>Zelenyuka</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Juan</first><last>Yang</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Dan</first><last>Imre</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:gsmith</key><key>Desorption/Ionization,</key><key>Spectrometry,</key><key>Size,</key><key>Ionization,</key><key>Instrument,</key><key>Airborne</key><key>Desorption,</key><key>Performance,</key><key>Particles,</key><key>Ionization</key><key>Particle</key><key>Splat,</key><key>Aerosol-Particles,</key><key>Laser</key><key>Mass</key><key>Single</key><key>Ultrafine</key></keys><date>2010-06-22 19:38:37</date><changeDate>2010-06-22 19:38:53</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2009</year><url>http://www.sciencedirect.com/science?_ob=ArticleURL&amp;_udi=B6VND-4VJBTWM-1&amp;_user=655127&amp;_coverDate=04%252F15%252F2009&amp;_rdoc=1&amp;_fmt=high&amp;_orig=search&amp;_sort=d&amp;_docanchor=&amp;view=c&amp;_acct=C000033918&amp;_version=1&amp;_urlVersion=0&amp;_userid=655127&amp;md5=20b9597dd71d491c6c9612195f20a206</url><abstract>In ablation-based single particle mass spectrometry it is common to find that the mass spectra of particles with identical compositions exhibit significant particle-to-particle fluctuations and high degree of fragmentation. This is particularly true when it comes to particles containing organic compounds. At laser fluence that is sufficient to ionize sulfates, mass spectra of the identical organic particles are classified into multitude of classes, some of which are indistinguishable from elemental carbon. In contrast, the individual particle mass spectra generated in two-step mode, in which an IR laser pulse is used to evaporate the semivolatile particle components and a time delayed UV laser pulse is used to ionize the evaporating plume, exhibit greatly diminished particle-to-particle fluctuations and significantly improved mass spectral quality. Since individual particle mass spectra must first be classified and only then can be averaged and analyzed, the IR/UV mode greatly improves the capability to properly quantify particle compositions. We present an experimental investigation of the properties and behavior of individual particle mass spectra of organic particles that are generated by ablation and in the two-step mode as function of UV laser fluence and the delay between the two lasers. The study shows that the two-step mode yields highly reproducible mass spectra that contain sufficient detail to allow molecular identification. In addition it produces significantly higher mass spectral intensities that are linearly related to the mass of organics in the particles. In contrast, ablation generated mass spectra were found to exhibit high degree of fragmentation and large particle-to-particle fluctuations. (C) 2009 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</abstract><journal>International Journal of Mass Spectrometry</journal><volume>282</volume><number>1-2</number><pages>6--12</pages><language>English</language><doi>10.1016/j.ijms.2009.01.015</doi><uri>papers://E88B624E-D406-46FF-9D95-BB9C1AAE3FDC/Paper/p2966</uri><affiliation>Pacific NW Natl Lab, Richland, WA 99354 USA</affiliation></publication><publication><id>han_45</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/20b753d48e72fa1321475c962ff6aafbc/vngudivada</bibsomy_id><title>Axiomatic Thinking for Information Retrieval: And Related Tasks</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Enrique</first><last>Amigo</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Hui</first><last>Fang</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Stefano</first><last>Mizzaro</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>ChengXiang</first><last>Zhai</last></author></authors><keys><key>IR</key><key>IRModel</key><key>AxiomaticThinking</key><key>merged:vngudivada</key></keys><date>2018-05-19 14:53:50</date><changeDate>2019-03-25 17:06:11</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2017</year><url /><abstract>This is the first workshop on the emerging interdisciplinary research area of applying axiomatic thinking to information retrieval (IR) and related tasks. The workshop aims to help foster collaboration of researchers working on different perspectives of axiomatic thinking and encourage discussion and research on general methodological issues related to applying axiomatic thinking to IR and related tasks.</abstract><pages>1419--1420</pages><doi>10.1145/3077136.3084369</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the 40th International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research and Development in Information Retrieval</booktitle><series>SIGIR '17</series><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>978-1-4503-5022-8</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_46</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/22299145d5300f939679a19982bd6e548/nosebrain</bibsomy_id><title>IR evaluation methods for retrieving highly relevant documents</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kalervo</first><last>Järvelin</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Jaana</first><last>Kekäläinen</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:cbrewster</key><key>merged:pprett</key><key>suchkiste</key><key>ir,</key><key>method</key><key>dcg</key><key>ir</key><key>merged:tillk</key><key>ndcg</key><key>merged:mkroell</key><key>ndcg,</key><key>ungelesen</key><key>InformationRetrieval</key><key>merged:nosebrain</key><key>evaluation</key><key>evaluation,</key><key>merged:utahell</key><key>seminal</key></keys><date>2012-12-23 16:10:43</date><changeDate>2012-12-23 16:10:43</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2000</year><url>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/345508.345545</url><abstract>This paper proposes evaluation methods based on the use of non-dichotomous relevance judgements in IR experiments. It is argued that evaluation methods should credit IR methods for their ability to retrieve highly relevant documents. This is desirable from the user point of view in modern large IR environments. The proposed methods are (1) a novel application of P-R curves and average precision computations based on separate recall bases for documents of different degrees of relevance, and (2) two novel measures computing the cumulative gain the user obtains by examining the retrieval result up to a given ranked position. We then demonstrate the use of these evaluation methods in a case study on the effectiveness of query types, based on combinations of query structures and expansion, in retrieving documents of various degrees of relevance. The test was run with a best match retrieval system (In-Query&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;) in a text database consisting of newspaper articles. The results indicate that the tested strong query structures are most effective in retrieving highly relevant documents. The differences between the query types are practically essential and statistically significant. More generally, the novel evaluation methods and the case demonstrate that non-dichotomous relevance assessments are applicable in IR experiments, may reveal interesting phenomena, and allow harder testing of IR methods.</abstract><pages>41--48</pages><doi>10.1145/345508.345545</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the 23rd Annual International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research and Development in Information Retrieval (SIGIR 2000)</booktitle><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>1-58113-226-3</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_47</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/23605f4ca7455c8280c67045bbabebb6d/ikpcologne</bibsomy_id><title>Investigation of photoneutron reactions on Os-192 and Ir-191,Ir-193 at
   energies of relevance for the astrophysical p process</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>J.</first><last>Hasper</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>D.</first><last>Galaviz</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>S.</first><last>Mueller</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>A.</first><last>Sauerwein</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>D.</first><last>Savran</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>L.</first><last>Schnorrenberger</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>K.</first><last>Sonnabend</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>A.</first><last>Zilges</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:ikpcologne</key><key>myown</key><key>zilges</key></keys><date>2019-11-20 10:09:48</date><changeDate>2019-11-20 10:09:48</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2009</year><url /><abstract>We have investigated the photoneutron reactions on the isotopes Os-192
   and Ir-191,Ir-193 for astrophysically relevant photon energies just
   above the neutron separation energy. The experiments were performed
   using the photoactivation technique at the superconducting Darmstadt
   linear electron accelerator (S-DALINAC). The measurements extend the
   existing experimental database on photoneutron reactions in this mass
   region and serve as an important test for the state-of-the-art
   statistical model calculations commonly used for the prediction of
   stellar reaction rates.</abstract><journal>Phys. Rev. C</journal><volume>79</volume><number>5</number><issn>2469-9985</issn><doi>10.1103/PhysRevC.79.055807</doi></publication><publication><id>han_48</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2dd1ffb80913f82adc3422b824ed4f556/hlwoodcock</bibsomy_id><title>Comparative investigation of the structure and IR of tetrazolate ion with density functional theory and MP2 ab initio methods</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Z. X.</first><last>Chen</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>H. M.</first><last>Xiao</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:hlwoodcock</key><key>bibtex-import</key></keys><date>2006-06-16 05:03:46</date><changeDate>2006-06-16 05:03:46</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1999</year><url /><abstract>A number of DFT methods were used to calculate the geometry, electronic structure, IR and thermodynamic properties of tetrazolate ion. Comparisons were made between the DFT computed results and the MP2 ab initio ones. Compared with the ab initio results, it was found that the hybrid DFT method: B3LYP, has the best performance in calculating all these properties than the other DFT methods, Therefore, it can be used for systematic investigation of tetrazole derivatives and their complexes.</abstract><journal>CHEMICAL JOURNAL OF CHINESE UNIVERSITIES-CHINESE</journal><volume>20</volume><number>5</number><pages>782--787</pages></publication><publication><id>han_49</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2fa25894f6b77abb8a4d714ea0abd9d97/ericblackman</bibsomy_id><title>Diagnostics of Coronal Magnetic Fields Through the Hanle Effect in UV and IR Lines</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>N. E.</first><last>Raouafi</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>P.</first><last>Riley</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>S.</first><last>Gibson</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>S.</first><last>Fineschi</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>S. K.</first><last>Solanki</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:ericblackman</key></keys><date>2019-03-25 08:20:55</date><changeDate>2019-03-25 08:20:55</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2016</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.3389/fspas.2016.00020</url><abstract>The plasma thermodynamics in the solar upper atmosphere, particularly in the
corona, are dominated by the magnetic field, which controls the flow and
dissipation of energy. The relative lack of knowledge of the coronal vector
magnetic field is a major handicap for progress in coronal physics. This makes
the development of measurement methods of coronal magnetic fields a high
priority in solar physics. The Hanle effect in the UV and IR spectral lines is
a largely unexplored diagnostic. We use magnetohydrodynamic (MHD) simulations
to study the magnitude of the signal to be expected for typical coronal
magnetic fields for selected spectral lines in the UV and IR wavelength ranges,
namely the H I Ly-\$\alpha\$ and the He I 10830 \AA lines. We show that the
selected lines are useful for reliable diagnosis of coronal magnetic fields.
The results show that the combination of polarization measurements of spectral
lines with different sensitivities to the Hanle effect may be most appropriate
for deducing coronal magnetic properties from future observations.</abstract><journal>Frontiers in Astronomy and Space Sciences</journal><volume>3</volume><issn>2296-987X</issn><doi>10.3389/fspas.2016.00020</doi></publication><publication><id>han_50</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2a40bf156db914567f9d7afcd6b06128f/gscbpsjournal</bibsomy_id><title>Spectroscopic profiling of Eclipta prostrata ethanolic leaf extract by UV &amp; FT-IR</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Banu Shirin</first><last>Akhter</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Aziz</first><last>Shahin</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Farhana</first><last>Sharika</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Al-Reza Md</first><last>Sharif</last></author></authors><keys><key>Eclipta</key><key>prostrata</key><key>merged:gscbpsjournal</key><key>leaf</key></keys><date>2020-12-30 17:04:28</date><changeDate>2020-12-30 17:04:28</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2019</year><url>https://gsconlinepress.com/journals/gscbps/node/847</url><abstract>Eclipta prostrata is a significant medicinal plant which is commonly known as “Keshoraj” in Bangladesh. The present study deals with spectroscopic analysis of ethanolic extract of leaf by UV and FT-IR of this plant. The UV and FT-IR spectrum shows the presence of carbonyl group (ketone), amide, aromatic nature of compounds, sulfur compounds, nitro compounds, non-conjugated diene, gem distributed, 1°, 2° amines, anthracene and flavones, fistein, quercetin, NaQSA Sodium Salts of  Quercetin 5’ Sulfonic Acid, myricetin, anthocyanin types of flavonoids. The above mention bioactive compounds are mainly contributed in medicinal utilities of the plant.</abstract><journal>GSC Biological and Pharmaceutical Sciences</journal><volume>8</volume><number>1</number><issn>2581-3250</issn><doi>10.30574/gscbps.2019.8.1.0060</doi></publication><publication><id>han_51</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2c8e03cdc4967169b61c8212b9206b40f/sasha-markov</bibsomy_id><title>Cisplatin Binding to Biological Ligands Revealed at the Encounter Complex Level by IR Action Spectroscopy</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Davide</first><last>Corinti</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Cecilia</first><last>Coletti</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Nazzareno</first><last>Re</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Barbara</first><last>Chiavarino</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Maria Elisa</first><last>Crestoni</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Simonetta</first><last>Fornarini</last></author></authors><keys><key>platinum</key><key>merged:sasha-markov</key><key>anticancer</key></keys><date>2016-03-03 09:57:58</date><changeDate>2016-03-03 09:57:58</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2016</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1002/chem.201504521</url><abstract>Cisplatin cis-diamminedichloroplatinum(II) was the first platinum-based antineoplastic agent and is still a cornerstone for the treatment of various solid tumors. Reactive events responsible for cisplatin activity are unveiled here at the molecular level. Simple ligands (L) representing ubiquitous functional groups in the biological environment likely to be encountered by administered cisplatin have been allowed to react with cis-PtCl(NH3)2(H2O)+, the primary intermediate from cisplatin hydrolysis. The substitution reactions have been examined by a combined experimental and computational approach and the structural features of the substitution product, cis-PtCl(NH3)2(L)+, have been probed by IR multiple-photon dissociation (IRMPD) spectroscopy. Furthermore, IRMPD spectroscopy has been exploited to elucidate the structure of PtCl(NH3)2(L)(H2O)+ clusters, also obtained by electrospray ionization (ESI) from the aqueous solution and representing the major focus of this investigation. These ions conform to the encounter complex of cis-PtCl(NH3)2(H2O)+ with the incoming ligand and represent the first direct evidence of a prototypical Eigen–Wilkins encounter complex in solution, lying on the reaction coordinate for ligand substitution and extracted by ESI for mass spectrometric analysis. Activated PtCl(NH3)2(L)(H2O)+ ions dissociate by the loss of either H2O or L, the former process implying a ligand substitution event. IRMPD spectroscopy has thus revealed both structural details and reaction dynamics at the level of the isolated encounter complex.</abstract><journal>Chemistry – A European Journal</journal><volume>22</volume><number>11</number><pages>3794--3803</pages><issn>1521-3765</issn><doi>10.1002/chem.201504521</doi></publication><publication><id>han_52</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2977aa6276aa8af172c9d2cc4c860b14f/kgreff</bibsomy_id><title>Hand gesture recognition with a novel IR time-of-flight range camera: a pilot study</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Pia</first><last>Breuer</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Christian</first><last>Eckes</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Stefan</first><last>Müller</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:kgreff</key><key>recognition</key><key>TOF</key><key>Hand</key><key>gesture</key></keys><date>2011-02-22 16:58:45</date><changeDate>2011-02-22 16:58:45</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2007</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=1759437.1759461</url><abstract>We present a gesture recognition system for recognizing hand movements in near realtime. The system uses a infra-red time-of-flight range camera with up to 30 Hz framerate to measure 3d-surface points captured from the hand of the user. The measured data is transformed into a cloud of 3d-points after depth keying and suppression of camera noise by median filtering. Principle component analysis (PCA) is used to obtain a first crude estimate on the location and orientation of the hand. An articulated hand model is fitted to the data to refine the first estimate. The unoptimized system is able to estimate the first 7 Degrees of Freedom of the hand within 200 ms. The reconstructed hand is visualized in AVANGO/Performer and can be utilized to implement a natural man-machine interface. The work reviews relevant publications, underlines the advantages and shortcomings of the approach and provides an outlook on future improvements.</abstract><pages>247--260</pages><booktitle>Proceedings of the 3rd international conference on Computer vision/computer graphics collaboration techniques</booktitle><series>MIRAGE'07</series><publisher>Springer-Verlag</publisher><isbn>978-3-540-71456-9</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_53</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/219c4d109c0275fb875afb29483ea7c4c/riche.ma</bibsomy_id><title>Phase investigations of the Al---Ir system</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>K.M.</first><last>Axler</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>E.M.</first><last>Foltyn</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>D.E.</first><last>Peterson</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>W.B.</first><last>Hutchinson</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:riche.ma</key><key>Al_Ir_phase_diagram</key></keys><date>2011-01-27 11:26:27</date><changeDate>2011-01-27 11:26:27</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1989</year><url>http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/B759D-48GNFGM-7D/2/48eeb94bdffa0b3168d304202272e50f</url><abstract>The phase behavior of the Al---Ir system has been studied using differential thermal analysis, electron microprobe analysis, X-ray diffraction, chemical analysis and X-ray fluorescence. Our work confirms the existence of four compounds: Al9Ir2, Al3Ir, Al2.7Ir and AlIr. We also observed an additional intermetallic phase, with a stoichiometry corresponding to Al13Ir4; however, this compound exhibits a complex X-ray pattern and currently no structure has been determined.
Peritectic temperatures were determined for Al9Ir2 (900 °C), Al13Ir4 (1015 °C) and Al3Ir (1450 °C). The Al2.7Ir phase is stable to above 1450 °C, and the congruent melting temperature of AlIr is 2120 ± 20 °C. The solubility of aluminum in iridium was measured between 1085 and 1850 °C, and the maximum solid solubility was extrapolated to 18 at.% at 2058 °C. The maximum solid solubility of iridium in aluminum was measured to be less than 0.1 at.%. A phase diagram for the Al---Ir system is presented.</abstract><journal>Journal of the Less Common Metals</journal><volume>156</volume><number>1-2</number><pages>213 - 219</pages><issn>0022-5088</issn><doi>10.1016/0022-5088(89)90420-7</doi></publication><publication><id>han_54</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/212176d90012ed75f57996af0b9240d02/jaeschke</bibsomy_id><title>Cumulated gain-based evaluation of IR techniques</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kalervo</first><last>Järvelin</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Jaana</first><last>Kekäläinen</last></author></authors><keys><key>retrieval</key><key>merged:jaeschke</key><key>evaluation</key><key>ir</key><key>merged:dblp</key><key>information</key><key>dblp</key></keys><date>2009-11-03 15:41:30</date><changeDate>2014-07-28 15:57:11</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2002</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=582418</url><abstract>Modern large retrieval environments tend to overwhelm their users by their large output. Since all documents are not of equal relevance to their users, highly relevant documents should be identified and ranked first for presentation. In order to develop IR techniques in this direction, it is necessary to develop evaluation approaches and methods that credit IR methods for their ability to retrieve highly relevant documents. This can be done by extending traditional evaluation methods, that is, recall and precision based on binary relevance judgments, to graded relevance judgments. Alternatively, novel measures based on graded relevance judgments may be developed. This article proposes several novel measures that compute the cumulative gain the user obtains by examining the retrieval result up to a given ranked position. The first one accumulates the relevance scores of retrieved documents along the ranked result list. The second one is similar but applies a discount factor to the relevance scores in order to devaluate late-retrieved documents. The third one computes the relative-to-the-ideal performance of IR techniques, based on the cumulative gain they are able to yield. These novel measures are defined and discussed and their use is demonstrated in a case study using TREC data: sample system run results for 20 queries in TREC-7. As a relevance base we used novel graded relevance judgments on a four-point scale. The test results indicate that the proposed measures credit IR methods for their ability to retrieve highly relevant documents and allow testing of statistical significance of effectiveness differences. The graphs based on the measures also provide insight into the performance IR techniques and allow interpretation, for example, from the user point of view.</abstract><journal>ACM Transactions on Information Systems</journal><volume>20</volume><number>4</number><pages>422--446</pages><issn>1046-8188</issn><doi>10.1145/582415.582418</doi><publisher>ACM</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_55</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2a8ecc30f336c46935d47a8ac58cd5841/ideseditor</bibsomy_id><title>Effect of Glittering and Reflective Objects of Different
Colors to the Output Voltage-Distance Characteristics
of Sharp GP2D120 IR</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>N.S.N. Anwar</first><last>M.R. Yaacob</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>A.M.</first><last>Kassim</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:ideseditor</key><key>GP2D120_IR</key></keys><date>2012-09-17 08:20:43</date><changeDate>2012-09-17 08:20:43</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2012</year><url>http://doi.searchdl.org/01.IJEPE.3.2.23</url><abstract>This paper presents a study on the effect of glittering
and reflective objects with different colors to the output voltagedistance
characteristics of Sharp GP2D120 IR Sensor, which
operates by employing the principle of single point
triangulation. The study was conducted by using a compact
disk and plastic materials with four different colors, in which
the distance for each of them was measured by a Sharp
GP2D120 IR Sensor mounted on a constructed experimental
setup. The results obtained shows the output-voltage-distance
characteristics which indicate that; the white color plastic is
having the highest level of reflectivity, followed by gray,
transparent and black color objects, and compact disk as a
glittering object is seemed to be having the lowest level of
reflectivity.</abstract><journal>ACEEE International Journal on Electrical and Power Engineering</journal><volume>3</volume><number>2</number><pages>5</pages></publication><publication><id>han_56</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2f8c070cb738ea82a40838b1eb8257e31/hotho</bibsomy_id><title>A comparison of LSA, wordNet and PMI-IR for predicting user click behavior</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Ishwinder</first><last>Kaur</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Anthony J.</first><last>Hornof</last></author></authors><keys><key>relatedness</key><key>semantic</key><key>merged:hotho</key><key>toread</key><key>merged:ewomant</key><key>wordnet</key><key>lsa</key><key>information_scent</key><key>automated_evaluation</key></keys><date>2013-04-23 17:50:39</date><changeDate>2013-04-23 17:50:40</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2005</year><url>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/1054972.1054980</url><abstract>A predictive tool to simulate human visual search behavior would help interface designers inform and validate their design. Such a tool would benefit from a semantic component that would help predict search behavior even in the absence of exact textual matches between goal and target. This paper discusses a comparison of three semantic systems-LSA, WordNet and PMI-IR-to evaluate their performance in predicting the link that people would select given an information goal and a webpage. PMI-IR best predicted human performance as observed in a user study.</abstract><pages>51--60</pages><doi>10.1145/1054972.1054980</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the SIGCHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems</booktitle><series>CHI '05</series><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>1-58113-998-5</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_57</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2f6eddba1f2c6b7cdbfa67a0c79ae5ae8/stumme</bibsomy_id><title>Text Mining Scientific Papers: A Survey on FCA-Based Information Retrieval Research</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Jonas</first><last>Poelmans</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>DmitryI.</first><last>Ignatov</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Stijn</first><last>Viaene</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Guido</first><last>Dedene</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>SergeiO.</first><last>Kuznetsov</last></author></authors><keys><key>FCA</key><key>merged:stumme</key><key>IR</key><key>Text</key><key>SOTA</key><key>Mining</key></keys><date>2014-06-30 16:22:33</date><changeDate>2014-06-30 16:22:33</changeDate><pub-type>incollection</pub-type><year>2012</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1007/978-3-642-31488-9_22</url><abstract>Formal Concept Analysis (FCA) is an unsupervised clustering technique and many scientific papers are devoted to applying FCA in Information Retrieval (IR) research. We collected 103 papers published between 2003-2009 which mention FCA and information retrieval in the abstract, title or keywords. Using a prototype of our FCA-based toolset CORDIET, we converted the pdf-files containing the papers to plain text, indexed them with Lucene using a thesaurus containing terms related to FCA research and then created the concept lattice shown in this paper. We visualized, analyzed and explored the literature with concept lattices and discovered multiple interesting research streams in IR of which we give an extensive overview. The core contributions of this paper are the innovative application of FCA to the text mining of scientific papers and the survey of the FCA-based IR research.</abstract><volume>7377</volume><pages>273-287</pages><language>English</language><doi>10.1007/978-3-642-31488-9_22</doi><booktitle>Advances in Data Mining. Applications and Theoretical Aspects</booktitle><series>Lecture Notes in Computer Science</series><publisher>Springer Berlin Heidelberg</publisher><isbn>978-3-642-31487-2</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_58</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2151dcf2b50646cf6e372f5a31f0db314/juver</bibsomy_id><title>A substantive theory of classification for information retrieval</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Birger</first><last>Hjørland</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Karsten Nissen</first><last>Pedersen</last></author></authors><keys><key>IR</key><key>information_retrieval</key><key>algorithm</key><key>wismasys0809</key><key>classification</key><key>theory</key><key>merged:juver</key></keys><date>2008-11-09 23:37:22</date><changeDate>2008-11-09 23:37:22</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2005</year><url>http://www.emeraldinsight.com/Insight/viewPDF.jsp?Filename=html/Output/Published/EmeraldFullTextArticle/Pdf/2780610502.pdf</url><abstract>Purpose – To suggest that a theory of classification for information retrieval (IR), asked for by
Spa¨rck Jones in a 1970 paper, presupposes a full implementation of a pragmatic understanding. Part of
the Journal of Documentation celebration, “60 years of the best in information research”.
Design/methodology/approach – Literature-based conceptual analysis, taking Spa¨rck Jones as its
starting-point. Analysis involves distinctions between “positivism” and “pragmatism” and “classical”
versus Kuhnian understandings of concepts.
Findings – Classification, both manual and automatic, for retrieval benefits from drawing upon a
combination of qualitative and quantitative techniques, a consideration of theories of meaning, and the
adding of top-down approaches to IR in which divisions of labour, domains, traditions, genres,
document architectures etc. are included as analytical elements and in which specific IR algorithms are
based on the examination of specific literatures. Introduces an example illustrating the consequences
of a full implementation of a pragmatist understanding when handling homonyms.
Practical implications – Outlines how to classify from a pragmatic-philosophical point of view.
Originality/value – Provides, emphasizing a pragmatic understanding, insights of importance to
classification for retrieval, both manual and automatic.</abstract><journal>Journal of Documentation</journal><volume>61</volume><number>5</number><pages>582-597</pages></publication><publication><id>han_59</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2295f51a66f5d303d5608c831df3a97bc/gzymeri</bibsomy_id><title>Indexing and ranking in Geo-IR systems</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Bruno</first><last>Martins</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Mário J.</first><last>Silva</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Leonardo</first><last>Andrade</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:gzymeri</key><key>imported</key><key>merged:mchaves</key><key>MA</key><key>ranking</key><key>merged:dblp</key><key>indexing</key><key>GIR</key><key>dblp</key></keys><date>2012-10-17 12:26:12</date><changeDate>2012-10-17 12:26:12</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2005</year><url>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/1096985.1096993</url><abstract>This paper addresses document indexing and retrieval using geographical location. It discusses possible indexing structures and result ranking algorithms, surveying known approaches and showing how they can be combined to build an effective Geo-IR system.</abstract><pages>31--34</pages><doi>10.1145/1096985.1096993</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the 2005 workshop on Geographic information retrieval</booktitle><series>GIR '05</series><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>1-59593-165-1</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_60</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2ead23af5dfae86efd8c9732d401c17a5/riche.ma</bibsomy_id><title>Electronic origin of anomalously high shear modulus and intrinsic brittleness of fcc Ir</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Sami</first><last>Kamran</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Kuiying</first><last>Chen</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Liang</first><last>Chen</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Linruo</first><last>Zhao</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:riche.ma</key><key>Ir_brittleness</key></keys><date>2011-04-15 14:34:13</date><changeDate>2011-04-15 14:34:13</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2008</year><url>http://stacks.iop.org/0953-8984/20/i=8/a=085221</url><abstract>Through ab initio density functional theory based calculations, we find that the anomalously large shear modulus and the intrinsic brittleness of face-centred cubic (fcc) iridium (Ir) are primarily a consequence of its relatively strong bonds. Comparative analysis of the bond order, which dictates the bond strength, the localization of the valence electrons and the elastic constants of Ir and a selection of fcc metals allows us to rationalize the peculiarities of Ir in terms of its strong and directional bonds. Furthermore, the similarities between the failures of Al and Ir are suggested to reflect the resemblance existing between the angular features of their bonds.</abstract><journal>Journal of Physics: Condensed Matter</journal><volume>20</volume><number>8</number><pages>085221</pages></publication><publication><id>han_61</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/286e07dc5fda6859a25baa524f2d50f83/jrennstich</bibsomy_id><title>What is History in International Relations?</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>J.M.</first><last>Hobson</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>G.</first><last>Lawson</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:jrennstich</key><key>ir</key><key>history</key><key>theory</key></keys><date>2010-03-02 17:25:53</date><changeDate>2010-03-02 17:26:46</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2008</year><url /><abstract>Discussion of role of history in US and European traditions of IR.</abstract><journal>Millennium</journal><volume>37</volume><number>2</number><pages>415--435</pages></publication><publication><id>han_62</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/283440d8067f1d07f7d8b566f927c6cf7/miki</bibsomy_id><title>The early phases of galaxy clusters formation in IR: coupling
  hydrodynamical simulations with GRASIL3D</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Gian Luigi</first><last>Granato</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Cinthia</first><last>Ragone-Figueroa</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Rosa</first><last>Dominguez-Tenreiro</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Aura</first><last>Obreja</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Stefano</first><last>Borgani</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Gabriella</first><last>De Lucia</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Giuseppe</first><last>Murante</last></author></authors><keys><key>transfer</key><key>galaxy</key><key>radiative</key><key>formation</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>clusters</key></keys><date>2014-12-22 07:13:34</date><changeDate>2014-12-22 07:13:34</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2014</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1412.6105</url><note>cite arxiv:1412.6105Comment: 12 pages, 10 figures, submitted to MNRAS</note><abstract>We compute and study the infrared and sub-mm properties of high redshift
(z&gt;1) simulated clusters and proto-clusters, by coupling the results of a large
set of hydro-dynamical zoom-in simulations including active galactic nuclei
(AGN) feedback (Ragone-Figueroa et al. 2013), with the recently developed
radiative transfer code GRASIL3D (Dominguez-Tenreiro et al. 2014), which
accounts for the effect of dust reprocessing in an arbitrary geometry, and we
customized for the present purpose. While this field is in its infancy from the
observational point of view, a rapid development is expected in the near
future, thanks to observations performed in the far IR and sub-mm bands.
Notably, we find that in this spectral regime our prediction are little
affected by the assumption required by this post-processing, and the emission
is mostly powered by star formation rather than accretion onto super massive
black hole (SMBH). The comparison with the little observational information
available so far, highlights that the simulated cluster regions never attain
the impressive star formation rates suggested by these observations. This
problem becomes more intriguing taking into account that the brightest cluster
galaxies (BCGs) in the same simulations turns out to be too massive
(Ragone-Figueroa et al. 2013). It seems that the interplay between the feedback
schemes and the starformation model should be revised, possibly incorporating a
positive feedback mode.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_63</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2465b49ed8a4fb208afba29e453541a3b/datentaste</bibsomy_id><title>Measuring Effectiveness of Geographic IR Systems in Digital Libraries</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Damien</first><last>Palacio</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Guillaume</first><last>Cabanac</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Christian</first><last>Sallaberry</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Gilles</first><last>Hubert</last></author></authors><keys><key>Geo</key><key>ECDL2011</key><key>InformationRetrieval</key><key>IR</key><key>merged:datentaste</key></keys><date>2010-10-14 22:17:01</date><changeDate>2010-10-14 22:17:01</changeDate><pub-type>incollection</pub-type><year>2010</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1007/978-3-642-15464-5_34</url><note>10.1007/978-3-642-15464-5\_34</note><abstract>Common search engines process users’ queries (i.e., information needs) by retrieving documents from pre-built term-based indexes. For digital libraries, such approaches are limited regarding particular contexts, such as specialized collections (e.g., cultural heritage collections) or specific retrieval criteria (e.g., multidimensional criteria). In this paper, we consider Information Retrieval systems exploiting geographic dimensions: spatial, temporal, and topical dimensions. Our contribution is twofold as we propose a Geographic Information Retrieval system evaluation framework and test the following hypothesis: combining spatial and temporal dimensions along with the topical dimension improves the effectiveness of Information Retrieval systems.</abstract><volume>6273</volume><pages>340--351</pages><booktitle>Research and Advanced Technology for Digital Libraries</booktitle><series>Lecture Notes in Computer Science</series><publisher>Springer Berlin / Heidelberg</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_64</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/23d2a2212b1227e11db2535e14f1231ad/ctqmat</bibsomy_id><title>Indirect chiral magnetic exchange through Dzyaloshinskii–Moriya-enhanced RKKY interactions in manganese oxide chains on Ir(100)</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Martin</first><last>Schmitt</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Paolo</first><last>Moras</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Gustav</first><last>Bihlmayer</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Ryan</first><last>Cotsakis</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Matthias</first><last>Vogt</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Jeannette</first><last>Kemmer</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Abderrezak</first><last>Belabbes</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Polina M.</first><last>Sheverdyaeva</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Asish K.</first><last>Kundu</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Carlo</first><last>Carbone</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>Stefan</first><last>Blügel</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>Matthias</first><last>Bode</last></author></authors><keys><key>b</key><key>merged:ctqmat</key></keys><date>2019-08-22 10:51:14</date><changeDate>2019-08-22 10:51:14</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2019</year><url>https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-019-10515-3</url><abstract>Localized electron spins can couple magnetically via the Ruderman–Kittel–Kasuya–Yosida interaction even if their wave functions lack direct overlap. Theory predicts that spin–orbit scattering leads to a Dzyaloshinskii–Moriya type enhancement of this indirect exchange interaction, giving rise to chiral exchange terms. Here we present a combined spin-polarized scanning tunneling microscopy, angle-resolved photoemission, and density functional theory study of MnO2 chains on Ir(100). Whereas we find antiferromagnetic Mn–Mn coupling along the chain, the inter-chain coupling across the non-magnetic Ir substrate turns out to be chiral with a 120° rotation between adjacent MnO2 chains. Calculations reveal that the Dzyaloshinskii–Moriya interaction results in spin spirals with a periodicity in agreement with experiment. Our findings confirm the existence of indirect chiral magnetic exchange, potentially giving rise to exotic phenomena, such as chiral spin-liquid states in spin ice systems or the emergence of new quasiparticles.</abstract><journal>Nature Communications</journal><volume>10</volume><number>1</number><pages>2610--</pages><issn>20411723</issn><doi>10.1038/s41467-019-10515-3</doi></publication><publication><id>han_65</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/26f5153f8f69725a188722c7e8e5f97b8/psschulz</bibsomy_id><title>Infrared Spectroscopy of a Wilkinson Catalyst in a Room-Temperature
   Ionic Liquid</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Johannes</first><last>Kiefer</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Katharina</first><last>Obert</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Simone</first><last>Himmler</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Peter S.</first><last>Schulz</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Peter</first><last>Wasserscheid</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Alfred</first><last>Leipertz</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:psschulz</key><key>IR</key></keys><date>2009-06-29 17:55:14</date><changeDate>2009-06-29 17:55:15</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>{2008}</year><url /><abstract>Homogeneous catalysis in room-temperature ionic liquids (ILs)
   constitutes a most interesting field of research with high potential in
   technical applications. As concerns the hydrogenation of unsaturated
   hydrocarbons, Wilkinson's compound RhCl(PPh3)(3) represents a catalyst
   that provides high selectivity and activity. Herein, we demonstrate the
   application of infrared spectroscopy to the quantitative analysis of
   the Wilkinson catalyst in the IL 1-ethyl-3-methylimidazolium acetate
   (EMIMOAc). Our study demonstrates for the first time the
   quantitative, accurate and reproducible determination of the
   concentration of a rhodium catalyst by means of IR spectroscopy and,
   moreover, allows the investigation of intermolecular interactions.
   Spectral features, located mainly in the fingerprint region of the IR
   spectrum, are identified revealing the influence of the dissolved
   catalyst on the IL's vibrational structure. In particular, the
   ring-bending mode of the imidazolium ring shows a frequency shift as a
   function of catalyst concentration, probably due to hydrogen-bond
   formation between the IL cation and the Rh complex. The results show
   the potential of IR spectroscopy both for application as a quick
   process control technology in catalytic processes and as a toot for
   better understanding of IL-catalyst interactions.</abstract><journal>CHEMPHYSCHEM</journal><volume>9</volume><number>15</number><pages>2207-2213</pages><issn>1439-4235</issn><doi>10.1002/cphc.200800450</doi></publication><publication><id>han_66</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/220760423ec4d8ff5553427e8677850e7/sasha-markov</bibsomy_id><title>SpinâOrbit Coupling and Outer-Core Correlation Effects in Ir- and Pt-Catalyzed CâH Activation</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kejuan</first><last>Chen</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Guiling</first><last>Zhang</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Hui</first><last>Chen</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Jiannian</first><last>Yao</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>David</first><last>Danovich</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Sason</first><last>Shaik</last></author></authors><keys><key>iridium</key><key>platinum</key><key>correlation</key><key>merged:sasha-markov</key><key>C-H-activation</key><key>spin-orbit</key></keys><date>2015-07-29 11:26:47</date><changeDate>2015-07-29 11:26:47</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2012</year><url>/brokenurl#         http://dx.doi.org/10.1021/ct3000537    </url><abstract>The transition metal-dependent spinâorbit coupling (SOC) and outer-core (5s5p) correlation effects in Ir- and Pt-catalyzed CâH activation processes are studied here using high level ab initio computations. The catalysts involve complexes with oxidation states: Ir(I), Ir(III), Pt(0), and Pt(II). It is demonstrated that for these heavy 5d transition metal-containing systems, the SOC effect and outer-core correlation effect on CâH activation are up to the order of â¼1 kcal/mol, and should be included if chemical accuracy is aimed. The interesting trends in our studied systems are: (1) the SOC effect consistently increases the CâH activation barriers and is apparently larger in higher oxidation states (Pt(II) and Ir(III)) than in low-oxidation states (Pt(0) and Ir(I)); and (2) the magnitude of outer-core (5s5p) correlation effects is larger in less coordinate-saturated system. The effect of basis set on the outer-core correlation correction is significant; larger basis sets tend to increase the CâH activation barriers.</abstract><journal>Journal of Chemical Theory and Computation</journal><volume>8</volume><number>5</number><pages>1641-1645</pages><doi>10.1021/ct3000537</doi></publication><publication><id>han_67</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/221356685ee7e5b69a6562fdf57e9db29/achraf.elghazi</bibsomy_id><title>Content-Aware DataGuides: Interleaving IR and DB Indexing Techniques for Efficient Retrieval of Textual XML Data</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Felix</first><last>Weigel</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Holger</first><last>Meuss</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>François</first><last>Bry</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Klaus U.</first><last>Schulz</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:achraf.elghazi</key></keys><date>2009-01-09 21:08:17</date><changeDate>2009-01-09 21:08:17</changeDate><pub-type>inbook</pub-type><year>2004</year><url>http://www.springerlink.com/content/pugmdl3yn1ug82c5</url><abstract>Not only since the advent of XML, many applications call for e.cient structured document retrieval, challenging both Information Retrieval (IR) and database (DB) research. Most approaches combining indexing techniques from both .elds still separate path and content matching, merging the hits in an expensive join. This paper shows that retrieval is signi.cantly accelerated by processing text and structure simultaneously. The Content-Aware DataGuide (CADG) interleaves IR and DB indexing techniques to minimize path matching and suppress joins at query time, also saving needless I/O operations during retrieval. Extensive experiments prove the CADG to outperform the DataGuide 11,14 by a factor 5 to 200 on average. For structurally unselective queries, it is over 400 times faster than the DataGuide. The best results were achieved on large collections of heterogeneously structured textual documents.</abstract><journal>Advances in Information Retrieval</journal><pages>378--393</pages></publication><publication><id>han_68</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2167658db9b09b071a2b8cfb420f20be0/tillk</bibsomy_id><title>The relationship between IR effectiveness measures and user satisfaction</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Azzah</first><last>Al-Maskari</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Mark</first><last>Sanderson</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Paul</first><last>Clough</last></author></authors><keys><key>suchkiste</key><key>effectiveness</key><key>ir</key><key>merged:dblp</key><key>merged:tillk</key><key>merged:griesbau</key><key>ungelesen</key><key>dblp</key><key>retrieval</key><key>system</key><key>measures</key><key>relationship</key><key>evaluation</key><key>information</key></keys><date>2009-02-23 19:01:20</date><changeDate>2009-02-23 19:01:20</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2007</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=1277902</url><abstract>This paper presents an experimental study of users assessing the quality of Google web search results. In particular we look at how users’ satisfaction correlates with the effectiveness of Google as quantified by IR measures such as precision and the suite of Cumulative Gain measures (CG, DCG, NDCG). Results indicate strong correlation between users’ satisfaction, CG and precision, moderate correlation with DCG, with perhaps surprisingly negligible correlation with NDCG. The reasons for the low correlation with NDCG are examined.</abstract><pages>773--774</pages><doi>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/1277741.1277902</doi><booktitle>SIGIR '07: Proceedings of the 30th annual international ACM SIGIR conference on Research and development in information retrieval</booktitle><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>978-1-59593-597-7</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_69</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2da55dd030ab2402d66e6847d93d3c60f/heh15</bibsomy_id><title>Origins Space Telescope: predictions for far-IR spectroscopic surveys</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Matteo</first><last>Bonato</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Gianfranco</first><last>De Zotti</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>David</first><last>Leisawitz</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Mattia</first><last>Negrello</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Marcella</first><last>Massardi</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Ivano</first><last>Baronchelli</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Zhen-Yi</first><last>Cai</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Charles M.</first><last>Bradford</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Alexandra</first><last>Pope</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Eric J.</first><last>Murphy</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>Lee</first><last>Armus</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>Asantha</first><last>Cooray</last></author></authors><keys><key>infraed-telescope</key><key>merged:heh15</key><key>OST</key></keys><date>2019-03-05 15:14:27</date><changeDate>2019-03-05 15:14:27</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2019</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1903.00946</url><note>cite arxiv:1903.00946Comment: 24 pages, 20 figures, 2 tables, accepted for publication in PASA</note><abstract>We illustrate the extraordinary potential of the (far-IR) Origins Survey
Spectrometer (OSS) on board the Origins Space Telescope (OST) to address a
variety of open issues on the co-evolution of galaxies and AGNs. We present
predictions for blind surveys, each of 1000 h, with different mapped areas (a
shallow survey covering an area of 10 deg$^2$ and a deep survey of 1
deg$^2$) and two different concepts of the OST/OSS: with a 5.9 m telescope
(Concept 2, our reference configuration) and with a 9.1 m telescope (Concept 1,
previous configuration). In 1000 h, surveys with the reference concept will
detect from $1.9 10^6$ to $8.7 10^6$ lines from
$4.8 10^5$-$2.7 10^6$ star-forming galaxies and from
$1.4 10^4$ to $3.8 10^4$ lines from $1.3
10^4$-$3.5 10^4$ AGNs. The shallow survey will detect
substantially more sources than the deep one; the advantage of the latter in
pushing detections to lower luminosities/higher redshifts turns out to be quite
limited. The OST/OSS will reach, in the same observing time, line fluxes more
than one order of magnitude fainter than the SPICA/SMI and will cover a much
broader redshift range. In particular it will detect tens of thousands of
galaxies at $z 5$, beyond the reach of that instrument. The polycyclic
aromatic hydrocarbons lines are potentially bright enough to allow the
detection of hundreds of thousands of star-forming galaxies up to $z 8.5$,
i.e. all the way through the re-ionization epoch. The proposed surveys will
allow us to explore the galaxy-AGN co-evolution up to $z5.5-6$ with very
good statistics. OST Concept 1 does not offer significant advantages for the
scientific goals presented here.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_70</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/28f08a3cccb59e0d55aed34fac82800e9/thesaiorg</bibsomy_id><title>Simulation of a WiMAX network to evaluate the performance of MAC IEEE 802.16 during the IR phase of Network Entry and Initialization</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Manu G V</first><last>Namratha M Pradeep</last></author></authors><keys><key>Circular</key><key>computing;</key><key>Model;</key><key>Backoff</key><key>delay;</key><key>Markov</key><key>Pervasive</key><key>Ubiquitous</key><key>merged:thesaiorg</key><key>topology;</key><key>WiMAX</key><key>Linear</key></keys><date>2014-02-21 08:00:08</date><changeDate>2014-02-21 08:00:08</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2013</year><url>http://ijacsa.thesai.org/</url><abstract>Pervasive Computing is also called as Ubiquitous Computing, which means “being present everywhere at once” or “constantly encountered”. The main idea behind making these pervasive computing systems is that these systems improve living by performing computations on their own, without having to be monitored by anyone. These systems are targeted to become invisible to the user i.e., they perform their tasks without the user’s knowledge. 
To achieve this environment, the underlying requirement is a Network. One of the biggest constraints in achieving this environment is the “Last Mile” problem. It refers to the last leg of delivering connectivity from a communications provider to a customer. In recent years there has been increasing interest shown in wireless technologies for subscriber access, as an alternative to traditional twisted-pair local loop. 
WiMAX, Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a Telecommunications technology that provides wireless transmission of data and is based on the IEEE 802.16 standard (also called Broadband Wireless Access). 802.16 uses paired radio channels Up Link Channel (UL) and Down Link Channel (DL) for establishing a communication between Base Station (BS) and Subscriber Station (SS). When a SS wants to establish connectivity with a BS it goes through the Network Entry and Initialization procedure of which Initial Ranging (IR) is a very important part. IR is the process of acquiring the correct timing offset and power adjustments such that the SS’s transmissions are aligned to maintain the UL connection with the BS. All the SS’s of a BS will compete for the contention slots for their network entry. Whenever the SS has to transmit the request packets it performs the Truncated Binary Exponential Backoff procedure. This method is the contention resolution procedure used in IEEE 802.16 networks. 
Our focus here was to simulate a WiMAX network so as to evaluate the performance of MAC IEEE 802.16 during the IR phase of Network Entry and Initialization. We have used Network Simulator-2 (NS-2) for our simulation purposes. We are using WiMAX “patch” which simulates the PHY and the MAC features of a WiMAX network. We have evaluated the performance of MAC IEEE 802.16 for various topologies.</abstract><journal>International Journal of Advanced Computer Science and Applications(IJACSA)</journal><volume>4</volume><number>3</number></publication><publication><id>han_71</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2eb658999f48a8aa7412a6dc528ba3a27/jrennstich</bibsomy_id><title>The Sociology of a Not so International Discipline: American and European Developments in International Relations.</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Ole</first><last>Wæver</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:jrennstich</key><key>ir</key><key>text</key><key>teaching</key></keys><date>2010-03-02 17:25:53</date><changeDate>2010-03-02 17:26:54</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1998</year><url /><abstract>The international relations (IR) discipline is dominated by the American research community. Data about publication patterns in leading journals document this situation as well as a variance in theoretical orientations. IR is conducted differently in different places. The main patterns are explained through a sociology of science model that emphasizes the different nine- teen th-century histories of the state, the early format of social science, and the institutionalized delineation among the different social sciences. The internal social and intellectual structure of American IR is two-tiered, with relatively independent subfields and a top layer defined by access to the leading journals (on which IR, in contrast to some social sciences, has a high consensus). The famous successive 'great debates' serve an important function by letting lead theorists focus and structure the whole discipline. IR in France, Germany, and the United Kingdom has historically been structured differently, often with power vested more locally. American IR now moves in a direction that undermines its global hegemony. The widespread turn to rational choice privileges a reintegration (and status-wise rehabilitation) with the rest of political science over attention to JR practices elsewhere. This rationalistic turn is alien to Europeans, both because their IR is generally closer to sociology, philosophy, and anthropology, and because the liberal ontological premises of rational choice are less fitting to European societies. Simultaneously, European IR is beginning to break the local power bastions and establish independent research communities at a national or, increasingly, a European level. As American IR turns from global hegemony to national professionalization, IR becomes more pluralistic.</abstract><journal>International Organization</journal><volume>52</volume><number>4</number><pages>687--727</pages><issn>00208183</issn></publication><publication><id>han_72</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2b2a5592435b3d28cc2ee8bd2a518b62d/bretschneider_m</bibsomy_id><title>A Series of Pyrene-Substituted Silicon Phthalocyanines as Near-IR Sensitizers in Organic Ternary Solar Cells</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Lili</first><last>Ke</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Jie</first><last>Min</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Matthias</first><last>Adam</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Nicola</first><last>Gasparini</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Yi</first><last>Hou</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>J. Darío</first><last>Perea</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Wei</first><last>Chen</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Hong</first><last>Zhang</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Stefanie</first><last>Fladischer</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Anna-Chiara</first><last>Sale</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>Erdmann</first><last>Spiecker</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>Rik R.</first><last>Tykwinski</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>Christoph J.</first><last>Brabec</last></author><author><nr>14</nr><first>Tayebeh</first><last>Ameri</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:bretschneider_m</key><key>ternary</key><key>organic</key></keys><date>2016-08-19 10:03:50</date><changeDate>2016-08-19 10:03:50</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2016</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1002/aenm.201502355</url><abstract>An attractive method to broaden the absorption bandwidth of polymer/fullerene-based bulk heterojunction (BHJ) solar cells is to blend near infrared (near-IR) sensitizers into the host system. Axial substitution of silicon phthalocyanines (Pcs) opens a possibility to modify the chemical, thermodynamic, electronic, and optical properties. Different axial substitutions are already designed to modify the thermodynamic properties of Pcs, but the impact of extending the π-conjugation of the axial ligand on the opto-electronic properties, as a function of the length of the alkyl spacer, has not been investigated yet. For this purpose, a novel series of pyrene-substituted silicon phthalocyanines (SiPc-Pys) with varying lengths of alkyl chain tethers are synthesized. The UV–vis and external quantum efficiency (EQE) results exhibit an efficient near IR sensitization up to 800 nm, clearly establishing the impact of the pyrene substitution. This yields an increase of over 20% in the short circuit current density (J
SC) and over 50% in the power conversion efficiency (PCE) for the dye-sensitized ternary device. Charge generation, transport properties, and microstructure are studied using different advanced technologies. Remarkably, these results provide guidance for the diverse and judicious selection of dye sensitizers to overcome the absorption limitation and achieve high efficiency ternary solar cells.</abstract><journal>Advanced Energy Materials</journal><volume>6</volume><number>7</number><pages>n/a--n/a</pages><issn>1614-6840</issn><doi>10.1002/aenm.201502355</doi></publication><publication><id>han_73</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2587324ee0c3b1b3a4dda0b160f8800f7/abelion</bibsomy_id><title>Dirac fermions in the heavy-fermion superconductors Ce(Co,Rh,Ir)In$_5$</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kent R.</first><last>Shirer</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Yan</first><last>Sun</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Maja D.</first><last>Bachmann</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Carsten</first><last>Putzke</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Toni</first><last>Helm</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Laurel E.</first><last>Winter</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Fedor F.</first><last>Balakirev</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Ross D.</first><last>McDonald</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>James G.</first><last>Analytis</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Nityan L.</first><last>Nair</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>Eric D.</first><last>Bauer</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>Filip</first><last>Ronning</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>Claudia</first><last>Felser</last></author><author><nr>14</nr><first>Tobias</first><last>Meng</last></author><author><nr>15</nr><first>Binghai</first><last>Yan</last></author><author><nr>16</nr><first>Philip J. W.</first><last>Moll</last></author></authors><keys><key>kondo</key><key>merged:abelion</key><key>heavy-fermion</key><key>dirac</key></keys><date>2018-08-02 06:24:12</date><changeDate>2018-08-02 06:24:12</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2018</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1808.00403</url><note>cite arxiv:1808.00403</note><abstract>The Ce(Co,Rh,Ir)In$_5$ family of ``Ce-115'' materials hosts an abundance of
correlated electron behavior, including heavy-fermion physics, magnetism,
superconductivity and nematicity. The complicated behavior of these entangled
phenomena leads to a variety of exotic physical properties, which, despite the
seemingly simple crystal structure of these compounds, remain poorly
understood. It is generally accepted that the interplay between the itinerant
and local character of Ce-$4f$ electrons is the key to their exotic behavior.
Here, we report theoretical evidence that the Ce-115 materials are also
topological semi-metals, with Dirac fermions around well-separated nodes. Dirac
nodes in each compound are present on the $\Gamma-Z$ plane close to the Fermi
level. As the Dirac bands are derived from In-orbitals, they occur in all
family members irrespective of the transition metal (Co,Rh,Ir). We present the
expected Fermi-arc surface state patterns and show the close proximity of a
topological Lifshitz transition, which possibly explains the high field physics
of Ce-115 materials. Experimentally, we highlight the surprising similarity of
Ce(Co,Rh,Ir)In$_5$ in high magnetic fields, despite the distinctly different
states of the Ce-$4f$ electrons. These results raise questions about the role
Dirac fermions play in exotic transport behavior, and we propose this class of
materials as a prime candidate for unconventional topological
superconductivity.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_74</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/242031598526676c9798f1210d9cf74cb/iswc2007</bibsomy_id><title>Semplore: An IR Approach to Scalable Hybrid Query of Semantic Web Data</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Lei</first><last>Zhang</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>QiaoLing</first><last>Liu</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Jie</first><last>Zhang</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Haofen</first><last>Wang</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Yue</first><last>Pan</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Yong</first><last>Yu</last></author></authors><keys><key>datum</key><key>scalable</key><key>semantic</key><key>approach</key><key>iswc</key><key>semantic_web</key><key>merged:iswc2007</key><key>query</key><key>ir</key><key>research_13</key><key>web</key><key>2007</key><key>hybrid</key><key>data_management</key><key>application_software</key></keys><date>2007-11-07 19:13:58</date><changeDate>2007-11-07 19:14:15</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2007</year><url>http://iswc2007.semanticweb.org/papers/645.pdf</url><abstract>As an extension to the current Web, Semantic Web will not only contain structured data with machine understandable semantics but also textual information.  While structured queries can be used to find information more precisely on the Semantic Web, keyword searches are still needed to help exploit textual information.  It thus becomes very important that we can combine precise structured queries with imprecise keyword searches to have a hybrid query capability. In addition, due to the huge volume of information on the Semantic Web, the hybrid query must be processed in a very scalable way. In this paper, we define such a hybrid query capability that combines unary tree-shaped structured queries with keyword searches. We show how existing information retrieval (IR) index structures and functions can be reused to index semantic web data and its textual information, and how the hybrid query is evaluated on the index structure using IR engines in an efficient and scalable manner. We implemented this IR approach in an engine called Semplore. Comprehensive experiments on its performance show that it is a promising approach. It leads us to believe that it may be possible to evolve current web search engines to query and search the Semantic Web. Finally, we breifly describe how Semplore is used for searching Wikipedia and an IBM customer's product information.</abstract><volume>4825</volume><pages>645--658</pages><booktitle>Proceedings of the 6th International Semantic Web Conference and 2nd Asian Semantic Web Conference (ISWC/ASWC2007), Busan, South Korea</booktitle><series>LNCS</series><publisher>Springer Verlag</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_75</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/22854ca9b3ec4c3dee63c8b4d4b8023da/ijtsrd</bibsomy_id><title>Endothelial Nitric Oxide Synthase T786C Gene Polymorphism TT Genotype is Associated with High Nitric Oxide Levels and Low HOMA IR Levels in Coronary Artery Disease Patients</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Namrata Bhutani | Deepak Tangadi | Neha</first><last>Bhutani</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:ijtsrd</key><key>Biochemistry</key></keys><date>2020-07-16 11:11:48</date><changeDate>2020-07-16 11:11:48</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2020</year><url>https://www.ijtsrd.com/biological-science/biochemistry/31317/endothelial-nitric-oxide-synthase-t786c-gene-polymorphism-tt-genotype-is-associated-with-high-nitric-oxide-levels-and-low-homair-levels-in-coronary-artery-disease-patients/namrata-bhutani</url><abstract>BACKGROUND Data suggest eNOS 786T C gene polymorphism is distinct in specific population group, ethnicity and geographic region and perhaps this genetic variability might produce different results on exposure to various environmental factors 9 14. Besides there is hardly any data available in Indian population. Sofurther research is needed to explore the complex interaction between environmental factors and eNOS 786T C gene polymorphism in susceptibility to insulin resistance in patients with CAD in Indian population.AIM This study aimed to study the association of Insulin Resistance, Nitric Oxide and intergenotypic variation of endothelial Nitric Oxide Synthase T786C gene polymorphism among coronary artery disease subjects. METHODOLOGY This study consisted of 60 adult patients of with documented CAD and 60 age and sex matched healthy subjects as controls.Fasting Serum Insulin was measured by ELISA,fasting Serum nitric oxide by modified Griess reaction and fasting plasma glucose on fully automated chemistry analyzer Hitachi 902 HOMA IR was calculated mathematically by using formula given by Matthew et al. The eNOS gene loci was amplified by using PCR and by RFLP. A p value 0.05 was considered significant. Statistical analysis was performed with the help of SPSS version.. RESULTS Intergenotypic levels of nitric oxide were significantly lower in TC genotype than TT both in study as well as control groups. Also, TC genotype showed significantly higher HOMA IR levels as compared to TT genotype in both study as well as control group. Moreover, CC genotype could not be found in both cases and control groups..Thus, TT genotype may have a protective role in development of insulin resistance and coronary artery disease as seen by high Nitric Oxide levels and low HOMA IR levels in TT genotype than TC genotypes in both case as well as control groups.CONCLUSIONS Endothelial nitric oxide synthase t786c gene polymorphism tt genotype is associated with high nitric oxide levels and low homa ir levels in coronary artery disease patients. Namrata Bhutani | Deepak Tangadi | Neha Bhutani "Endothelial Nitric Oxide Synthase (T786C) Gene Polymorphism TT Genotype is Associated with High Nitric Oxide Levels and Low HOMA-IR Levels in Coronary Artery Disease Patients" Published in International Journal of Trend in Scientific Research and Development (ijtsrd), ISSN: 2456-6470, Volume-4 | Issue-4 , June 2020, URL: https://www.ijtsrd.com/papers/ijtsrd31317.pdf Paper Url :https://www.ijtsrd.com/biological-science/biochemistry/31317/endothelial-nitric-oxide-synthase-t786c-gene-polymorphism-tt-genotype-is-associated-with-high-nitric-oxide-levels-and-low-homair-levels-in-coronary-artery-disease-patients/namrata-bhutani</abstract><journal>International Journal of Trend in Scientific Research and Development</journal><volume>4</volume><number>4</number><pages>909-916</pages><language>English</language><issn>2456-6470</issn></publication><publication><id>han_76</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/288c5089db0cca9215edf0f7c87d3c3ad/hertel-group</bibsomy_id><title>(Invited) Charge-Localization in Doped Semiconducting Carbon Nanotubes Revealed By IR- and EPR Spectroscopy</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Klaus H</first><last>Eckstein</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Michael</first><last>Auth</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Florian</first><last>Oberndorfer</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Friedrich</first><last>Schoeppler</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Andreas</first><last>Sperlich</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Vladimir</first><last>Dyakonov</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Tobias</first><last>Hertel</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:hertel-group</key><key>doping</key><key>swnt</key></keys><date>2021-01-14 14:47:25</date><changeDate>2021-01-14 14:47:25</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2020</year><url>https://doi.org/10.1149/ma2020-017717mtgabs</url><abstract>IR and EPR spectroscopic investigations of redox- p-doped semiconducting (6,5) single-wall carbon nanotubes (s-SWNTs) were used to study carrier localization and delocalization from low- up to degenerate doping levels. At low carrier concentrations, the analysis of IR-intraband transitions as well as the appearance of a doping-induced vibrational D-band anti-resonance, point to charge-localization on the few nm length-scale. Moreover, the rise of a spin 1/2 signal in EPR closely tracks the increase of the doping level, supporting the notion of charge-localization at low carrier concentrations. At doping levels exceeding 0.1 nm-1, EPR data as well as intra- and D-band absorption in the IR point to antiferromagnetic coupling between surplus charge carriers becoming dominant. These results are expected to be relevant for field- or redox-chemical doping of s-SWNTs in any polarizable, heterogeneous environment.</abstract><journal>ECS Meeting Abstracts</journal><volume>MA2020-01</volume><number>7</number><pages>717--717</pages><doi>10.1149/ma2020-017717mtgabs</doi><publisher>The Electrochemical Society</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_77</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2adf51572c23179b2365edd05bdf14578/kweiand</bibsomy_id><title>Comparing XML-IR Query Formation Interfaces</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Alan</first><last>Woodley</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Shlomo</first><last>Geva</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Sylvia Lauretta</first><last>Edwards</last></author></authors><keys><key>IR,</key><key>Keyword</key><key>Search</key><key>Querying,</key><key>Search,</key><key>Empirical,</key><key>Language</key><key>Natural</key><key>XML,</key><key>merged:kweiand</key></keys><date>2010-05-13 11:34:37</date><changeDate>2010-05-13 11:34:41</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2007</year><url /><abstract>Abstract XML information retrieval (XML-IR) systems differ from traditional information retrieval systems by using structure of XML documents to retrieve more specific units of information than the documents themselves. Users interact with XML-IR systems via structured queries that express their content and structural requirements. Historically, it has been common belief within the XML-IR community that structured queries will perform better than traditional keyword-only queries. However, recent system-orientated analysis has show that this assumption may be incorrect when system performance is averaged over a set of queries. Here, we test this assumption with users via a simulated work task experiment. We compare a keyword only interface with two user friendly XML-IR interfaces: NLPX, a natural language interface and Bricks, a query-bytemplate interface. This is the first time that a XML-IR natural language interface has been tested in user experiments. We compare the retrieval performance of all three interfaces and the usability of the two structured interfaces. Our results correspond to those of the system-orientated evaluation and indicate that structured queries do not aid retrieval performance. They also show that in terms of retrieval performance and usability the structured interfaces are comparable.</abstract><pages>64--71</pages><booktitle>Australian Journal of Intelligent Information Processing Systems</booktitle></publication><publication><id>han_78</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/289845b1c61374e452312444cf926a340/ak-engel-uniwue</bibsomy_id><title>Time-resolved photoelectron spectroscopy of IR-driven electron dynamics in a charge transfer model system</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Mirjam</first><last>Falge</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Friedrich Georg</first><last>Frobel</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Volker</first><last>Engel</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Stefanie</first><last>Gräfe</last></author></authors><keys><key>myown</key><key>merged:ak-engel-uniwue</key></keys><date>2017-11-06 11:49:57</date><changeDate>2017-11-06 11:55:01</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1039/C7CP01832K</url><abstract>If the adiabatic approximation is valid, electrons smoothly adapt to molecular geometry changes. In contrast, as a characteristic of diabatic dynamics, the electron density does not follow the nuclear motion. Recently, we have shown that the asymmetry in time-resolved photoelectron spectra serves as a tool to distinguish between these dynamics Falge et al., J. Phys. Chem. Lett., 2012, 3, 2617. Here, we investigate the influence of an additional, moderately intense infrared (IR) laser field, as often applied in attosecond time-resolved experiments, on such asymmetries. This is done using a simple model for coupled electronic-nuclear motion. We calculate time-resolved photoelectron spectra and their asymmetries and demonstrate that the spectra directly map the bound electron-nuclear dynamics. From the asymmetries, we can trace the IR field-induced population transfer and both the field-driven and intrinsic (non-)adiabatic dynamics. This holds true when considering superposition states accompanied by electronic coherences. The latter are observable in the asymmetries for sufficiently short XUV pulses to coherently probe the coupled states. It is thus documented that the asymmetry is a measure for phases in bound electron wave packets and non-adiabatic dynamics.</abstract><journal>Phys. Chem. Chem. Phys.</journal><volume>19</volume><number>30</number><pages>19683-19690</pages><doi>10.1039/C7CP01832K</doi><publisher>The Royal Society of Chemistry</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_79</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/279e0fe073919d3aff5bf82f55a4acdd5/aho</bibsomy_id><title>Collaborative information retrieval: Toward a social informatics view of IR interaction</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Murat</first><last>Karamuftuoglu</last></author></authors><keys><key>information-retrieval</key><key>merged:brusilovsky</key><key>collaboration</key><key>merged:aho</key><key>collaboration,</key></keys><date>2018-03-19 12:24:51</date><changeDate>2018-03-19 12:24:51</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1998</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1002/(sici)1097-4571(1998)49:12%3C1070::aid-asi3%3E3.0.co;2-s</url><abstract>This article attempts to lay down theoretical groundwork for information retrieval (IR) that involves the combined efforts of several users. It is argued that the fundamental intellectual problems of IR are the production and consumption of knowledge. Knowledge production is fundamentally a collaborative labor, which is deeply embedded in the practices of a community of participants constituting a domain. The current technological advances in networked systems make the intertextual and intersubjective nature of meaning production and communication readily visible by merging various heterogeneous media into the homogenizing framework of the digital medium. Collaborative IR as envisaged in this article would be based on the ethos of voluntary cooperation to facilitate free exchange of ideas and stimulate creativity. What sorts of functionalities can be expected in a Collaborative IR system are illustrated with the help of some examples of collaborative systems and services from various domains. \copyright 1998 John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc.</abstract><journal>Journal of the American Society for Information Science</journal><volume>49</volume><number>12</number><pages>1070--1080</pages><issn>1097-4571</issn><doi>10.1002/(sici)1097-4571(1998)49:12%3C1070::aid-asi3%3E3.0.co;2-s</doi><publisher>John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc.</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_80</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2ffbf19e3b1380f39246bb79dfe5cbc27/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Predicting Future Space Near-IR Grism Surveys using the WFC3 Infrared
  Spectroscopic Parallels Survey</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>James W.</first><last>Colbert</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Harry</first><last>Teplitz</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Hakim</first><last>Atek</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Andrew</first><last>Bunker</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Marc</first><last>Rafelski</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Nathaniel</first><last>Ross</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Claudia</first><last>Scarlata</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Alejandro</first><last>Bedregal</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Alberto</first><last>Dominguez</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Alan</first><last>Dressler</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>Alaina</first><last>Henry</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>Matt</first><last>Malkan</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>Crystal L.</first><last>Martin</last></author><author><nr>14</nr><first>Dan</first><last>Masters</last></author><author><nr>15</nr><first>Patrick</first><last>McCarthy</last></author><author><nr>16</nr><first>Brian</first><last>Siana</last></author></authors><keys><key>oxygen</key><key>nir</key><key>grism</key><key>Ha</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2013-05-08 17:02:05</date><changeDate>2013-05-08 17:02:05</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2013</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1305.1399</url><note>cite arxiv:1305.1399Comment: 15 pages, 13 figures, submitted to ApJ</note><abstract>We present near-infrared emission line counts and luminosity functions from
the HST WFC3 Infrared Spectroscopic Parallels (WISP) program for 29 fields
observed using both the G102 and G141 grism. Altogether we identify 1048
emission line galaxies with observed equivalent widths greater than 40
Angstroms, 467 of which have multiple detected emission lines. The WISP survey
is sensitive to fainter flux levels (3-5x10^-17 ergs/s/cm^2) than the future
space near-infrared grism missions aimed at baryonic acoustic oscillation
cosmology (1-4x10^-16 ergs/s/cm^2), allowing us to probe the fainter emission
line galaxies that the shallower future surveys may miss. Cumulative number
counts of 0.7&lt;z&lt;1.5 galaxies are in rough agreement with the corrected count
predictions of H-alpha emitters from Geach et al. (2010), reaching 10,000
deg^-2 above an H-alpha flux of 2x10^-16 ergs/s/cm^2. H-alpha-emitting
galaxies with comparable OIII flux are roughly 5 times less common than
galaxies with just H-alpha emission at those flux levels. Galaxies with low
H-alpha/OIII ratios are very rare at the brighter fluxes that future
near-infrared grism surveys will probe; our survey finds no galaxies with
H-alpha/OIII&lt;0.95 that have H-alpha flux greater than 3x10^-16 ergs/s/cm^2.
We also find that our high redshift (z=0.9-1.5) counts are slightly higher
(factors of 1.3-2) than the high redshift (z=1.47) narrow band H-alpha survey
of HiZELS (Sobral et al. 2012), although our lower redshift luminosity function
(z=0.3-0.9) is consistent with their z=0.84 result. The evolution in the OIII
luminosity function from z=0.7-2.3 is almost entirely in the L* parameter,
which steadily increases with redshift over that range.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_81</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/23da1f39c08b26ea6deb153a9f532f19d/gron</bibsomy_id><title>An Intermediate Representation for Speculative Optimizations in a Dynamic Compiler</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Gilles</first><last>Duboscq</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Thomas</first><last>Würthinger</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Lukas</first><last>Stadler</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Christian</first><last>Wimmer</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Doug</first><last>Simon</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Hanspeter</first><last>Mössenböck</last></author></authors><keys><key>Compiler</key><key>IR</key><key>Graal</key><key>Optimization</key><key>Speculation</key><key>merged:gron</key></keys><date>2016-03-14 15:02:20</date><changeDate>2016-03-14 15:02:20</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2013</year><url /><abstract>We present a compiler intermediate representation (IR) that allows dynamic speculative optimizations for high-level languages. The IR is graph-based and contains nodes fixed to control flow as well as floating nodes. Side-effecting nodes include a framestate that maps values back to the original program. Guard nodes dynamically check assumptions and, on failure, deoptimize to the interpreter that continues execution. Guards implicitly use the framestate and program position of the last side-effecting node. Therefore, they can be represented as freely floating nodes in the IR. Exception edges are modeled as explicit control flow and are subject to full optimization. We use profiling and deoptimization to speculatively reduce the number of such edges. The IR is the core of a just-in-time compiler that is integrated with the Java HotSpot VM. We evaluate the design decisions of the IR using major Java benchmark suites.</abstract><pages>1--10</pages><doi>10.1145/2542142.2542143</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the 7th ACM Workshop on Virtual Machines and Intermediate Languages</booktitle><series>VMIL '13</series><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>978-1-4503-2601-8</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_82</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/29720ce5a83765676b85780523620f968/kweiand</bibsomy_id><title>The simplest query language that could possibly work</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>R.A.</first><last>O'Keefe</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>A.</first><last>Trotman</last></author></authors><keys><key>IR</key><key>Psychology,</key><key>Querying,</key><key>XML,</key><key>merged:kweiand</key><key>Foundations,</key></keys><date>2010-05-13 11:34:37</date><changeDate>2010-05-13 11:34:39</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2004</year><url /><abstract>The INEX'03 query language proved to be much too complicated for the INEX participants to use well, let alone anyone else. We need something simpler, but not too simple. Something which is basically a hybrid between Boolean IR queries and a stripped down CSS will do the job.</abstract><booktitle>Proceedings of the 2nd INEX Workshop</booktitle></publication><publication><id>han_83</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2c07a476888909c05a0ad1882f010eb14/brusilovsky</bibsomy_id><title>On the delusiveness of adopting a common space for modeling IR objects: Are queries documents?</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Peter</first><last>Bollmann-Sdorra</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Vijay V.</first><last>Raghavan</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:brusilovsky</key><key>social-search</key><key>merged:aho</key></keys><date>2017-11-15 17:02:25</date><changeDate>2017-11-15 17:02:25</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1993</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1002/(sici)1097-4571(199312)44:10%3C579::aid-asi3%3E3.0.co;2-b</url><abstract>Many authors, who adopt the vector space model, take the view that documents, terms, queries, etc., are all elements within the same (conceptual) space. This view seems to be a natural one, given that documents and queries have the same vector notation. We show, however, that the structure of the query space can be very different from that of the document space. To this end, concepts like preference, similarity, term independence, and linearity, both in the document space and in the query space, are discussed. Our conclusion is that a more realistic and complete view of IR is obtained if we do not consider documents and queries to be elements of the same space. This conclusion implies that certain restrictions usually applied in the design of an IR system are obviated. For example, the retrieval function need not be restricted to the ones that have the possibility to be interpreted as a similarity measure. \copyright 1993 John Wiley &amp; Sons, Inc.</abstract><journal>J. Am. Soc. Inf. Sci.</journal><volume>44</volume><number>10</number><pages>579--587</pages><issn>0002-8231</issn><doi>10.1002/(sici)1097-4571(199312)44:10%3C579::aid-asi3%3E3.0.co;2-b</doi><publisher>Wiley Subscription Services, Inc., A Wiley Company</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_84</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/262b5ae40c43d87930274e31020b42cac/ecml_pkdd_2011</bibsomy_id><title>Mining the Web for Synonyms: PMI-IR versus LSA on TOEFL</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Peter</first><last>Turney</last></author></authors><keys><key>10_year_award</key><key>award</key><key>web</key><key>pmi-ir</key><key>synonyms</key><key>toefl</key><key>2001</key><key>2011</key><key>merged:ecml_pkdd_2011</key><key>versus</key><key>Mining</key><key>ecml_pkdd_2011</key></keys><date>2011-09-03 12:02:05</date><changeDate>2011-09-03 12:02:05</changeDate><pub-type>incollection</pub-type><year>2001</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1007/3-540-44795-4_42</url><note>10.1007/3-540-44795-4_42</note><abstract>This paper presents a simple unsupervised learning algorithm for recognizing synonyms, based on statistical data acquired by querying a Web search engine. The algorithm, called PMI-IR, uses Pointwise Mutual Information (PMI) and Information Retrieval (IR) to measure the similarity of pairs of words. PMI-IR is empirically evaluated using 80 synonym test questions from the Test of English as a Foreign Language (TOEFL) and 50 synonym test questions from a collection of tests for students of English as a Second Language (ESL). On both tests, the algorithm obtains a score of 74%. PMI-IR is contrasted with Latent Semantic Analysis (LSA), which achieves a score of 64% on the same 80 TOEFL questions. The paper discusses potential applications of the new unsupervised learning algorithm and some implications of the results for LSA and LSI (Latent Semantic Indexing).</abstract><volume>2167</volume><pages>491-502</pages><booktitle>Machine Learning: ECML 2001</booktitle><series>Lecture Notes in Computer Science</series><publisher>Springer Berlin / Heidelberg</publisher><isbn>978-3-540-42536-6</isbn><affiliation>National Research Council of Canada Institute for Information Technology M-50 Montreal Road Ottawa Ontario Canada K1A 0R6</affiliation><keyword>Computer Science</keyword></publication><publication><id>han_85</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/22aca0b6477d62c496121f4a3502ba680/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Bayesian High-Redshift Quasar Classification from Optical and Mid-IR
  Photometry</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Gordon T.</first><last>Richards</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Adam D.</first><last>Myers</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Christina M.</first><last>Peters</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Coleman M.</first><last>Krawczyk</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Greg</first><last>Chase</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Nicholas P.</first><last>Ross</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Xiaohui</first><last>Fan</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Linhua</first><last>Jiang</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Mark</first><last>Lacy</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>Ian D.</first><last>McGreer</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>Jonathan R.</first><last>Trump</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>Ryan N.</first><last>Riegel</last></author></authors><keys><key>high</key><key>quasar</key><key>redshift</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>classification</key></keys><date>2015-07-29 09:52:35</date><changeDate>2015-07-29 09:52:35</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2015</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1507.07788</url><note>cite arxiv:1507.07788Comment: 54 pages, 17 figures; accepted by ApJS Data for tables 1 and 2  available at  http://www.physics.drexel.edu/~gtr/outgoing/optirqsos/data/master_quasar_catalogs.011414.fits.bz2  and  http://www.physics.drexel.edu/~gtr/outgoing/optirqsos/data/optical_ir_quasar_candidates.052015.fits.bz2</note><abstract>We identify 885,503 type 1 quasar candidates to i&lt;22 using the combination of
optical and mid-IR photometry. Optical photometry is taken from the Sloan
Digital Sky Survey-III: Baryon Oscillation Spectroscopic Survey
(SDSS-III/BOSS), while mid-IR photometry comes from a combination of data from
the Wide-Field Infrared Survey Explorer (WISE) ÄLLWISE" data release and
several large-area Spitzer Space Telescope fields. Selection is based on a
Bayesian kernel density algorithm with a training sample of 157,701
spectroscopically-confirmed type-1 quasars with both optical and mid-IR data.
Of the quasar candidates, 733,713 lack spectroscopic confirmation (and 305,623
are objects that we have not previously classified as photometric quasar
candidates). These candidates include 7874 objects targeted as high probability
potential quasars with 3.5&lt;z&lt;5 (of which 6779 are new photometric candidates).
Our algorithm is more complete to z&gt;3.5 than the traditional mid-IR selection
"wedges" and to 2.2&lt;z&lt;3.5 quasars than the SDSS-III/BOSS project. Number counts
and luminosity function analysis suggests that the resulting catalog is
relatively complete to known quasars and is identifying new high-z quasars at
z&gt;3. This catalog paves the way for luminosity-dependent clustering
investigations of large numbers of faint, high-redshift quasars and for further
machine learning quasar selection using Spitzer and WISE data combined with
other large-area optical imaging surveys.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_86</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/288e8963baee5808a218d0d4b8b2d1380/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Lower-Luminosity Galaxies could reionize the Universe: Very Steep
  Faint-End Slopes to the UV Luminosity Functions at z&amp;gt;=5-8 from the HUDF09
  WFC3/IR Observations</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>R. J.</first><last>Bouwens</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>G. D.</first><last>Illingworth</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>P. A.</first><last>Oesch</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>M.</first><last>Trenti</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>I.</first><last>Labbe</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>M.</first><last>Franx</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>M.</first><last>Stiavelli</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>C. M.</first><last>Carollo</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>P.</first><last>van Dokkum</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>D.</first><last>Magee</last></author></authors><keys><key>reionization</key><key>fuv</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>high-z</key><key>lumfunc</key></keys><date>2011-05-12 21:04:08</date><changeDate>2011-05-12 21:04:08</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2011</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1105.2038</url><note>cite arxiv:1105.2038
Comment: 6 pages, 4 figures, 1 table, submitted to Astrophysical Journal
  Letters</note><abstract>The HUDF09 data are the deepest near-IR observations ever, reaching to ~29.5
mag. The recent sample of 132 z~7 and z~8 galaxies from the HUDF09 data are
complemented here by new large samples at z~5 and z~6 galaxies (507 and 203,
respectively) and prior results at z~4. The luminosity functions we derive at
these redshifts reach to very faint limits of &amp;lt;0.05L*(z=3). The faint-end
slopes alpha are steep: -1.79+/-0.12 (z~5), -1.73+/-0.20 (z~6), -2.01+/-0.21
(z~7), and -1.91+/-0.32 (z~8). The results are consistent with a slope that
increases systematically to earlier times, with slopes close to -2 at z~7-8.
Slopes alpha ~-2 lead to formally divergent UV fluxes, though galaxies are not
expected to form below ~-10 AB mag. These results have major implications for
reionization. For such steep slopes, and a faint-end limit of -10 AB mag,
galaxies provide a very large UV ionizing photon flux. Adopting typical
parameters and extrapolating the current LF and faint-end slope evolution from
z~4-8 to z&amp;gt;8, we derive Thomson optical depths of 0.079, in excellent agreement
with the seven-year WMAP estimates (tau=0.088+/-0.015). It may thus not be
necessary to resort to extreme assumptions about the escape fraction or
clumping factor. Nevertheless, the uncertainties are large and depend
critically on the trend to steeper faint-end slopes at z&amp;gt;=6. We show that
deeper, and realistic, WFC3/IR+ACS observations can substantially lessen the
uncertainties on the z~5-8 slopes and further constrain this key parameter in
determining the UV ionizing flux from galaxies.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_87</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/20357d6b4d3aa885a0978036d50136373/hotho</bibsomy_id><title>A survey on the use of relevance feedback for information access systems</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Ian</first><last>Ruthven</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Mounia</first><last>Lalmas</last></author></authors><keys><key>feedback</key><key>merged:hotho</key><key>query</key><key>ir</key><key>survey</key><key>expansion</key><key>relevance</key></keys><date>2008-01-29 08:47:47</date><changeDate>2008-01-29 08:47:48</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2003</year><url>http://personal.cis.strath.ac.uk/~ir/papers/ker.pdf</url><abstract>Users of online search engines often find it difficult to express their need for information in the form of a query. However, if the user can identify examples of the kind of documents they require then they can employ a technique known as relevance feedback. Relevance feedback covers a range of techniques intended to improve a user's query and facilitate retrieval of information relevant to a user's information need. In this paper we survey relevance feedback techniques. We study both automatic techniques, in which the system modifies the user's query, and interactive techniques, in which the user has control over query modification. We also consider specific interfaces to relevance feedback systems and characteristics of searchers that can affect the use and success of relevance feedback systems.</abstract><journal>Knowl. Eng. Rev.</journal><volume>18</volume><number>2</number><pages>95--145</pages><issn>0269-8889</issn><doi>http://dx.doi.org/10.1017/S0269888903000638</doi><publisher>Cambridge University Press</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_88</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/25f7356c4e8566dc05938aec0690973c5/gsmith</bibsomy_id><title>rec-number 1212</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>R</first><last>Salawitch</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>P</first><last>Wennberg</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>G</first><last>Toon</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>B</first><last>Sen</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>J</first><last>Blavier</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:gsmith</key></keys><date>2010-06-22 19:38:37</date><changeDate>2010-06-22 19:39:26</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2002</year><url>http://links.isiglobalnet2.com/gateway/Gateway.cgi?GWVersion=2&amp;SrcAuth=mekentosj&amp;SrcApp=Papers&amp;DestLinkType=FullRecord&amp;DestApp=WOS&amp;KeyUT=000179630900002</url><note>622DH
Times Cited:15
Cited References Count:14</note><abstract>1 We report observations and calculations of peroxynitric acid, HO2NO2, in the stratosphere and upper troposphere. The simulations show that photolysis of HO2NO2 via excitation of purely vibrational modes at wavelengths longward of 760 nm (the near IR) can dominate loss of this species. Consideration of this photolytic pathway reduces calculated HO2NO2, resolving a large discrepancy between standard model calculations and observations of HO2NO2 at high-latitude spring. The lower calculated abundance of HO2NO2 reduces the efficiency of the OH + HO2NO2 sink of HOx. Consideration of this process leads to large increases in calculated HOx (20 to 60%) for high-latitude spring and better agreement with observed stratospheric abundances of HOx. Near IR photolysis of HO2NO2 alters the coupling between NOx and HOx in stratospheric and upper tropospheric photochemical models.</abstract><journal>Geophysical Research Letters</journal><volume>29</volume><number>16</number><pages>--</pages><uri>papers://E88B624E-D406-46FF-9D95-BB9C1AAE3FDC/Paper/p796</uri><affiliation>Salawitch, RJ
CALTECH, Jet Prop Lab, Mail Stop 183-601,4800 Oak Grove Dr, Pasadena, CA 91109 USA
CALTECH, Jet Prop Lab, Pasadena, CA 91109 USA
CALTECH, Pasadena, CA 91125 USA</affiliation></publication><publication><id>han_89</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/24a1b19925c2f726895d9c4d4206a3d85/ericblackman</bibsomy_id><title>The Spectacular Radio-Near-IR-X-ray Jet of 3C 111: X-ray Emission Mechanism and Jet Kinematics</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Devon</first><last>Clautice</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Eric S.</first><last>Perlman</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Markos</first><last>Georganopoulos</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Matthew L.</first><last>Lister</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Francesco</first><last>Tombesi</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Mihai</first><last>Cara</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Herman L.</first><last>Marshall</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Brandon</first><last>Hogan</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>Demos</first><last>Kazanas</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:ericblackman</key></keys><date>2019-03-25 08:20:55</date><changeDate>2019-03-25 08:20:55</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2016</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1602.04794</url><abstract>Relativistic jets are the most energetic manifestation of the active galactic
nucleus (AGN) phe- nomenon. AGN jets are observed from the radio through
gamma-rays and carry copious amounts of matter and energy from the sub-parsec
central regions out to the kiloparsec and often megaparsec scale galaxy and
cluster environs. While most spatially resolved jets are seen in the radio, an
in- creasing number have been discovered to emit in the optical/near-IR and/or
X-ray bands. Here we discuss a spectacular example of this class, the 3C 111
jet, housed in one of the nearest, double-lobed FR II radio galaxies known. We
discuss new, deep Chandra and HST observations that reveal both near-IR and
X-ray emission from several components of the 3C 111 jet, as well as both the
northern and southern hotspots. Important differences are seen between the
morphologies in the radio, X-ray and near-IR bands. The long (over 100 kpc on
each side), straight nature of this jet makes it an excellent prototype for
future, deep observations, as it is one of the longest such features seen in
the radio, near-IR/optical and X-ray bands. Several independent lines of
evidence, including the X-ray and broadband spectral shape as well as the
implied velocity of the approaching hotspot, lead us to strongly disfavor the
EC/CMB model and instead favor a two-component synchrotron model to explain the
observed X-ray emission for several jet components. Future observations with
NuSTAR, HST, and Chandra will allow us to further constrain the emission
mechanisms.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_90</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2277f41ba24ca8fcb51fe281471d52a44/sofiagruiz92</bibsomy_id><title>O encanto discreto do romanticismo: distanciamiento irónico e questoes de poética em Carlos Fradique Mendes</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Mar\'ıa Luisa</first><last>Leal</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:sofiagruiz92</key><key>Romanticismo</key><key>Espa{\~{n}}ol</key><key>Poes{\'{\i}}a</key><key>Ling{\"{u}}{\'{\i}}stica</key></keys><date>2015-12-01 11:35:13</date><changeDate>2015-12-01 11:35:13</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2005</year><url>http://dialnet.unirioja.es/servlet/fichero{\_}articulo?codigo=1971245{\&amp;}orden=79138</url><abstract>O encanto discreto do romanticismo: distanciamiento irónico e questoes de poética em Carlos Fradique Mendes. Autores: Mar\'ıa Luisa Leal Localización: Anuario de estudios filológicos, ISSN 0210-8178, Vol. 28, 2005 , pags. 149-162</abstract><journal>Anuario de estudios filológicos</journal><pages>149--162</pages><language>por</language><issn>0210-8178</issn></publication><publication><id>han_91</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2d269b5e4332f0b20742cc6d131e04347/sjbutler</bibsomy_id><title>Vocabulary Normalization’s Impact on IR-Based Concept Location</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Christopher</first><last>Uehlinger</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Dave</first><last>Binkley</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Dawn</first><last>Lawrie</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:sjbutler</key></keys><date>2012-08-11 13:46:12</date><changeDate>2012-08-11 13:46:12</changeDate><pub-type>techreport</pub-type><year>2012</year><url /><abstract>Tool support is crucial to modern software development, evolution, and maintenance. Early tools reused the static analysis performed by the compiler. These were followed by dynamic analysis tools and more recently tools that exploit natural language. This later class has the advantage that it can incorporate not only the code, but artifacts from all phases of software construction and its subsequent evolution. Unfortunately, the natural language found in source code often uses a vocabulary different from that used in other software artifacts and thus raises the vocabulary mismatch problem. This problem exists because many natural-language tools imported from Information Retrieval (IR) and Natural Language Processing (NLP) implicitly assume the use of a single natural language vocabulary. Vocabulary normalization, which goes well beyond simple identifier splitting, brings the vocabulary of the source into line with other artifacts. Consequently, it is expected to improve the performance of existing and future IR and NLP based tools. As a case study, an experiment with an LSI-based feature locator is replicated. Normalization universally improves performance. For the tersest queries, this improvement is over 200% (p &lt; 0.0001).</abstract><number>206520</number></publication><publication><id>han_92</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/252c315567bf063e746ebfa661d7c2db1/cirrus</bibsomy_id><title>Microfilm, paper, and OCR: issues in newspaper digitization at the Utah digital newspapers program</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Kenning</first><last>Arlitsch</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>John</first><last>Herbert</last></author></authors><keys><key>library</key><key>Digitalisierung</key><key>ocr</key><key>merged:cirrus</key></keys><date>2009-03-03 09:05:47</date><changeDate>2009-03-03 09:05:47</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2004</year><url>http://content.lib.utah.edu/u?/ir-main,114</url><abstract>Describes the issues surrounding digitizing newspapers from microfilm and paper in the Utah Digital Newspapers program. The paper also explores optical character recognition (OCR) accuracy and the problems of digital file storage of newspapers.</abstract><copyright>(c) Kenning Arlitsch &amp; John Herbert</copyright></publication><publication><id>han_93</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2b7c28d7ce057298e741dd2ddf21ec10d/acastro</bibsomy_id><title>Emergent IR dual 2d CFTs in charged AdS5 black holes</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Jan</first><last>de Boer</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Maria</first><last>Johnstone</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>M. M.</first><last>Sheikh-Jabbari</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Joan</first><last>Simon</last></author></authors><keys><key>ads5,</key><key>universality</key><key>kerr-cft,</key><key>merged:acastro</key></keys><date>2019-02-26 10:37:35</date><changeDate>2019-02-26 10:37:35</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2011</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1112.4664</url><abstract>We study the possible dynamical emergence of IR conformal invariance
describing the low energy excitations of near-extremal R-charged global AdS5
black holes. We find interesting behavior especially when we tune parameters in
such a way that the relevant extremal black holes have classically vanishing
horizon area, i.e. no classical ground-state entropy, and when we combine the
low energy limit with a large N limit of the dual gauge theory. We consider
both near-BPS and non-BPS regimes and their near horizon limits, emphasize the
differences between the local AdS3 throats emerging in either case, and discuss
potential dual IR 2d CFTs for each case. We compare our results with the
predictions obtained from the Kerr/CFT correspondence, and obtain a natural
quantization for the central charge of the near-BPS emergent IR CFT which we
interpret in terms of the open strings stretched between giant gravitons.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_94</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2052940c1016ef43c38d2ddf2c288f28d/giovanna</bibsomy_id><title>Nondestructive analysis and dating of historical paper based on IR
	Spectroscopy and chemometric data evaluation</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>T.</first><last>Trafela</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>M.</first><last>Strlic</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>J.</first><last>Kolar</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>D. A.</first><last>Lichtblau</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>M.</first><last>Anders</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>D. P.</first><last>Mencigar</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>B.</first><last>Pihlar</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:giovanna</key></keys><date>2010-05-12 15:26:52</date><changeDate>2010-05-12 15:26:56</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2007</year><url /><abstract>Sampling restrictions in analysis of cultural heritage materials narrow
	the choice of appropriate analytical methods considerably. In this
	work, near- and mid-FT-IR reflectance data were related to paper
	properties determined with classical analytical methods using partial
	least-squares. Nondestructive determination of properties, which
	are of importance for evaluation of the long-term stability of historical
	paper, i.e., ash content, lignin content, degree of polymerization
	of cellulose, pH, and aluminum content, is possible. With the use
	of a considerable sample set, satisfactory reliability was achieved
	for all properties but aluminum content. Considering that with age,
	chemical properties of paper change, dating of historical documents
	was attempted for the first time, also with success.</abstract><journal>Analytical Chemistry</journal><volume>79</volume><number>16</number><pages>6319-6323</pages></publication><publication><id>han_95</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/29f4ab13e07b48b9723113aa74224be65/folke</bibsomy_id><title>Introduction to Information Retrieval</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Christopher D.</first><last>Manning</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Prabhakar</first><last>Raghavan</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Hinrich</first><last>Schütze</last></author></authors><keys><key>retrieval</key><key>merged:folke</key><key>book</key><key>ir</key><key>online</key><key>information</key><key>introduction</key><key>merged:jil</key></keys><date>2010-12-20 06:06:48</date><changeDate>2010-12-20 06:06:48</changeDate><pub-type>book</pub-type><year>2008</year><url>http://nlp.stanford.edu/IR-book/information-retrieval-book.html</url><abstract>Class-tested and coherent, this textbook teaches classical and web information retrieval, including web search and the related areas of text classification and text clustering from basic concepts. It gives an up-to-date treatment of all aspects of the design and implementation of systems for gathering, indexing, and searching documents; methods for evaluating systems; and an introduction to the use of machine learning methods on text collections. All the important ideas are explained using examples and figures, making it perfect for introductory courses in information retrieval for advanced undergraduates and graduate students in computer science. Based on feedback from extensive classroom experience, the book has been carefully structured in order to make teaching more natural and effective.</abstract><publisher>Cambridge University Press</publisher><isbn>978-0-521-86571-5</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_96</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/27e1dc3f52085093cc33d8fe931253b34/hotho</bibsomy_id><title>Tagging and searching: Search retrieval effectiveness of folksonomies on the World Wide Web</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>P. Jason</first><last>Morrison</last></author></authors><keys><key>Social</key><key>social</key><key>folksonomy</key><key>merged:ewomant</key><key>ir</key><key>IR</key><key>analysis</key><key>google</key><key>performance</key><key>comparision</key><key>Web</key><key>Folksonomy</key><key>internet</key><key>tagging</key><key>merged:hotho</key><key>study</key><key>Information</key><key>dis</key><key>merged:beate</key><key>World</key><key>retrieval</key><key>web</key><key>web2.0</key><key>toread</key><key>social-search</key><key>merged:iamjason</key><key>engine</key><key>Search</key><key>information_retrieval</key><key>Wide</key><key>search</key><key>bookmarking</key></keys><date>2008-09-04 12:37:59</date><changeDate>2008-09-04 12:37:59</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2008</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=1377474</url><abstract>Many Web sites have begun allowing users to submit items to a collection and tag them with keywords. The folksonomies built from these tags are an interesting topic that has seen little empirical research. This study compared the search information retrieval (IR) performance of folksonomies from social bookmarking Web sites against search engines and subject directories. Thirty-four participants created 103 queries for various information needs. Results from each IR system were collected and participants judged relevance. Folksonomy search results overlapped with those from the other systems, and documents found by both search engines and folksonomies were significantly more likely to be judged relevant than those returned by any single IR system type. The search engines in the study had the highest precision and recall, but the folksonomies fared surprisingly well. Del.icio.us was statistically indistinguishable from the directories in many cases. Overall the directories were more precise than the folksonomies but they had similar recall scores. Better query handling may enhance folksonomy IR performance further. The folksonomies studied were promising, and may be able to improve Web search performance.</abstract><journal>Inf. Process. Manage.</journal><volume>44</volume><number>4</number><pages>1562--1579</pages><issn>0306-4573</issn><doi>http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ipm.2007.12.010</doi><publisher>Pergamon Press, Inc.</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_97</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2e680e087a17b115f0b146a8e502d35eb/thanhvg</bibsomy_id><title>MFI Fingerprint: How Pentasil-Induced IR Bands Shift during Zeolite Nanogrowth</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>David</first><last>Lesthaeghe</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Peter</first><last>Vansteenkiste</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Toon</first><last>Verstraelen</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>An</first><last>Ghysels</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Christine E. A.</first><last>Kirschhock</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Johan A.</first><last>Martens</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Veronique Van</first><last>Speybroeck</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Michel</first><last>Waroquier</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:thanhvg</key></keys><date>2009-09-09 22:20:15</date><changeDate>2011-09-22 16:42:11</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2008</year><url>http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/jp711550s</url><abstract>Silicalite-1 zeolite exhibits a characteristic pentasil framework vibration around 540−550 cm−1. In the initial stages of zeolite synthesis, however, this band is observed at much higher wavenumbers: literature shows this vibration to depend on particle size and to shift over 100 cm−1 with increasing condensation. In this work, the pentasil vibration frequency was derived from theoretical molecular dynamics simulations to obtain the correct IR band assignments for important nanoparticles. The IR spectroscopic fingerprint of oligomeric five-ring containing precursors proposed in the literature was computed and compared with experimental data. Our theoretical results show that, while isolated five-membered rings show characteristic vibrational bands around 650 cm−1, the combination of five-membered rings in the full MFI-type structure readily generates the bathochromic shift to the typical pentasil vibration around 550 cm−1. As opposed to what was previously believed, the IR band does not shift gradually as nanoparticle size increases, but it is highly dependent on the specific way structural units are added. The most important feature is the appearance of an additional band when double five-membered rings are included, which allows for a clear distinction between the key stages of early zeolite nucleation. Furthermore, the combination of the simulated spectra with the experimental observation of this spectral feature in nanoparticles extracted from silicalite-1 clear solutions supports their structured nature. The theoretical insights on the dependency of pentasil vibrations with the degree of condensation offer valuable support toward future investigations on the genesis of a zeolite crystal.</abstract><journal>J. Phys. Chem. C</journal><volume>112</volume><number>25</number><pages>9186--9191</pages></publication><publication><id>han_98</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2164c37be60c1a47d1727ad9b82f01237/jaeschke</bibsomy_id><title>Text Mining Scientific Papers: a Survey on FCA-based Information Retrieval Research.</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Jonas</first><last>Poelmans</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Paul</first><last>Elzinga</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Stijn</first><last>Viaene</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Guido</first><last>Dedene</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Sergei O.</first><last>Kuznetsov</last></author></authors><keys><key>formal</key><key>retrieval</key><key>merged:jaeschke</key><key>fca</key><key>concept</key><key>ir</key><key>analysis</key><key>information</key></keys><date>2012-02-23 14:50:59</date><changeDate>2014-07-28 15:57:11</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2011</year><url>http://dblp.uni-trier.de/db/conf/incdm/incdm2011p.html#PoelmansEVDK11</url><abstract>Formal Concept Analysis (FCA) is an unsupervised clustering technique and many scientific papers are devoted to applying FCA in Information Retrieval (IR) research. We collected 103 papers published between 2003-2009 which mention FCA and information retrieval in the abstract, title or keywords. Using a prototype of our FCA-based toolset CORDIET, we converted the pdf-files containing the papers to plain text, indexed them with Lucene using a thesaurus containing terms related to FCA research and then created the concept lattice shown in this paper. We visualized, analyzed and explored the literature
with concept lattices and discovered multiple interesting research streams in IR of which we give an extensive overview. The core contributions of this paper are the innovative application of FCA to the text
mining of scientific papers and the survey of the FCA-based IR research.</abstract><pages>82--96</pages><booktitle>Industrial Conference on Data Mining - Poster and Industry Proceedings</booktitle><publisher>IBaI Publishing</publisher><isbn>978-3-942954-06-4</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_99</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/293df73c45252ce1fe3d691aefe3284ec/hlwoodcock</bibsomy_id><title>IR spectra of phosphate ions in aqueous solution: Predictions of a DFT/MM approach compared with observations</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>M.</first><last>Klahn</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>G.</first><last>Mathias</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>C.</first><last>Kotting</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>M.</first><last>Nonella</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>J.</first><last>Schlitter</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>K.</first><last>Gerwert</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>P.</first><last>Tavan</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:hlwoodcock</key><key>bibtex-import</key></keys><date>2006-06-16 05:03:46</date><changeDate>2006-06-16 05:03:46</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2004</year><url /><abstract>Due to the progress of density functional theory (DFT) accurate computations of vibrational spectra of isolated molecules have become a standard task in computational chemistry. This is not yet the case for solution spectra. To contribute to the exploration of corresponding computational procedures, here we suggest a more efficient variant of the so-called instantaneous normal-mode analysis (INMA). This variant applies conventional molecular dynamics (MD) simulations, which are based on nonpolarizable molecular mechanics (MM) force fields, to the rapid generation of a large ensemble of different solvation shells for a solute molecule. Short hybrid simulations, in which the solute is treated by DFT and the aqueous solvent by MM, start from snapshots of the MM solute-solvent MD trajectory and yield a set of statistically independent hydration shells partially adjusted to the DFT/MM force field. Within INMA, these shells are kept fixed at their 300 K structures, line spectra are calculated from the DFT/MM Hessians of the solute, and its inhomogeneously broadened solution spectra are derived by second-order statistics. As our test application we have selected the phosphate ions HPO42- and H2PO4- because sizable solvation effects are expected for the IR spectra of these strongly polarizable ions. The widths, intensities, and spectral positions of the calculated bands are compared with experimental IR spectra recorded by us for the purpose of checking the computational procedures. These comparisons provide insights into the merits and limitations of the available DFT/MM approach to the prediction of IR spectra in the condensed phase.</abstract><journal>JOURNAL OF PHYSICAL CHEMISTRY A</journal><volume>108</volume><number>29</number><pages>6186--6194</pages></publication><publication><id>han_100</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/25d7ae643b66e0be21f289d4c514950e0/seandalai</bibsomy_id><title>German Decompounding in a Difficult Corpus</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Enrique</first><last>Alfonseca</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Slaven</first><last>Bilac</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Stefan</first><last>Pharies</last></author></authors><keys><key>2008</key><key>german</key><key>compounds</key><key>merged:seandalai</key><key>ir</key><key>cicling</key><key>splitting</key></keys><date>2008-09-15 20:18:34</date><changeDate>2008-09-15 20:18:34</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2008</year><url>http://www.springerlink.com/content/tw815263702576ww/fulltext.pdf</url><abstract>Splitting compound words has proved to be useful in areas such as Machine Translation, Speech Recognition or Information Retrieval (IR). In the case of IR systems, they usually have to cope with noisy data, as user queries are usually written quickly and submitted without review. This work attempts at improving the current approaches for German decompounding when applied to query keywords. The results show an increase of more than 10% in accuracy compared to other state-of-the-art methods.</abstract><booktitle>Proceedings of the 9th International Conference on Intelligent Text Processing and Computational Linguistics (CICLING-08)</booktitle></publication><publication><id>han_101</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2cbb98e8e335da95a023eeb9e70e8579a/miki</bibsomy_id><title>The evolving far-IR galaxy luminosity function and dust-obscured
  star-formation rate density out to z~5</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>M. P.</first><last>Koprowski</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>J. S.</first><last>Dunlop</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>M. J.</first><last>Michałowski</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>K. E. K.</first><last>Coppin</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>J. E.</first><last>Geach</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>R. J.</first><last>McLure</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>D.</first><last>Scott</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>P. P.</first><last>van der Werf</last></author></authors><keys><key>obscured</key><key>IR</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>dust</key></keys><date>2017-06-05 10:18:15</date><changeDate>2017-06-05 10:18:15</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1706.00426</url><note>cite arxiv:1706.00426Comment: 17 pages, 12 figures, 5 tables, submitted to MNRAS</note><abstract>We present a new measurement of the evolving galaxy far-IR luminosity
function (LF) extending out to redshifts z~5, with resulting implications for
the level of dust-obscured star-formation density in the young Universe. To
achieve this we have exploited recent advances in sub-mm/mm imaging with
SCUBA-2 on the James Clerk Maxwell Telescope (JCMT) and the Atacama Large
Millimeter/Submillimeter Array (ALMA), which together provide unconfused
imaging with sufficient dynamic range to provide meaningful coverage of the
luminosity-redshift plane out to z&gt;4. Our results support previous indications
that the faint-end slope of the far-IR LF is sufficiently flat that comoving
luminosity-density is dominated by bright objects (~L*). However, we find that
the number-density/luminosity of such sources at high redshifts has been
severely over-estimated by studies that have attempted to push the
highly-confused Herschel SPIRE surveys beyond z~2. Consequently we confirm
recent reports that cosmic star-formation density is dominated by UV-visible
star formation at z&gt;4. Using both direct (1/Vmax) and maximum likelihood
determinations of the LF, we find that its high-redshift evolution is well
characterized by continued positive luminosity evolution coupled with negative
density evolution (with increasing redshift). This explains why bright sub-mm
sources continue to be found at z&gt;5, even though their integrated contribution
to cosmic star-formation density at such early times is very small. The
evolution of the far-IR galaxy LF thus appears similar in form to that already
established for active galactic nuclei, possibly reflecting a similar
dependence on the growth of galaxy mass.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_102</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2d5564c2e0ea55d8cb12e33e3a78620be/sac</bibsomy_id><title>Score region algebra: building a transparent XML-R database</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Vojkan</first><last>Mihajlović</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Henk Ernst</first><last>Blok</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Djoerd</first><last>Hiemstra</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Peter M. G.</first><last>Apers</last></author></authors><keys><key>algebra</key><key>merged:sac</key><key>xml</key><key>ir</key><key>region</key></keys><date>2012-05-29 15:52:25</date><changeDate>2012-05-29 15:52:25</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2005</year><url>http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/1099554.1099560</url><abstract>A unified database framework that will enable better comprehension of ranked XML retrieval is still a challenge in the XML database field. We propose a logical algebra, named score region algebra, that enables transparent specification of information retrieval (IR) models for XML databases. The transparency is achieved by a possibility to instantiate various retrieval models, using abstract score functions within algebra operators, while logical query plan and operator definitions remain unchanged. Our algebra operators model three important aspects of XML retrieval: element relevance score computation, element score propagation, and element score combination. To illustrate the usefulness of our algebra we instantiate four different, well known IR scoring models, and combine them with different score propagation and combination functions. We implemented the algebra operators in a prototype system on top of a low-level database kernel. The evaluation of the system is performed on a collection of IEEE articles in XML format provided by INEX. We argue that state of the art XML IR models can be transparently implemented using our score region algebra framework on top of any low-level physical database engine or existing RDBMS, allowing a more systematic investigation of retrieval model behavior.</abstract><pages>12--19</pages><doi>10.1145/1099554.1099560</doi><booktitle>Proceedings of the 14th ACM international conference on Information and knowledge management</booktitle><series>CIKM '05</series><publisher>ACM</publisher><isbn>1-59593-140-6</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_103</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/24b8c16a3cb78baffc991dca22612e05f/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Molecular gas content in strongly-lensed z~1.5-3 star-forming galaxies
  with low IR luminosities</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>M.</first><last>Dessauges-Zavadsky</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>M.</first><last>Zamojski</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>D.</first><last>Schaerer</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>F.</first><last>Combes</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>E.</first><last>Egami</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>A. M.</first><last>Swinbank</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>J.</first><last>Richard</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>P.</first><last>Sklias</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>T. D.</first><last>Rawle</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>M.</first><last>Rex</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>J. P.</first><last>Kneib</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>F.</first><last>Boone</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>A.</first><last>Blain</last></author></authors><keys><key>mass</key><key>lensed</key><key>low</key><key>molecular</key><key>gas</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2014-08-06 09:59:05</date><changeDate>2014-08-06 09:59:05</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2014</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1408.0816</url><note>cite arxiv:1408.0816Comment: 21 pages, 16 figures. Submitted to A&amp;A</note><abstract>To extend the molecular gas measurements to typical star-forming galaxies
(SFGs) with SFR &lt; 40 Msun yr^-1 and M* &lt; 2.5x10^10 Msun at z~1.5-3, we have
observed CO emission with the IRAM Plateau de Bure Interferometer and 30m
telescope for five strongly-lensed galaxies selected from the Herschel Lensing
Survey. These observations are combined with a compilation of CO measurements
from the literature. From this, we infer the luminosity correction factors r2,1
= 0.8 and r3,1 = 0.65 of the CO rotational levels J=2 and J=3, respectively,
valid for SFGs and sub-mm galaxies at z&gt;1. The combined sample of CO-detected
SFGs at z&gt;1 shows a large spread in star formation efficiency (SFE), such that
SFE extend beyond the low values of local spirals and overlap the distribution
of z&gt;1 sub-mm galaxies. We find that the spread in SFE (or equivalently in
molecular gas depletion timescale) is due to primarily the specific star
formation rate, but also stellar mass and redshift. Correlations of SFE with
the offset from the main-sequence and the compactness of the starburst are less
clear. The increase of the molecular gas depletion timescale with M* now
revealed by low M* SFGs at z&gt;1 is opposed to the admitted constant molecular
gas depletion timescale and the linear Kennicutt-Schmidt relation. We confirm
an increase of the molecular gas fraction (fgas) from z~0.2 to z~1.2, followed
by a quasi non-evolution toward higher redshifts. At each redshift fgas shows a
large dispersion due to the dependence of fgas on M*, producing a gradient of
increasing fgas with decreasing M*. We provide the first measure of fgas of z&gt;1
SFGs at the low-M* end (10^9.4 &lt; M*/Msun &lt; 10^9.9), reaching a mean fgas =
0.67+/-0.20 which shows a clear fgas upturn. Finally, we find evidence for a
non-universal dust-to-gas ratio among high-redshift SFGs and sub-mm galaxies,
local spirals and ULIRGs with near-solar metallicities.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_104</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/231448acdff0cd82f667a1d0b69bdf415/ruyhliu</bibsomy_id><title>A meta-analysis of the effects of search experience on search performance in terms of the recall measure in controlled IR user experiments</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Ying-Hsang</first><last>Liu</last></author></authors><keys><key>myown</key><key>merged:ruyhliu</key></keys><date>2012-10-01 15:37:59</date><changeDate>2012-10-01 15:40:21</changeDate><pub-type>incollection</pub-type><year>2010</year><url>http://ruyhliu.phpfogapp.com/wp-content/papercite-data/pdf/liu-2010nx.pdf</url><abstract>This paper reports a meta-analysis of the effects of search experience on search performance in terms of the recall measure in controlled IR user experiments. More specifically, this study was designed to answer the research question: how large is the average effect size in the set of studies included in the meta-analysis? Search experience, a manifestation of users' search skills accumulated through their interactions with IR systems over time, has been identified as an important research variable in user search behaviours. The participants included in primary studies were end-users or intermediaries recruited for IR user experiments. The results of the meta-analysis (N = 8) using a fixed-effects model showed that search experience has an overall positive effect on the recall measure (weighted mean correlation coefficient r = 0.04, 95% confidence interval was -0.01 to 0.09). Our findings may provide implications for designing adaptive or personalized IR systems that take into account the contextual information at the user and interactional levels.</abstract><booktitle>Proceedings of the Fifteenth Australasian Document Computing Symposium</booktitle><publisher>School of Computer Science and IT, RMIT University</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_105</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2338f3dc86d4b70015bc036bc58565743/miki</bibsomy_id><title>ARCONS: A 2024 Pixel Optical through Near-IR Cryogenic Imaging
  Spectrophotometer</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>B. A.</first><last>Mazin</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>S. R.</first><last>Meeker</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>M. J.</first><last>Strader</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>B.</first><last>Bumble</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>K.</first><last>O'Brien</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>P.</first><last>Szypryt</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>D.</first><last>Marsden</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>J. C.</first><last>van Eyken</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>G. E.</first><last>Duggan</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>G.</first><last>Ulbricht</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>C.</first><last>Stoughton</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>M.</first><last>Johnson</last></author></authors><keys><key>technology</key><key>merged:miki</key><key>detector</key></keys><date>2013-06-21 04:07:35</date><changeDate>2013-06-21 04:07:35</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2013</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1306.4674</url><note>cite arxiv:1306.4674Comment: 12 pages, 16 figures, submitted to PASP</note><abstract>We present the design, construction, and commissioning results of ARCONS, the
Array Camera for Optical to Near-IR Spectrophotometry. ARCONS is the first
ground-based instrument in the optical through near-IR wavelength range based
on Microwave Kinetic Inductance Detectors (MKIDs). MKIDs are revolutionary
cryogenic detectors, capable of detecting single photons and measuring their
energy without filters or gratings, similar to an X-ray microcalorimeter. MKIDs
are nearly ideal, noiseless photon detectors, as they do not suffer from read
noise or dark current and have nearly perfect cosmic ray rejection. ARCONS is
an Integral Field Spectrograph (IFS) containing a lens-coupled 2024 pixel MKID
array yielding a 20"x20" field of view, and has been deployed on the Palomar
200" and Lick 120" telescopes for 24 nights of observing. We present initial
results showing that ARCONS and its MKID arrays are now a fully operational and
powerful tool for astronomical observations.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_106</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/27598931c44a2bc82d3a0d9219448db76/jhandcock</bibsomy_id><title>Palant\'ır: raising awareness among configuration management workspaces</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Anita</first><last>Sarma</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Zahra</first><last>Noroozi</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>André</first><last>van der Hoek</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>se</key><key>awareness</key><key>merged:jhandcock</key><key>merged:pnk</key><key>applications</key></keys><date>2008-11-24 22:11:02</date><changeDate>2008-11-24 22:11:02</changeDate><pub-type>inproceedings</pub-type><year>2003</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=776870</url><abstract>Current configuration management systems promote workspaces that isolate developers from each other. This isolation is both good and bad. It is good, because developers make their changes without any interference from changes made concurrently by other developers. It is bad, because not knowing which artifacts are changing in parallel regularly leads to problems when changes are promoted from workspaces into a central configuration management repository. Overcoming the bad isolation, while retaining the good isolation, is a matter of raising awareness among developers, an issue traditionally ignored by the discipline of configuration management. To fill this void, we have developed Palantír, a novel workspace awareness tool that complements existing configuration management systems by providing developers with insight into other workspaces. In particular, the tool informs a developer of which other developers change which other artifacts, calculates a simple measure of severity of those changes, and graphically displays the information in a configurable and generally non-obtrusive manner. To illustrate the use of Palantír, we demonstrate how it integrates with two representative configuration management systems.</abstract><pages>444--454</pages><booktitle>ICSE '03: Proceedings of the 25th International Conference on Software Engineering</booktitle><publisher>IEEE Computer Society</publisher><isbn>0-7695-1877-X</isbn></publication><publication><id>han_107</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/22134cd8011080a2a37666402fd741d2a/ruettinger</bibsomy_id><title>Evaluation of thermodynamic and photophysical properties of tricarbocyanine near-IR dyes in organized media using single-molecule monitoring</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Steven A.</first><last>Soper</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Jr Benjamin L.</first><last>Legendre</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Jiping</first><last>Huang</last></author></authors><keys><key>imported</key><key>merged:ruettinger</key></keys><date>2007-01-12 21:53:18</date><changeDate>2007-01-12 21:53:18</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>1995</year><url>http://www.sciencedirect.com/science?_ob=ArticleURL&amp;_udi=B6TFN-3YCN033-5B&amp;_user=10&amp;_handle=V-WA-A-W-WE-MsSAYWA-UUW-U-AACZCWBBUC-AACVAUVAUC-WZUWYEVY-WE-U&amp;_fmt=summary&amp;_coverDate=05%2F12%2F1995&amp;_rdoc=22&amp;_orig=browse&amp;_srch=%23toc%235231%231995%23997629996%23156003!&amp;_cdi=5231&amp;view=c&amp;_acct=C000050221&amp;_version=1&amp;_urlVersion=0&amp;_userid=10&amp;md5=377555330725167d162f02a4661b34d5</url><abstract>Detection of single NIR fluorescent dye molecules in the organized media sodium dodecyl sulfate (SDS) and triton X-100 surfactnts above their critical micelle concentrations was used to determine partition coefficients and photophysical properties of dye molecules resident within the micelle aggregate. Inspection of the filtered data showed evidence of large amplitude photon bursts arising from single molecular events in these organized media. In pure H2O containing dye, no bursts were observed. The results indicate that only molecules resident within the hydrophobic core of the micelle were detected. From the number of events observed and the number of events expected, partition coefficients (Kp) for IR-132 in SDS and triton X-100 solutions were calculated. In addition, the photon yield per molecule associated with only those molecules resident within the hydrophobic cavity of the micelle was determined.</abstract><journal>Chem. Phys. Lett.</journal><volume>237</volume><number>3-4</number><pages>339-345</pages></publication><publication><id>han_108</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/208f4315c2c458950ea6da27868d3f184/hlwoodcock</bibsomy_id><title>Molecular structure and IR spectra of bromomethanes by DFT and post-Hartree-Fock MP2 and CCSD(T) calculations</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>R.</first><last>Venkatraman</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>J. S.</first><last>Kwiatkowski</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>G.</first><last>Bakalarski</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>J.</first><last>Leszczynski</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:hlwoodcock</key><key>bibtex-import</key></keys><date>2006-06-16 05:03:46</date><changeDate>2006-06-16 05:03:46</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2000</year><url /><abstract>The molecular parameters (geometries, rotational constants, dipole moments) and vibrational IR spectra (harmonic wavenumbers, absolute intensities) of bromomethanes (CH3Br, CH2Br2, CHBr3, CBr4) are predicted by a density functional theory with the hybrid Becke3-LYP functional (DFT) and post-Hartree-Fock methods (MP2, CCSD(T)) using a 6-311G(2d,2p)-type basis set. The MP2 calculations an carried out with different numbers of frozen core orbitals to find how the number of bromine orbitals used for electron correlation influences the predicted molecular parameters and IR spectra of the species in question. Three options were used: (a) all electrons (full), with both the core and valence orbitals considered; (b) partial frozen core option (pfc), when the orbitals up to 3p of bromine were frozen; and (c) full frozen core option (ffc), when all core orbitals up to 3d were frozen. The CCSD(T) calculations for geometric parameters were carried out with both the pfc and ffc options, while for the prediction of the IR spectra only the ffc option was used. In addition, the calculations at the DFT and MP2(pfc) levels with inclusion of f functions on carbon and bromine atoms in bromomethanes (and also the CCSD(T)(pfc) calculations for CH3Br) were carried out to predict the changes in the geometric parameters and/or vibrational IR spectra of the molecules upon inclusion of f functions The geometries of bromomethanes (particularly the CBr bond lengths) are predicted better by the DFT and CCSD(T) calculations when the f functions (in particular on bromine atom) are included, while the MP2 calculations without f functions are good enough for comet predictions of the molecular geometries. The molecular parameters and vibrational IR spectra of bromomethanes in question and their deuterated species predicted by the DFT, MP2(ffc) and CCSD(T)(ffc) with the 6-311G(2d,2p) basis set agree well with the available experimental data.</abstract><journal>MOLECULAR PHYSICS</journal><volume>98</volume><number>6</number><pages>371--386</pages></publication><publication><id>han_109</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2a0e3a4beedfdbc382d8b76902f9ce999/miki</bibsomy_id><title>A far-IR view of the starburst driven superwind in NGC 2146</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>K.</first><last>Kreckel</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>L.</first><last>Armus</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>B.</first><last>Groves</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>M.</first><last>Lyubenova</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>T.</first><last>Diaz-Santos</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>E.</first><last>Schinnerer</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>P.</first><last>Appleton</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>K. V.</first><last>Croxall</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>D. A.</first><last>Dale</last></author><author><nr>10</nr><first>L. K.</first><last>Hunt</last></author><author><nr>11</nr><first>P.</first><last>Beirao</last></author><author><nr>12</nr><first>A. D.</first><last>Bolatto</last></author><author><nr>13</nr><first>D.</first><last>Calzetti</last></author><author><nr>14</nr><first>J. Donovan</first><last>Meyer</last></author><author><nr>15</nr><first>B. T.</first><last>Draine</last></author><author><nr>16</nr><first>J.</first><last>Hinz</last></author><author><nr>17</nr><first>R. C.</first><last>Kennicutt</last></author><author><nr>18</nr><first>S.</first><last>Meidt</last></author><author><nr>19</nr><first>E. J.</first><last>Murphy</last></author><author><nr>20</nr><first>J. D. T.</first><last>Smith</last></author><author><nr>21</nr><first>F. S.</first><last>Tabatabaei</last></author><author><nr>22</nr><first>F.</first><last>Walter</last></author></authors><keys><key>galaxy</key><key>starburst</key><key>superwind</key><key>nearby</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2014-03-12 09:47:43</date><changeDate>2014-03-12 09:47:43</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2014</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1403.2381</url><note>cite arxiv:1403.2381Comment: 15 pages, 13 figures, submitted to ApJ</note><abstract>NGC 2146, a nearby luminous infrared galaxy (LIRG), presents evidence for
outflows along the disk minor axis in all gas phases (ionized, neutral atomic
and molecular). We present an analysis of the multi-phase starburst driven
superwind in the central 5 kpc as traced in spatially resolved spectral line
observations, using far-IR Herschel PACS spectroscopy, to probe the effects on
the atomic and ionized gas, and optical integral field spectroscopy to examine
the ionized gas through diagnostic line ratios. We observe an increased ~250
km/s velocity dispersion in the OI 63 micron, OIII 88 micron, NII 122
micron and CII 158 micron fine-structure lines that is spatially coincident
with high excitation gas above and below the disk. We model this with a slow
~200 km/s shock and trace the superwind to the edge of our field of view 2.5
kpc above the disk. We present new SOFIA 37 micron observations to explore the
warm dust distribution, and detect no clear dust entrainment in the outflow.
The stellar kinematics appear decoupled from the regular disk rotation seen in
all gas phases, consistent with a recent merger event disrupting the system. We
consider the role of the superwind in the evolution of NGC 2146 and speculate
on the evolutionary future of the system. Our observations of NGC 2146 in the
far-IR allow an unobscured view of the wind, crucial for tracing the superwind
to the launching region at the disk center, and provide a local analog for
future ALMA observations of outflows in high redshift systems.</abstract></publication><publication><id>han_110</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2dda7cfeb503c829924e2bfd67d037f6c/thesaiorg</bibsomy_id><title>Detection and Measurement of magnetic data for short length wireless communication using FT-IR</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Abu</first><last>Saleh</last></author></authors><keys><key>merged:thesaiorg</key><key>Spectrum;</key><key>FT-IR;</key><key>prism.</key><key>FT;</key></keys><date>2014-02-21 08:00:08</date><changeDate>2014-02-21 08:00:08</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2010</year><url>http://ijacsa.thesai.org/</url><abstract>Infrared (IR) radiation is a type of electromagnetic radiation. Infrared “light” has a longer wavelength than visible light. Red light has a longer wavelength than other colors of light, and infrared has even longer waves than red does; so infrared is sort of “redder-than-red” light or “beyond red” light. Infrared radiation lies between visible light and radio waves on the electromagnetic spectrum. In this paper, the infrared radiation is used for detecting the magnetic data for high speedy short range wireless communication. But infrared radiation may use in various way. This paper contains the performance of the FT-IR technique that is for multiplexing the transmissions of different users are viewed at the same time.</abstract><journal>International Journal of Advanced Computer Science and Applications(IJACSA)</journal><volume>1</volume><number>2</number></publication><publication><id>han_111</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/25e503dff9cc0e9daf119a3670e629e99/cgoehler</bibsomy_id><title>High-Performance Near-IR Photodetector Using Low-Bandgap MA0.5FA0.5Pb0.5Sn0.5I3 Perovskite</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Xiaobao</first><last>Xu</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Chu-Chen</first><last>Chueh</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>Peifeng</first><last>Jing</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>Zhibin</first><last>Yang</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>Xueliang</first><last>Shi</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>Ting</first><last>Zhao</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>Lih Y.</first><last>Lin</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>Alex K.-Y.</first><last>Jen</last></author></authors><keys><key>perovskite</key><key>merged:cgoehler</key><key>Capacitance</key></keys><date>2017-05-17 12:50:14</date><changeDate>2017-05-17 12:50:14</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2017</year><url>http://dx.doi.org/10.1002/adfm.201701053</url><abstract>Photodetectors with ultrafast response are explored using inorganic/organic hybrid perovskites. High responsivity and fast optoelectronic response are achieved due to the exceptional semiconducting properties of perovskite materials. However, most of the perovskite-based photodetectors exploited to date are centered on Pb-based perovskites, which only afford spectral response across the visible spectrum. This study demonstrates a high-performance near-IR (NIR) photodetector using a stable low-bandgap Sn-containing perovskite, (CH3NH3)0.5(NH2CHNH2)0.5Pb0.5Sn0.5I3 (MA0.5FA0.5Pb0.5Sn0.5I3), which is processed with an antioxidant additive, ascorbic acid (AA). The addition of AA effectively strengthens the stability of Sn-containing perovskite against oxygen, thereby significantly inhibiting the leakage current. Consequently, the derived photodetector shows high responsivity with a detectivity of over 1012 Jones ranging from 800 to 970 nm. Such low-cost, solution processable NIR photodetectors with high performance show promising potential for future optoelectronic applications.</abstract><journal>Advanced Functional Materials</journal><pages>n/a--n/a</pages><issn>1616-3028</issn><doi>10.1002/adfm.201701053</doi></publication><publication><id>han_112</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2d08dd2770ce7773be87595a612408040/ashvath</bibsomy_id><title>Library Information Retrieval (IR) System of University of Cyprus (UCY)</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Antreas</first><last>Dionysiou</last></author></authors><keys><key>Retrieval,</key><key>myown</key><key>User</key><key>Web</key><key>merged:ashvath</key><key>Elasticsearch,</key><key>Search</key><key>Information</key><key>Technologies,</key><key>Engine</key><key>Experience,</key></keys><date>2019-07-01 06:50:13</date><changeDate>2019-07-01 06:50:13</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2019</year><url>https://airccse.com/ijcsitce/papers/6119ijcsitce02.pdf</url><abstract>Building an effective Information Retieval (IR) System for such a complex sector like a library, is indeed a challenging task. Creating this kind of applications, one must be aware of basic IR methodologies and structures used, as well as the User’s Experience requirements. Combining different technologies for creating different kinds of applications has been one of the major  problems in software reuse. However, in recent years, many frameworks that offer a complete suite for developing cross-platform applications have been developed. In this paper, we present a combination of breakthrough technologies and frameworks for developing a Python based RestAPI, an Administrator’s side desktop application and a cross-platform application powered by Ionic, Angular, HTML and CSS, as the main IR tool of UCY’s library.</abstract><journal>International Journal of Computational Science, Information Technology and Control Engineering (IJCSITCE)</journal><volume>6</volume><number>1</number><pages>9-20</pages><doi>10.5121/ijcsitce.2019.6102</doi></publication><publication><id>han_113</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/25fcb5287c7c5b1bf5025cddfc7da0c70/tillk</bibsomy_id><title>Traditional IR for web users: a context for general audience digital libraries</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Dietmar</first><last>Wolfram</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>Hong</first><last>Xie</last></author></authors><keys><key>suchkiste</key><key>merged:tillk</key><key>ungelesen</key></keys><date>2009-02-22 19:56:18</date><changeDate>2009-02-22 19:56:18</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2002</year><url>http://portal.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=637512.637515&amp;coll=GUIDE&amp;dl=GUIDE&amp;CFID=23119749&amp;CFTOKEN=18730145</url><abstract>The emergence of general audience digital libraries (GADLs) defines a context that represents a hybrid of both "traditional" IR, using primarily bibliographic resources provided by database vendors, and "popular" IR, exemplified by public search systems available on the World Wide Web. Findings of a study investigating end-user searching and response to a GADL are reported. Data collected from a Web-based end-user survey and data logs of resource usage for a Web-based GADL were analyzed for user characteristics, patterns of access and use, and user feedback. Cross-tabulations using respondent demographics revealed several key differences in how the system was used and valued by users of different age groups. Older users valued the service more than younger users and engaged in different searching and viewing behaviors. The GADL more closely resembles traditional retrieval systems in terms of content and purpose of use, but is more similar to popular IR systems in terms of user behavior and accessibility. A model that defines the dual context of the GADL environment is derived from the data analysis and existing IR models in general and other specific contexts. The authors demonstrate the distinguishing characteristics of this IR context, and discuss implications for the development and evaluation of future GADLs to accommodate a variety of user needs and expectations.</abstract><journal>Inf. Process. Manage.</journal><volume>38</volume><number>5</number><pages>627--648</pages><issn>0306-4573</issn><doi>http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/S0306-4573(01)00056-5</doi><publisher>Pergamon Press, Inc.</publisher></publication><publication><id>han_114</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/2a5714e1031000a9b87dc323a4f632936/jrennstich</bibsomy_id><title>Rereading Early Twentieth-Century Ir Theory: Idealism Revisited</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>Andreas</first><last>Osiander</last></author></authors><keys><key>liberalism</key><key>merged:jrennstich</key><key>ir</key><key>text</key><key>teaching</key><key>theory</key></keys><date>2010-03-02 17:25:53</date><changeDate>2010-03-02 17:26:53</changeDate><pub-type>article</pub-type><year>2002</year><url /><abstract>The article presents a 'revisionist' synopsis of the thinking of some important early twentieth-century 'Idealist' IR writers. I contend that these writers ground their interpretations of international relations on a shared paradigm that has hitherto gone largely unrecognised. Following a critique of certain widely held views of IR Idealism, I draw attention to a number of aspects or themes in this body of writing in an attempt to establish the underlying paradigm. I argue that the authors in question were familiar with the type of thinking that later came to be called Realist, but held that industrial modernisation rendered it increasingly anachronistic and dangerous. The crucial difference between Idealism and Realism is in their respective theories of history. In order to understand Idealist IR thinking, it is essential to realise the extent to which it relies on the notion, not so much of progress (as is usually asserted) as of an inescapable, directional historical process.</abstract><journal>International Studies Quarterly</journal><volume>42</volume><number>3</number><pages>409--43</pages></publication><publication><id>han_115</id><bibsomy_id>https://www.bibsonomy.org/bibtex/24430ae6f13a3b297847c409badf967c7/miki</bibsomy_id><title>Modelling the number density of Halpha emitters for future spectroscopic
  near-IR space missions</title><authors><author><nr>1</nr><first>L.</first><last>Pozzetti</last></author><author><nr>2</nr><first>C. M.</first><last>Hirata</last></author><author><nr>3</nr><first>J. E.</first><last>Geach</last></author><author><nr>4</nr><first>A.</first><last>Cimatti</last></author><author><nr>5</nr><first>C.</first><last>Baugh</last></author><author><nr>6</nr><first>O.</first><last>Cucciati</last></author><author><nr>7</nr><first>A.</first><last>Merson</last></author><author><nr>8</nr><first>P.</first><last>Norberg</last></author><author><nr>9</nr><first>D.</first><last>Shi</last></author></authors><keys><key>Halpha</key><key>emitters</key><key>function</key><key>luminosity</key><key>density</key><key>merged:miki</key></keys><date>2016-03-07 08:51:51</date><changeDate>2016-03-07 08:51:51</changeDate><pub-type>misc</pub-type><year>2016</year><url>http://arxiv.org/abs/1603.01453</url><note>cite arxiv:1603.01453Comment: 16 pages, 7 figures, A&amp;A (in press, preprint version available  online). Models can be downloaded at  http://www.bo.astro.it/~pozzetti/Halpha/Halpha.html</note><abstract>The future space missions Euclid and WFIRST-AFTA will use the Halpha emission
line to measure the redshifts of tens of millions of galaxies. The Halpha
luminosity function at z&gt;0.7 is one of the major sources of uncertainty in
forecasting cosmological constraints from these missions. We construct unified
empirical models of the Halpha luminosity function spanning the range of
redshifts and line luminosities relevant to the redshift surveys proposed with
Euclid and WFIRST-AFTA. By fitting to observed luminosity functions from Halpha
surveys, we build three models for its evolution. Different fitting
methodologies, functional forms for the luminosity function, subsets of the
empirical input data, and treatment of systematic errors are considered to
explore the robustness of the results. Functional forms and model parameters
are provided for all three models, along with the counts and redshift
distributions up to z~2.5 for a range of limiting fluxes (F_Halpha&gt;0.5 - 3 x
10^-16 erg cm^-2 s^-1) that are relevant for future space missions. For
instance, in the redshift range 0.90&lt;z&lt;1.8, our models predict an available
galaxy density in the range 7700--13300 and 2000--4800 deg^-2 respectively at
fluxes above F_Halpha&gt;1 and 2 x 10^-16 erg cm^-2 s^-1, and 32000--48000 for
F_Halpha&gt;0.5 x 10^-16 erg cm^-2 s^-1 in the extended redshift range 0.40&lt;z&lt;1.8.
We also consider the implications of our empirical models for the total Halpha
luminosity density of the Universe, and the closely related cosmic star
formation history.</abstract></publication></publications>